Chapter 565: Taking a Vacation

Laura and the others understood Zhao Hai by now. Zhao Hai was a person with little ambition. If he wasn’t compelled to upgrade his Space, they wouldn’t have reached their current status.

At this time, a voice was heard from the courtyard, Zhao Hai then allowed Megan to open the door. What they saw were people coming into the courtyard. There were two middle-aged people and in their sides were two seemingly 20-year old men.

Kristen was standing in between the two middle-aged people, acting like a spoiled child. Zhao Hai deduced that these two people might be Kristen’s parents.

Sure enough, when Kristen saw Zhao Hai open the door, she immediately spoke some words to the couple. The two looked at Zhao Hai and walked over and together they said, “We thank Patriarch Zhao Hai for saving our daughter’s life, please accept our gratitude.”

Zhao Hai quickly returned the gesture and said, “This one wouldn’t dare, it’s just a small help.”

At this point, Juno came as Zhao Hai was talking to Kristen’s parents. He smiled faintly and then said, “It’s good that you’re back, let’s invite Patriarch Zhao Hai for a meal.”

Kristen’s father immediately nodded and then turned his head to Zhao Hai and gestured his hand, “Please accept our Hurricane family’s invitation. Patriarch Zhao Hai, Ladies, please.” Zhao Hai complied, and then he led Laura and the others as he followed the Hurricane Family to the dining room.

Although Kristen’s home wasn’t a castle and their yard was not big, they still had a place specifically used for dining. However, it’s furniture weren’t up to par with the other Great Nobles. The chairs and tables looked like they were used for many years. Although it was much better than commoners’ homes, it was much worse compared to nobles.

Juno was there waiting for Zhao Hai and the others in the dining room. After the group sat down, Juno’s wife immediately had the dished served.

After seeing the dishes, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. This Hurricane Family surely is very interesting. They’re chosen to live this kind of village life, they lived with ordinarly old furniture, and the way they received their guests was the same as how country people receive them.

When Nobles eat meals, they would generally choose relatively good food, the more expensive the better. But country people were different, vegetables, fish, and meat were already good food. The Hurricane Family seems to embody this philosophy as well.

This was the first time that Laura and the others had this kind of food, so they felt very curious. On the other hand, Zhao Hai wasn’t, instead, what he felt was warmth. Back on Earth, he had eaten meals like this all the time.

Juno repeatedly offered Zhao Hai the dishes, and Zhao Hai didn’t decline. He ate the meal as he chatted with Juno, the meal was very relaxed and comfortable.

Zhao Hai discovered that the Hurricane Family people were very nice to speak to. Moreover, they don’t talk like other nobles. You don’t need to worry about your words, afraid of offending them. They also didn’t go and probe your background, the Hurricane Family just wanted to talk about day to day activities.

After having eaten their meal, the group went to the living room and sat. Kristen’s mother had served them something to drink. Kristen and the ladies, as well as Kristen’s grandmother, left the room, leaving only Zhao Hai and Juno inside.

After taking a drink, Zhao Hai looked at Juno and said, “Elder, I just want to ask. What do you want to do about the recent matter?”

The matter that Zhao Hai meant was naturally the attack on Kristen. He wanted to know how Juno wanted to deal with it. If Juno doesn’t want to make a move, then there would be no need for Zhao Hai to touch the Radiant Church. Otherwise, if he made a move this time, claiming that the Radiant Church attacked Kristen but the Hurricane Family doesn’t have his back, then he would be placed in an awkward position.

If the Hurricane Family wanted to deal with the Radiant Church, then Zhao Hai can lend a hand, revealing this matter to the entire continent, making people raise their vigilance.

After Juno heard Zhao Hai, his eyes immediately shined as he said, “Does Mister mean the attack on Kristen? I’m still quite not sure, but it’s for certain that I won’t let this matter go. Mister Zhao Hai should also understand that even if the Buddha Empire was afraid of being controlled by the Radiant Church, suppressing it, the Church still has their presence inside the Empire. If we deal with them now, they would definitely fight back. And that would not be good.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he knew that Juno was right. Seeing Zhao Hai nod, Juno continued, “Therefore, I want to spread this matter in the meantime, letting everyone be on guard against the Radiant Church. I think that as long as the continent knew about this, then they would definitely think of ways to deal with the Radiant Church.”

Zhao Hai nodded again and then said, “This action is also good. Dealing with the Radiant Church couldn’t be done in a single day. If the Radiant Church’s attack on Kristen were to spread, the people would surely dread the church. In the future, it would be much more difficult for the church to attack individual people. Moreover, Great Nobles would also start suppressing them even more. Soon enough, the Radiant Church wouldn’t be able to take advantage of any situation.”

Juno nodded and said, “This is the only thing that we could do right now. But I can also be sure that the Radiant Church wouldn’t let our Hurricane Family go with just this. Although our Hurricane Family doesn’t have enemies, it doesn’t mean that nobody can bully us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Elder should already know about my Buda Clan’s enmity with the Radiant Church. If Elder needs anything from us, feel free to send word.”

Juno laughed and said, “Alright, if our Hurricane Family goes to war with the Radiant Church, then we would certainly ask the Buda Clan for help.”

When Zhao Hai heard Juno’s words, he couldn’t help but feel elated. Juno had already regarded the Buda Clan as allies, and for the clan, this was a great thing.

However, Zhao Hai can also see that Juno doesn’t want to specifically state this alliance. But it still made Zhao Hai happy, having a potential ally was already very good.

In the next several days, Zhao Hai and the others lived in Juno’s residence. The farmers woke up very early, although Zhao Hai and the others don’t wake up very late, they were still much worse than them.

Moreover, from these past several days, Zhao Hai also understood that the performance of the Hurricane Family towards him was not deliberately done. This was because in Zhao Hai’s stay in Juno’s residence, he can see that the Bamboo rice being planted and taken care of were all done with care. The other farmers who were around Juno’s residence were also greeting Juno every single day. It was quite obvious that this was their day to day life.

After observing for several days, Zhao Hai discovered that the Hurricane Family was quite a loose family. They don’t look like they share a common family, but just their surname. The people in the family generally lived on their own. Although they had a Patriarch, his authority wasn’t as strong as in the other Noble families. Every year, the Patriarch would go and collect the taxes, but this tax would also be circulated back into the family.

Compared to the other Nobles, the position of Patriarch in the Hurricane Family was more of a rallying position than a position of power.

However, if one were to say that the Hurricane Family was dispersed, then they would also be very wrong. The Hurricane Family still had their faith in the Wind God, and each person was fully devoted to the belief. Although they live separately, once a ceremony was required, all of them went in as one. They were more solid than any average Noble family.

Zhao Hai had lived for five days in Juno’s residence. And he spent this five days mostly outdoors. He was going all around the mountain and looking at the Bamboo Rice as well as the Oil Trees. He also chatted with the villagers and came to know them by name.

Regarding Zhao Hai’s actions, Juno couldn’t help but be surprised. Juno has also heard about Zhao Hai’s background. He was a playboy from his younger years, but when their clan suffered disaster, he suddenly encountered a fortuitous encounter and managed to make the Buda Clan into what it is today.

However, Juno also thought that Zhao Hai didn’t know about the habits and customs of a village. After all, Zhao Hai lived in a major city in the past. He may go outside at the very least, once every year. But this one time might only be about business, or to fight another person. For him to be able to get comfortable in a village was impossible if he didn’t live in one in the past. So how was he very familiar with it right now?

Zhao Hai was obviously very used to it, moreover, he looks like he has lived in a village for majority of his life. This made Juno confused. Actually, what made Juno most surprised was the conduct of Zhao Hai’s wives.

With their identities, Juno had always thought that they were going to be delicate ladies, just like princesses. Compared to their previous living arrangements, this village setting of the Hurricane Family was too simple and crude.

However, Laura and the others were acting pretty normal, they can actually move on their own. They also weren’t very curious about crops like the Bamboo Rice or the Oil Trees. In fact, it was the opposite, they knew a lot about the Bamboo Rice and the Oil trees, this was very surprising for the old man.

Although Juno was very surprised about Zhao Hai’s group, he didn’t attempt to probe them or ask. In the recent days, Zhao Hai was also not talking about the matter with the Dwarves, nor about the matters with the Buda Clan and the Radiant Church. Zhao Hai seemed to enjoy his current state, one could see the joy and bliss reflected on his face.

Five days passed by in a blink of an eye. And on the morning of the next day, Zhao Hai and the others got up early, combed their hair, and washed their face before going to the dining room to have breakfast. Breakfast in the countryside was very simple, and since they were already familiar with Juno, they didn’t need to act too polite.

Juno was already waiting for them in the dining room. After the group sat down, Juno smiled to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you should prepare yourself. We’ll be departing for Dwarf Mountain today.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Alright. Actually, there’s no need to prepare anything, I’m ready to go anytime.” To be honest, he wasn’t actually thinking about leaving this village life, he was enjoying himself here. The five days that Zhao Hai spent here was the most comfortable he had been in the past year. It seemed very much like a vacation, making Zhao Hai very reluctant to leave.

But as it seems, it looks like the vacation has ended.

Chapter 566: Frightened

Standing on the deck of the Haven, Juno’s facial expression was very calm while Zhao Hai was there standing at his side. They were now navigating back in Iron Warhorse River.

The Hurricane Family’s five-master ship had received some damages in the fight, so it was now under repair. Therefore, when they departed this time, they used Zhao Hai’s ship.

Not only did Iron Warhorse River span the entire Buddha Empire, it was also quite deep and very wide. The river was an important lifeline for the Buddha Empire’s prosperity.

The end of the river was a place not far from the Dwarf Mountains. This was very convenient for Zhao Hai, as they were now heading towards the Dwarves.

They had been sailing for four days after they left the Hurricane Family’s territory. In about three days, they should reach the end of the river.

While looking at the river’s scenery, Juno sighed and said, “It’s been quite a few years since I’ve left the territory, I don’t know how those old folks were doing. Little Hai, this trip to the Dwarves, I can only be responsible for introducing you to them. You must know that the Dwarves are very stubborn. If they decided to not trade with you, then nobody’s words can change their minds. Right, what kind of things do you intend to trade with them?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They’re Dwarves, naturally I’d want their metalwares. I intend to trade them with liquor in exchange.”

Juno stared, then he laughed and said, “Good, that’s a great idea. Those fellows do indeed love drinking. If you give them great wines, they would surely do business with you. Right, what liquor are you selling? Is it Milk Wine?”

Zhao Hai’s best selling liquor was also made known to Juno. Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Yes, but I intend to trade them with a higher quality Milk Wine.”

Juno smiled and said, “That’s good. There’s no better business with Dwarves other than liquor. I’ve also tried your Milk WIne, they’re very good. Especially that higher quality one, it’s fragrant.”

The higher quality milk wine that Juno mentioned was actually the Milk Wine made from cow’s milk. This was because cow’s milk was much mellower compared to argali milk. Making it’s flavor much better, therefore, making a much better wine. Of course, the sellers needed to differentiate and describe the difference of the two, otherwise, the other Nobles wouldn’t be able to tell the difference.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Grandpa Juno, if you like, I’ll have a batch given to you. In any case, those are my products. Me giving them away wouldn’t be a big deal.”

Juno smiled and said, “Alright, after we head back, you leave some behind for me. By now, I find the other wines quite tasteless. I must say Little Hai, you’ve been living a great life on board your ship.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’m not really that comfortable. As you can see, I always move around, doing things here and there.”

Juno smiled and said, “No need to underplay yourself Little Hai, just let this old man complain here for a little bit. Right, Dwarves are generally good people. But don’t go and deceive them, if they find out, they wouldn’t be able to let you off easily.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, I already know this. I quite understand their character, after all, they seem to be like the Beastmen.”

Juno smiled and said, “Alright, just be good. Also, Dwarves can take jokes, you can even tease them about their height, and they will never get angry. However, if you say something bad about their metalwares, they will immediately get enraged. Doing that is not a good idea.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I’ll remember that. I will certainly watch my mouth. In fact, most of these ironware would be supplied to the Beastmen. If not for their needs for weapons, I wouldn’t be coming here.”

Juno nodded, the reason why he reminded Zhao Hai about this point was because he was afraid that Zhao Hai would undercut the price by intentionally saying that the Dwarf goods are no good. If that happens, Zhao Hai would definitely be offending the entire Dwarf Race.

However, when Juno heard that Zhao Hai wanted to get the majority of these ironware for the Beastmen, he immediately became curious. The Milk Wines that Zhao Hai had been selling was definitely related to the Beastmen. What made people confused was that the Milk Wine that Zhao Hai sells were much better than those of the Beastmen. It was actually a peculiar thing.

Juno looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Do you have a good relationship with the Beastmen?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’m friends with the Cow and Dog Race. I have good relationship with the Black Bears and I also have some deals with the Hawks recently. As for the other races, I don’t have too much contact with them.”

Juno nodded, then he smiled faintly and said, “The Radiant Church had just made a huge blunder back in Aksu Empire. Does this matter have something to do with you?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he shook his head and said, “I don’t. I only received rumors about the matter with the Radiant Church and the Aksu Empire. I don’t know any of the specifics. You should know that me and the Radiant Church don’t really look eye to eye. So it’s quite impossible for me to know about their matters. My scouts don’t have supernatural activities to know about their secret plans. Also how could the Radiant Church let untrusted people know about specific things?”

Juno nodded, he believed Zhao Hai’s words. The Radiant Church attached great importance to this matter, otherwise they wouldn’t have sent a red robed Archbishop to manage their operation. However, this defeat still baffled a lot of people. Nobody knew how the Beastmen found out about the Radiant Church’s plan, causing the Church to lose a lot.

Even if the continent was confused, there weren’t a lot of people who suspected Zhao Hai. The continent knew about the enmity between Zhao Hai and the Radiant Church. The Radiant Church naturally knew about this, so they should be on guard against Zhao Hai.

At the same time, the Buda Clan was also still an emerging Clan, their background was insufficient. Moreover, Zhao Hai also had a falling out with the entire Aksu Empire, almost no family in the Aksu Empire was on his side. Although his relationship with the Iksa Family and the Purcell Family was good, the Iksa Family was already gone before the Beastman attack while the Purcell Duchy was turned into sacrificial paws by the Radiant Church. Therefore, there would be no way for Zhao Hai to find out about anything.

Because of this, after the war, no matter how strange the Radiant Church’s defeat was, nobody had any thoughts that Zhao Hai would have a hand on the Church’s demise.

When summarizing the reasons of their failure, although the Radiant Church had turned their internal and external arrangements inside out, they still didn’t place any suspicions towards Zhao Hai. In their minds, even if the Buda Clan was strong, their information gathering aspect was still very weak.

It was impossible for the people of the continent to even come up with the existence of the Space. They were still stuck in thinking about the normal modes of gathering information.

But still, Juno’s question made Zhao Hai break into a cold sweat. It was great that they had prepared an excuse for this. He didn’t want any other people to know that he had used the Beastmen to deal with the Radiant Church. The lesser people knew the better.

The people of the continent might be repulsed with the Radiant Church, but they still think of them as fellow Humans. If they came to know that Zhao Hai sided with the Beastmen in order to deal a blow to the Radiant Church, then they might make Zhao Hai into the number one enemy of the Humans.

It was also good that there were only a few Beastmen who knew about Zhao Hai’s hand in the matter. The general populace only believed that there was a mysterious person that helped them. After all, when Zhao Hai visited the Beastman camp, he donned the disguise of another person.

If there were people to suspect, then it might be the Engraved Ark. This organization was very mysterious, moreover, they wanted to subvert the Ark Continent. Such matters was what they might possibly do.

Juno had just blurted this question out thoughtlessly and didn’t take it to heart. But even if Zhao Hai told him that he used the Beastmen against the Radiant Church, he still wouldn’t it say anything. After all, if the Beastmen were to attack the Aksu Empire, they would be dealing a huge blow against the Radiant Church.

And with their recent attack to his Granddaughter, Kristen, Juno was even more unsupportive towards the Church. Juno had a lot of children, but the one he favors the most was Kristen’s father. He already set his heart on having Kristen’s father as the future Patriarch of the Family. However, the one Juno loved the most was Kristen. Therefore, the Radiant Church attacking Kristen had managed to touch Juno’s bottom line.

The Hurricane Family were good-natured people, but this didn’t mean that they would just endure. In their early years, the reason why the Hurricane Family was able to hold on to their territory was because they also punched back. If the Hurricane Family fully mobilized this time, their might would not be worse than the other millenium-old family. They weren’t even behind in terms of their wealth. It was only because of their ancestral doctrine that they maintained this kind of life.

In fact, even if Juno said that it was not the time to deal with the Radiant Church, he already sent some people towards the Churches of the Radiant Church inside the Buddha Empire. Nobody from the Radiant Church was spared.

Being a good person didn’t mean that you didn’t have any temper. If people hit your left face, you turn back and hit their right. If one doesn’t fight back, it didn’t mean that you have great values, it also means that you are without spine.

The reason why Juno told Zhao Hai that he didn’t want to move against the Radiant Church was because he didn’t want Zhao Hai to know. Juno knew about how big Zhao Hai’s enmity with the Radiant Church was. If Juno told Zhao Hai, then it was inevitable that Zhao Hai would help, elevating the matter by another lever. In the current case, the matter was still under Juno’s control.

Chapter 567: Dwarf Iron Mountain

While the ship was sailing along Iron Warhorse River, they could spot three-masted and five-masted ships sailing with them. These ships had displaced a lot of water, showing people how much cargo they were carrying.

They were already not far from the pier for Dwarf Mountain. From the direction these ships were heading, it seems like they were all packing a lot of iron and iron goods inside.

When people mention Dwarven ironware, they might think of weapons. But in reality, there were a lot of ironware that were from the Dwarves. Everything that can be made out of iron was also made by the Dwarves.

Moreover, Dwarves don’t only create things from iron, they also use a variety of metals as well. Their gold and silver items also held some fame in the continent, but not as much as their ironware.

Weapons that Dwarves produce might be crude and simple, but the products they make from precious metals were absurdly magnificent, looking like they were art. Even Elves cannot be compared to how innately skilled the Dwarves were in this aspect.

Like what was heard, the Dwarves had been hollowing out huge portions of Dwarf Mountain. At the same time, they also knew that the mountain would run out of iron eventually, so they also started to recycle some iron. Iron was easy to reuse, the Dwarves can just remelt some dscared iron products to make new ones.

Because of this, whether ships were heading or leaving Dwarf Mountain, all of them had iron in their cargo.

Zhao Hai also knew about this practice of the Dwarves, but they don’t need a lot of people to bring them iron. Right now, they already have Merchants, specifically tasked to get them some scrap iron. One could say that the development of the Dwarves were much better than the Beastmen.

Before long, the Haven slowly came to a stop at the pier. The pier was very big, the ships that were moored along it were a lot. Zhao Hai also noticed that of the ships present, almost all of them were owned by Buddha Empire Nobles, he couldn’t spot any ships belonging from the other nations.

But what intrigued Zhao Hai the most about this pier was the pier managers. These people were very short, the tallest of them was only about 1.5 meters. However, their figures were very sturdy, they wore iron armor while everyone of them carried a hammer at their back.

This hammer wasn’t the same as the weapons of Ancient China. This hammer looks like it was used to hammer iron, but it’s very big, they seem to weigh a couple of dozen jins each.

In addition to the hammer, the Dwarves also wore iron armor. The amount of load that each of them carried was at minimum about 100 jin. But from their appearances, it seems like it didn’t bother them, showing how formidable their strengths were.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai had seen a Dwarf. These people had brown hair and a full beard on their faces, they also had a slight blush on their cheeks, probably from all the drinking that they had done.

After the ship stooped, Zhao Hai walked down from it along with Juno. Before long, two Dwarves approached them, the two bowed slightly to Zhao Hai and Juno and said, “Are you two doing business?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Dwarf friend, this one is Buda Clan’s Zhao Hai. I came this time to do business. Since this is my first time, I have been accompanied with the Hurricane Family’s Patriarch.

When the Dwarf heard Zhao Hai that the person beside him was the Hurricane Family’s patriarch, his face immediately changed to respect as he bowed to Juno and said, “So it turns out to be Patriarch Juno. We’ve been very rude, please come with us.”

It seemed like they had ignored Zhao Hai’s self introduction. Zhao Hai can only stare blankly for a moment before bitterly smiling.

The Buda Clan was now quite famous in the Continent, however, these Dwarves seem to not know about him. This had two possibilities, it might be because they really haven’t heard about Zhao Hai, or they might have taken a dislike towards him.

Juno looked at the Dwarf and calmly said, “This is Mister Zhao Hai, Buda Clan’s Patriarch, he is a friend of mine.”

Quite ordinary words, but these made the Dwarf stare. Then he turned to Zhao Hai with a look of unfriendliness and said, “Buda Clan? Rosen Empire’s Buda Clan?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Is there a problem?”

The Dwarf looked at Zhao Hai and said, “It’s been a long time since people from the Rosen Empire has come here. The last merchant from the Rosen Empire sold us moldy bamboo rice.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Dwarf, he stared for a moment before he faintly smiled and said, “Really? Is he from the Buda Clan?”

The Dwarf didn’t expect this to be Zhao Hai’s response. He also understood what Zhao Hai meant. The Dwarf couldn’t help but laugh and said, “I like you. Patriarch Zhao Hai, please.”

Juno nodded at the side in commendation. If Zhao Hai defended the Rosen Empire merchants, then it would become impossible for him to do any business with the Dwarves. It’s good that Zhao Hai’s answer made these Dwarves quite delighted.

Zhao Hai also discovered that these Dwarves aren’t the same as the Beastmen. Beastmen were direct, but they weren’t as smart as the Dwarves. Even if the Dwarves were also direct, they also had more contact with Humans and knew about how to read them.

Zhao Hai’s group left the pier along with the two Dwarves, then the Dwarves got the group some carriages. The carriage was fairly big, it was pulled by a Magic Beast that Zhao Hai has not seen before. This one looked like pangolin, however, their heads looked like a cross between a horse and a bull.

After the carriage arrived, the two Dwarves immediately invited Zhao Hai’s group to ride it. The Dwarves then talked with the group while inside. Naturally, the two were much more respectful towards Juno.

Seeing their conduct, Zhao Hai can’t do anything but just smile. From what he can see on the expressions of the Dwarves, it seems like Juno held quite a high standing in their hearts.

When Juno noticed that Zhao Hai was curious about the Magic Beast, he smiled and said, “This beast is called Iron Armor Beast, a unique Magic Beast of the Dwarven Race. It’s a great complement to them as it is very good at excavating earth as well as digging through mountains. At the same time, through proper training, these can also help the Dwarves find iron ore deposits. However, this Magic Beast also has its peculiarities. Other than the Dwarves, these beasts are unable to be trained by Humans or any other races. Because of this, the Dwarves had always believed that this beast was a gift to them but the Artisan God.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he didn’t think that this was false. After all,  there were a lot of strange things in the Ark Continent. Maybe there were really gods looking at the continent from some other place.

The Iron Armor beast walked very steadily, moreover, it’s speed was not very slow. It didn’t take a long time before Zhao Hai and the others saw the mountain in the distance. This mountain was very different from the Hurricane Family’s territory. Back in the Hurricane Family’s place, bamboo rice and oil trees can be seen everywhere, but here, Zhao Hai can only spot a single plant that he hadn’t seen before.

This tree is very strange, it’s trunk was very straight and very black. However, it wasn’t very thick. On top of the tree were some branches, each branch had about five or six extensions on them. At the same time, there were more than ten leaves on each branch, each leaf was very big, about more than one meter long and were very thin. One could get an impression of a spear upon seeing the dark green leaves. The entire tree gives one a feeling of weight and sharpness.

For a tree to give a sharp feeling was very strange. At this time, Juno opened his mouth and said, “This is called a Spear Tree. It’s branch, leaves, and trunk can all be made into spears of high quality. They are also quite heavy, much heavier than average spears. However, they are also very tough, they are one of the specialty goods in Dwarf Mountain.

Zhao Hai nodded, but deep inside he was excited. He really felt that he hadn’t wasted his time in coming here. These unique things in Dwarf Mountain are very helpful. Even if they cannot upgrade the Space, he can still acquire them for future use.

Zhao Hai was now anticipating his visit towards the Elven Forest. If the Dwarves, who were famous for the ironware, already had these unique plants and beasts, then what would the Elves, who were famous for their unique plants, have? It was no wonder that Zhao Hai looked forward to his visit.

Dwarf Iron Mountain was very tall, not worse than any other tall mountain in the continent. The mountain was part of a very long mountain range, comparable only to Hawk King Mountain.

Before long, the Iron Armor Beast carriage entered the mountain. Upon entering, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk, the scale of this place simply placed the lake chamber back at Iron Mountain to shame.

But there was no water in this mountain chamber, on the contrary, it looked just like a huge factory. Blacksmiths and their furnaces can be seen everywhere. Shirtless Dwarves, were all hard at work, hammering their metals and producing some ‘ding’ ‘ding’ sounds along the way. The noise in this place would compel you to shout at someone beside you just to talk to them.

Inside, weapons and various products can be seen everywhere. All kinds of full body armor were also being made. Various Dwarves can be seen loading and unloading goods here and there, however, no Human merchants can be seen inside.

Zhao Hai was actually afraid of the noise inside, he felt like his head was about to explode. But fortunately, it didn’t take too long before the carriage went out of the other side of the mountain, bringing them back to the quiet atmosphere once again.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath and then said, “That was too scary. If I stay for a day inside there, then I might get killed by the noise. How can the Dwarves endure it?”

Juno smiled and said, “They don’t need for the Dwarves to endure, you didn’t notice, but all of them were wearing ear plugs. With those, they don’t need to worry about the noise. Inside the mountain, Dwarves wouldn’t even open their mouths, they only use hand signals to communicate with one another.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “So it’s like this. But I find something strange. Why haven’t I seen any Human merchants in there?”

Juno smiled, “There are several places in the mountain that Humans can use to interact with the Dwarves clearly. After making clear about their transactions, the Dwarves would carry their orders out by themselves while the Humans would leave the mountain. Otherwise, Humans might become insane if they stay inside for a long time, .”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to inspect the surroundings, they were now exiting the first mountain. What was in front of Zhao Hai were a chain of other mountains stretching as far as his eyes can see. On these mountains, Spear Trees can be seen growing with no end in sight.

Zhao Hai knew that this was the real Dwarf Mountain. The area of this group of mountains was very large, it was no less than the entire Beastman Prairie.

Juno looked at the stretch of mountains and said, “Everyone knew about the Dwarf Mountain, but there were only a few of them who knew about the real Dwarf territory. Only friends of the Dwarves can see this scene. If one wasn’t someone that the Dwarves trust, then they can only go up to that first mountain.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’m very lucky to have Grandpa Juno with me this time. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have seen such a scene.”

Juno smiled faintly and said, “You don’t need to be too polite with me. If I don’t see you as a good Merchant, then I wouldn’t be taking you here. Why did you think I accompanied you personally? If you’re not a good merchant, let along saving Kristen, even if you saved the entire Hurricane Family, I still wouldn’t take you here. I treat the Dwarves as my friends, and I can not do any disservice towards them.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Laura and the others were quite all this time. They were enthralled by the scenery outside. This time, Juno only brought a few people from his family, they were on the carriages behind. Shue and Shun were also present on one of those carriages.

It didn’t take a long time before the Iron Armor Beast entered a second mountain. This mountain was also very big, with a lot of Dwarves being busy inside as well. But there weren’t a lot of weapons that can be seen here, most of the things here were iron ores.

The carriage continued to go along the mountain range. Zhao Hai also felt that each mountain that they passed, their altitude seemed to get lower. It seemed like the road that they were on was on a gentle slope.

Before long, the Iron Armor Beast stopped. Then Juno turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s head out, we still need to ride a boat.”

When he arrived outside, Zhao Hai looked around for a moment. This place was beside a mountain. There were a lot of Dwarves present here, loading and unloading their goods towards other Iron Armor Beast carriages.

On the side of this mountain was a pier with boats moored at its side. These boats weren’t big, however, they can still fit quite a number of people inside.

The Dwarf that drove their carriage arrived at Juno’s side and said, “Mister Juno, please come with me.” Juno nodded, and then he led Zhao Hai and the others to walk towards the pier.

After looking at the boats on the pier, Zhao Hai noticed that some of them were loaded with iron ore while some had nothing in them. Naturally, these empty boats were meant for them to ride on.

Chapter 568: Hammer

Under the guidance of the Dwarf, Zhao Hai and the others got up to ride the boat. While the Dwarf guided them, the other one was responsible for driving.

They traversed the underground quite steadily. While they were travelling, ZHao Hai can notice some magic lights coming from the walls of the river from time to time.

Inside the channel, boats can also be seen travelling in both directions. Their speeds were quite fast for boats, all of them were driven by Dwarves.

By utilizing the brightness from the Magic lamps, Zhao Hai can see that there were also some piers placed on the sides of the river. These piers also had some boats in it. Some of the boats were carrying iron ores, while some had weapons and armor.

Zhao Hai was now admiring the Dwarves, they’re really quite formidable. From what Zhao Hai can see, it seems like the Dwarves had scraped out entire mountains, making them into cities. How much skill did this need?

Juno sat on the ship and looked around before he sighed and said, “From the time I came here, nothing much has changed. But I can fairly remember that there weren’t a lot of magic lamps before, torches were mostly used back then.”

The lead Dwarf smiled at him and said, “Mister Juno, these lamps haven’t been replaced in ten years. We happened to find a Magic Crystal deposit not far from the mountain. Otherwise, we wouldn’t be replacing the torches with these Magic lamps.”

Juno nodded and said, “Your luck is really good. But since you discovered a Magic Crystal deposit, why haven’t you sold them?”

The Dwarf shook his head and said, “We can’t, there aren’t a lot of Magic Crystals in that deposit. The only thing we have is only enough for our use.”

Juno nodded. After sailing from quite some time in the underground river, they finally stopped at a pier. The Dwarf then led them to land and had them ride an Iron Beast carriage that was already waiting for them.

After the group entered the Iron Armor Beast carriage, they continued on to their travel along the mountain range. From what Zhao Hai can see in Juno’s expression, it seems like they were going to a special place.

Sure enough, when they came out of the mountain, a main road was seen. This road was very wide, it was paved with stone and it was extended from a distant the mountain. But from what Zhao Hai can see, the mountain was just like a tunnel, he can see the other side of it.

Upon entering the mountain, Zhao Hai immediately knew that he had made a mistake. The mountain was very big, moreover, a lot of Dwarf women were very busy inside.

Upon looking, Zhao Hai can see that there were tools for assembling full body armors. These armors were fish scale armors that infantry used. There were fully assembled armors as well as components waiting to be built.

After crossing the mountain, a building appeared not far away from the group. It was constructed like a temple very enormous and was constructed out of iron and iron ore. It was tall, about 20 meters in height, with 18 large stone pillars supporting it. The pillars were thick, each having about 5 meters in diameter.

There was a wide area in front of the building, about 10 thousand meters in diameter. The ground was paved with iron as well, making it very flat. Zhao Hai can see some people constantly cleaning the square.

Juno gave a sigh and said, “This is a sacred land of the Dwarf Race, the Artisan Divine Palace. It was originally a small mountain, but it was hollowed out by the Dwarves. The stones from the mountain became the foundation of the entire palace. Every year, the Dwarves would all come to this place to worship the Artisan God, it’s quite a spectacle.”

The Iron Armor Beast stopped on the square outside the Divine Palace. Then Juno turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Let’s head out, carriages are prohibited in the vicinity of the Divine Palace. We’ll give our respects to the Artisan God first before we see my old friends.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then followed Juno down. The Dwarf guide was also with them as the group slowly walked towards the Divine Palace. Zhao Hai can see a lot of dwarves in the square, cleaning. They seem to be of old age, judging from their white hair and beard.

Although the Dwarves noticed Zhao Hai and the others, they seem to not care about it as they continued to get busy in their job. Before long, Zhao Hai and the others were already near the Palace Great Hall.

The closer you get to the hall, the more of its grandeur that you feel. He didn’t know if it was an illusion, but Zhao Hai can feel a pressure inside the hall which made him very uncomfortable.

Zhao Hai and the others then entered the Great Hall upon which they were greeted with it’s beautiful interior, carvings and art that could be seen everywhere.

However, there wasn’t any statue inside the Great Hall, what made Zhao Hai surprised was that the only thing that was present here was a hammer.

Yes, Zhao Hai did not misjudge it, it was a red hammer. It’s like the hammers that the Dwarves use, but it was a bit smaller, about a couple of jin less heavy.

This hammer was just too small to be used by the Dwarves. It was even short enough to be called a one-handed hammer. But what made Zhao Hai confused was that this hammer had given him an immense pressure. The pressure was even greater than what he felt when he faced 9th rank experts.

When Juno saw that Zhao Hai was motionless as he looked at the hammer, he couldn’t help but stare. Hi didn’t understand why Zhao Hai was staring at the hammer. Juno had visited the Dwarves a hundred times before, and he had also seen this hammer, however, he just can’t see anything special about it.

The Dwarf guide had also noted Zhao Hai’s expression, which made him gawk, and then his two eyes shined. However, he didn’t say anything and just stepped towards the Hammer along with Juno and Zhao Hai.

Under the leadership of the Dwarf, the group paid their respects towards the hammer before they left the Great Hall. After leaving the hall, Juno then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, why did you stare at that hammer? Did you see anything strange?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, I just felt a very strong pressure from the hammer. I’ve faced 9th rank experts before, but I still wasn’t able to feel the kind of pressure that I got from the hammer. I felt that the hammer had a life, moreover, it seems to be much more formidable than a 9th rank expert.”

After Zhao Hai finished talking, the Dwarf guide in front turned around and faced Zhao Hai in shock.

The Dwarf looked at Zhao Hai for quite some time before he turned back and proceeded. Zhao Hai and Juno looked at each other in confusion before they followed the Dwarf.

After they went past the Great Hall, they were once again greeted with another big mountain. When they entered, Zhao Hai was astounded by the number of people inside here. These people weren’t here for work or to play with iron. From what was seen, it seems like this place was the living area of the Dwarves.

Juno looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Don’t be surprised, this is the place where Dwarves live. It’s almost the same as the village back at home.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he was still somewhat surprised upon inspecting these short Dwarves. Old Dwarves, Middle aged Dwarves, Dwarf children, all of them don’t feel any different. Dwarf children were like Human children in the way they play all around the place, the Dwarf women were there doing sewing and knitting while they chat with each other, old Dwarves were sitting in threes or fours chatting away while drinking wine.

Like Juno said, it wasn’t very different from any Human village. It was just that the people here were not Humans.

The Dwarf guide then led Zhao Hai and the others to enter the village. But before they went in, they stopped by the guards at the entrance as the guide said, “Please inform the Patriarch, Hurricane Family’s Patriarch Juno has come to visit.”

Just as the guide’s request was said, a voice was suddenly heard, “What? That old man Juno has come? Quick, quick, have him come over.”

Along with the voice, a Dwarf also appeared in front of the group. This Dwarf wasn’t young, he already had a white beard. The Dwarf was about 1.5 meters in height, and since he was a Dwarf, his build was very sturdy. He had a big pair of hands, each finger was very thick and full of calluses, all of them looked just like withered branches.

When this old Dwarf saw Juno, he couldn’t help but laugh as he hugged his old friend and patted him at the back, “You old fogy, I thought you had died. I didn’t expect you to suddenly visit. Hahahaha.”

Juno was obviously used to being greeted by the Dwarves this way, so he didn’t care, instead he returned the old Dwarf’s hug and said, “You as well, who thought that you’re still alive.”

Zhao Hai was on the side, looking at the two old men. They looked just like two bickering children as they chatted with each other. But even so, Zhao Hai can feel the deep friendship that was shared between the two.

After a moment of talking, Juno gestured towards Zhao Hai and said, “This is the Patriarch of the Buda Clan, Zhao Hai Buda. I accompanied him this time since he wanted to do business with you.”

Then Juno turned to Zhao Hai and said, “This is the Patriarch of the Dwarf Race, Billy.”[1]

Zhao Hai bowed and said, “Zhao Hai has seen Patriarch Billy.”

Billy sized Zhao Hai up, then he looked at Laura and the others at the back before he nodded and said, “Since you came with Juno, then you don’t need to be polite with me. Kid, come with me, take your group and get some rest at a room nearby.”

Zhao Hai didn’t decline, then he turned to give a nod to Laura and the others. The group then gave Billy another salute before retreating with the Dwarf guide.

* * *

This naming offends me, I don’t know why.

Chapter 569: Four Types of Liquor

Zhao Hai followed Billy and Juno into a cave in the mountain. The place looked very ordinary, probably something rarely used. On the cave was a big desk along with several bookshelves at the side.

Not far from the cave was a place for rest, with a set of wooden sofas and some tables.

After arriving at the resting area, Billy looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Kid, in just one year, you have made quite great achievements. The Buda Clan is now well known. I want to know what business you’ll have with us Dwarves.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I have some goods from my Buda Clan. I think the Patriarch also knew about my Clan’s Milk Wine.”

Zhao Hai knew that most of the other races were very direct, much more direct than humans. Therefore, he didn’t waste any words and just said what the other party wanted to hear.

Billy looked at Zhao Hai and then smiled. “I’ve drank your Milk Wine, it’s really good. Is it from your cooperation with the Beastmen?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “The Milk Wine that they make is still incomplete, it still needed further processing. Therefore, I struck a deal with the Beastman and had them supply me with Milk Wine. I’ll process those and then sell them to the Human territories.”

Billy nodded, “Your quite honest, Kid. Tell me, what do you need?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “i have a peculiar hobby, I like strange plants and unique Magic Beasts. As long as it’s rare, I’d want it. I can use my Milk Wine to trade with those things with you, naturally it includes iron wares as well. What do you think?”

Billy knit his eyebrows and said, “This is not a problem. But you should know that Magic Beasts like our Iron Armor Beast are unique to our Dwarf Race.  It’s not like we don’t want to give them away to the other races, but if the Iron Beasts were given to others, they would immediately starve themselves and die. At the same time, unique trees and plants in our mountain will not grow elsewhere. Are you fine with this?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’m merely curious about those things. I’ve also done the same with the Beastmen, so I’m quite familiar with the implications. In fact, I have some alchemists back at the clan, they also want to see those kinds of things. Therefore, I’m going out of my way to collect them.”

Billy didn’t say anything. In fact, there were a lot of unique plants and beasts in the hands of both the Dwarves and the Beastmen. It’s not like they don’t want to give them away, it’s just that they don’t have any uses. Because of that, they slowly went forgotten.

Billy nodded, “This is not an issue, these things are practically worthless. If you want to, there’s no problem in us giving you a few. Right, what price do you want to sell your milk wine?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Patriarch doesn’t need to worry, I’ll sell it at a normal price. The price that we sell at the mainland is what the price that I’ll be giving you.”

Billy stared at Zhao Hai and said, “Really?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “There’s no need to doubt me. If you go to the Beastman Prairie and inquire, you will know that our Buda Clan had always been fair in doing business. Compared to other merchants, the grain that we sell in the Prairie is priced much lower. There’s no reason for us to sell to the Dwarves at a high price.”

Judging by Zhao Hai’s expression, Billy can see if Zhao Hai was telling the truth or not. After thinking for a while, Billy nodded and said, “If this is the case, then it would be good for our Dwarf race. We’re living in the mountains all year round, the winds in here is very tough. So tough that we needed to drink some liquor after every meal. If you do supply us with this Milk Wine, then you would be doing us a great deed.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “In fact, I don’t only have Milk Wine in my hands, I also have other varieties of liquor. I’ll have to invite the two elders to have a taste.” Then he waved his hand and took out a few bottles of liquor.

The bottles contained several types of liquor. Among them were the ordinary milk wine, high-grade milk wine, white wine, and finally the beer. Zhao Hai didn’t bring out some fruit wine because it was obvious that they didn’t suit the palates of the Dwarves.

In fact, Zhao Hai already had prior knowledge about the Dwarves’ drinking customs. He understood that they really loved to drink, and that the liquor that they were drinking were quite special. Their liquor was a type made from potatoes that was farmed in the Buddha Empire. Although this potato looked much like sweet potatoes, and its liquor was also the same as the liquors back on Earth. Moreover, its flavor was very mellow, and it also had a distinct fermented fragrance. Most Dwarves are even disgusted by it. This liquor simply cannot be compared to Zhao Hai’s.

One can say that this potato liquor had a much worse flavor than fruit wine. But since Dwarves don’t like drinking fruit wine, they had no other choice but to consume this potato liquor.

Since Zhao Hai was already informed about these matter, therefore he didn’t bring some fruit wine out.

Billy and Juno looked at the four bottles on the table. These four bottles looked very common. Three of them had transparent contents while the last one had black liquid inside.

Zhao Hai opened the bottle containing ordinary milk wine and then looked at Billy and Juno, “This is the ordinary milk wine, I think the two of you had already tasted this. But this wine is divided into several types. What we are selling at large in the mainland had the lowest degree. But this bottle has a higher degree compared to the others.”

Each Dwarf table always had glasses for liquor in them, this was something that everybody knew. So Zhao Hai took two glasses from the table and then gave the two some of the ordinary milk wine.

Billy and Juno wasn’t polite, they immediately took the glass and drank the liquor. They had prior experience with milk wine, and they knew that it was fierce, therefore they only took a small sip.

After the two took a sip, they felt different. They had drunk the milk wines in the mainland. Those wines were very good to drink, but those cannot be compared to what Zhao Hai served them this time.

After they placed their cups down and nodded, Zhao Hai took the high grade milk wine and poured the two another two glasses of liquor.

Juno had already drank this high grade milk wine before, so his expression this time was quite mild. However, Billy hadn’t drank this before. Therefore, after he took a sip, his two eyes couldn’t help but light up, he felt that the flavor of this wine was very good.

Then Zhao Hai took the bottle of rice wine and then gave them a glass as he introduced it, “Taste this one, it’s something we made quite recently. It’s not milk wine nor fruit wine, but it’s made from bamboo rice.”

Juno and Billy stared at the bottle. Naturally, they knew about bamboo rice, but brewing alcohol from it? This was the first time that they had heard such a concept.

They curiously lifted the cup and drank from it. Although the degree of Zhao Hai’s rice wine wasn’t very high, it didn’t have the milky fragrance of milk wine. Instead, it had a purely wine flavor with a little sweet aftertaste. It was a gentle kind of drink.

After they tasted the liquor, the two’s eyes couldn’t help but light up. They didn’t expect that the liquor that was made from bamboo rice would be this good.

After seeing their reactions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. Then he poured them a glass of beer each. When Zhao Hai served them milk wine and rice wine, he only poured them a small amount, enough for a single sip. But this time, Zhao Hai poured the beer until the glass in half full. But even then, the foam at the top of the beer was already quite a lot.

Billy and Juno looked at Zhao Hai in confusion, Zhao Hai slightly knew what was on their minds as he said, “This liquor isn’t very strong, it’s quite mellow. However, I think you will find its flavor quite interesting. Please have a taste.”

Juno and Billy weren’t polite, they held their glasses and downed the liquor inside. When the beer entered their mouths, they first felt that it tasted very strange. But then, an indescribable mellow taste overwhelmed their taste buds. After the two drank the beer, they couldn’t help but snap their tongues.

While looking at the two, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This liquor is made from a rare type of plant grown in the continent. At this point, only our Buda Clan has been cultivating it. However, it’s production volume into beer is very great.”

Billy looked at the cup and nodded, “This final one is really good. It tastes quite nice. Do you have a lot of these?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “It’s current output is not very high. My highest output at this time would be milk wine. If you want the other ones, you may need to wait for some time.”

Billy nodded, “Then I want some milk wines, this ordinary ones since we Dwarves consume a lot of liquor. But you have to give me a very fair price.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, that’s not a problem. Large purchases always merit price deductions. I can sell them to the Dwarves at wholesale price.”

Billy gave a satisfied nod, “Good, good. Kid, when can you send the wine?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right now. How much do you want? I can deliver them right away.”

Billy stared at Zhao Hai and said, “How big is your Space Equipment?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “ Very big. Moreover, since I already planned to do business here, I also brought a large amount of milk wine along. I want to trade some of these wines into ironwares, then I’ll go transport them over to the Beastman Prairie.”

Billy nodded and said, “It looks like your relationship with the Beastmen is very good. In the past, our Dwarf race also had some dealings with the Beastmen. But after a few years, and the emergence of the Humans, our contact had been cut off. I didn’t expect that you would connect the two races with your business.”

Chapter 570: Prophecy

Zhao Hai didn’t know that the Dwarves had business dealings with the Beastmen before, so he smiled and said, “It’s nothing great, I just have good relationships with the Beastmen. When I went to the Prairie last time, the Beast King invited me over for a meal since he thinks highly of me. During the meal, I told him that I would be visiting here so he asked me to get some ironwares with me when I come back. Therefore, I’ll have to give some ironwares to the Beastmen when I return.”

Zhao Hai might be speaking calmly , but Juno and Billy heard things in a different tone. The two of them were aware of the relationship between the Humans and the Beastmen. There were a lot of Humans who can visit the Prairie to do business, however, it was rare for them to even get a glance of the Beast King.

Most importantly, from Zhao Hai’s words,  it seems like the Beast King still invited him over despite the recent war between the two races. This was enough to explain Zhao Hai’s standing inside the Beatman Prairie.

Juno looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, did you really share a meal with the Beast King?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I did, I cannot lie about this matter. After some time, Humans would be coming back to the Prairie to do business. They will surely know about this matter. The reason why I was able to cooperate for milk wine with the entire Beastman race was because of the Beast King’s help. Thanks to him sending his Beast King’s letters, the Beastmen believed me.”

Juno and BIlly became surprised as they asked, “Beast King’s letters?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, I think that’s what they called it. What’s wrong? I asked the Beast King for help and he didn’t say anything else.”

Juno and Billy stared at Zhao Hai for some time before Billy opened his mouth and said, “Kid, do you know what the Beast King’s letters represent?”

Zhao Hai stared, “Represent? Isn’t it just like notices sent by humans?”

Juno smiled bitterly and said, “You really know nothing, no wonder the Beastman Race helped you. The Beast King just couldn’t casually use his letters, they were only sent during important matters. Otherwise, the Beastmen wouldn’t hold his words in high regard.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I think it’s because of my milk wine business, it’s quite important to the beastmen. I even needed the help of the Hawk race in order to collect the massive amounts of milk wine. Otherwise, this cooperation would be impossible to progress quickly.”

Juno knit his brows and said, “That’s not right, why would the Beastmen believe you easily? The Beastmen had always been on guard against the Human race, why would they help you right now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Besides being a merchant, I’m also a Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bull tribe. Moreover, I also have the friendship flags of the Dog Race and the Black Bear Tribe. Therefore, they immediately trusted me.”

Juno didn’t understand this, so he was confused and asked, “Friendship flag? What is this friendship flag?”

Compared to Juno, Billy was more shocked than Zhao Hai, “Did you really obtain a Beastman Friendship flag? How is that possible?”

Juno became more puzzled, “What happened? What is a friendship flag?”

Billy forced a smile and said, “Beastman flags are divided into many types. People who do business with the Beastmen will receive that tribe’s War Flag, however, that flag has nothing of value. The Friendship Flag is different, as long as someone gets a Friendship Flag, that would mark him as a friend to the Beastmen, a genuine true friend. It represents being a friend worthy of them sacrificing their life for. Now you see how important Friendship Flags are? Also, Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bull Tribe? What’s this all about?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I’ve managed to help the Herculean Bulls in their time of extreme trouble. Also, the current Patriarch of the Herculean Bulls is my Beheading Blood Oath Brother. Therefore, I’ve become their tribe’s foreign Prince.”

Billy forced a smile and said, “Kid, you’re really lucky. No wonder the Beast King is willing to see you and even use his letters to help your business. Your milk wine business affects the entire Beastman Race, if they didn’t trust you then it might not have gone through.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ve always been fair in trading with the Beastmen. The price that I sell them grain is lower than all of the other Human Merchants. This also explains why my relationship with them is very good.”

Billy nodded, “Now I believe you. It seems like you’re genuine. I just hope that your business with our Dwarf Race gets to a point similar to your relationship with the Beastmen.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, it will.”

Billy smiled and said, “I hope. Right, how much milk wine did you bring? I want a lot.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You want a lot, but I have a lot. I’m afraid you won’t want all of them.”

Billy laughed and said, “Kid, you shouldn’t think too high of yourself. You’re underestimating the amount of liquor we Dwarves drink. If you want figures, then I’ll be taking 10 million jin.”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled, he didn’t think that the Dwarves would want this many, he was indeed overconfident. However, it doesn’t matter, he already had 1 million jin of milk wine inside the Space. He looked at Billy and laughed as well, “I didn’t think that you would want this many. I only have 1 million jin at this time. I can give the remaining amount in the future, what do you think?”

Billy laughed, “Alright, 1 million jin is enough. Right, you need to wait for a few days to get the things that you want. You stay here first, I also need to reminisce with old Juno. Tomorrow, I’ll take you to look around. If you need anything just send word and we’ll make sure to take care of it.”

Zhao Hai immediately became happy as he said, “That’s fantastic, I thank the Patriarch.”

Billy waved his hand and said, “No need to be polite. You go rest first while I have some people prepare some food. I’ll have someone invite you when the time comes.”

Then he turned his head outside and said, “Someone come here!” As his voice fell, a Dwarf came in from outside and bowed to Billy.

Billy nodded and said, “Lead Mister Zhao Hai and his wives to their resting area. Prepare a good room for them, he’s our friend, don’t neglect him.”

The Dwarf complied, then he led Zhao Hai and the others to exit. Seeing Zhao Hai leave, Billy turned to Juno and said, “Old fogy, you’ve really brought a decent person here this time. The Buddha Empire has been pressing our Dwarf Race in the recent years. If we can do business with Zhao Hai, then we might be able to be unafraid of the Buddha Empire.”

Juno smiled bitterly and said, “I actually didn’t expect him to hold such high status. It seems like the Buda Clan rising up in one year is not a fluke.”

Billy laughed and said, “I must say, you really outdid yourself this time. Right, why would you assist him? Does he have relationship with you? From what I knew, your Hurricane Family and the Buda Clan seems to have no past relations.”

Juno chuckled and replied, “Your right, our Hurricane Family and the Buda Clan doesn’t have any prior relationship. You might not have known, but Kristen had been the one doing business in the Rosen Empire. But this time, she was attacked by the people of the Radiant Church when she was heading back. If it wasn’t for Zhao Hai passing by, Kristen might have been ended.”

Billy stared for a moment before his eyes turned cold, “Radiant Church? THE Radiant Church? Why would they dare attack Kristen? No wonder I’ve been hearing about their churches in the Buddha Empire being picked off. Is it your doing?”

Juno coldly snorted and said, “Our Hurricane Family might have been good, but it doesn’t mean that we don’t have any temper. If we just let the Radiant Church go, then our family would be shamed in the continent. In the future, we wouldn’t be able to hold our heads high in the continent.”

Billy laughed at Juno’s reply, “Alright, that’s good. I have known you for so long, even I became angry with this. No wonder Kristen was not here to pick your goods, you actually sent her to Rosen Empire. That’s understandable, that place is not very far..”

Juno smiled bitterly and said, “That’s why I sent her there. Fortunately, she didn’t succumb to the enemies. If she didn’t, then I don’t know what I might do.”

Billy coldly snorted, “The Radiant Church is now quite weak, but they still dared to make this move. I should’ve given them a lesson. They came here in the past wanting to preach, fortunately, we drove them away.”

Juno said, “The Radiant Church came to preach here? Why didn’t I know that? There’s no news about this in the continent.”

Billy sneered, “They kidnapped a few Dwarves in the past and wanted them to come back here and preach in secret. But when they went to give respects in the Divine Palace, the hammer of the temple discovered them and they were all killed. It was later discovered that they were people of the Radiant Church.”

Juno replied, “There’s such a thing? I thought that the hammer in the Great Hall is just an ordinary one. Does the hammer really have special abilities?”

Billy looked at Juno and said, “I already told you before, that hammer is a Divine Artifact, but you didn’t believe me. Hmph”

After BIlly said this, a Dwarf’s voice was heard from the outside, “Patriarch, I have something to report.”

Billy said, “Come in.”

Then the Dwarf guide from before came in and stared at Juno. Billy frowned and said, “Ian, what’s wrong? Tell me. Don’t worry about Juno, he’s our friend, we don’t need to hide anything from our friend.”

Ian immediately said, “Yes, I’ve been unfair to Mister Juno.” Then he gave a bow to Juno who waved his hand. Then Ian turned his head to Billy and said, “Patriarch, I have something to report about Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai and Mister Juno went to the Divine Palace to pay respects, Mister Zhao Hai said that he had felt pressure from the Divine Artifact. He says that the Artifact is like a fearful existence surpassing 9th rank.”

Juno already heard this from Zhao Hai’s own mouth, so he wasn’t startled by the report. However, when Billy heard Ian’s report, his expression changed immediately, he stood up and looked deeply into Ian’s eyes and said, “Really? Did he say this?”

Ian nodded, “Yes, Patriarch. If you don’t believe me, then you can ask Mister Juno, he was also present at that time.”

Billy turned his head to Juno, Juno didn’t understand why Ian’s words made Billy tense. But he also knew that this wasn’t any small matter, therefore he immediately nodded and said, “Zhao Hai did say that, but I think that he was just cracking a joke. But from what I can see in your expression, it seems like Zhao Hai was telling the truth.”

Upon hearing the confirmation, Billy sat back on his chair as he bitterly smiled and said, “So the legend came true, I didn’t expect that this day would come.”

Juno was confused, he looked at Billy and said, “What’s wrong? Aren’t those just stories?”

Billy waved his hand, making Ian exit first, then he said, “It isn’t that simple, you might have seen Divine Artifacts before, but can you feel their might?”

Juno shook his head and said, “I couldn’t. I can’t even tell that it was a Divine Artifact. So what’s wrong with Zhao Hai knowing the might of Divine Artifacts?”

Billy nodded and said, “It’s because of this, theres a legend in our Dwarf Race related to that Divine Artifact. What you said in the past isn’t wrong, other than our Dwarf Race, no other race can feel that the hammer is a Divine Artifact. Actually, the legend of our Dwarf Race is really a prophecy. The prophecy says that when a person that is not a Dwarf discover the existence of the Divine Artifact, the the entire continent will suffer a catastrophe. However, the person who discovered the Artifact would be the one who would save the entire continent. He would be the saviour of all, the King of Kings.”

Juno stared at Billy, he really cannot convince himself to believe the old Dwarf’s words. Seeing Juno’s expression, Billy bitterly smiled and said, “Besides the Dwarves, no other race knows about this. The exact prophecy goes like this, ‘Recognition of the Divine Artifact, Wilting of the Tree of Life, Ruling the Five Forbidden Areas, Of which the Day of Catastrophe will arrive. The King of all, Hero of Salvation, he shall arrive. Aid the Hero, and the Continent will be saved.’ This meant that when someone other than our Race recognizes the Divine Artifact, and the Elves’ Tree of Life starts to wilt, and also when the Five Forbidden Areas gets conquered, a big disaster shall arrive to the Continent. When the King of all appears and saves the continent, our Dwarf Race would have to follow him and help him save all of the races in the continent.”

Juno was shocked at Billy’s revelation, he said, “Recognizing the Divine Artifact? Drying of the Tree of Life? Conquering the Five Forbidden Areas? Those are related to each other? So you’re saying that Zhao Hai is the person from the prophecy? You and the Elves have contact, what is the situation of their Tree of Life right now?”

Billy shook his head and said, “i don’t really know. But this prophecy came along with the Divine Artifact when it appeared in our race. Our Dwarf Race’s almanac held these words, I don’t think that it’s written by just anyone.”

Juno was speechless. He knew that the Dwarves’ history is much longer than his Hurricane Family. Although the Dwarves have moved several times, their solidarity didn’t disappear. Therefore, their race’s history shouldn’t have been falsely written.

Chapter 571: Whip

Although Humans are very powerful, much powerful than most races, they were also prone to infighting. Because of this, a lot of their historical records disappeared.

However, Dwarves were different, they were extremely united. Therefore, their historical records were much more complete compared to the Humans. So Juno didn’t even trust the historical records of the Humans.

Juno frowned and said, “But there seems to be no problem with the Elves’ Tree of Life. Also, there hasn’t been any signs of the Forbidden Areas being conquered. I don’t think the things in your book would happen.”

Billy bitterly smiled and said, “I also hope so. Otherwise, huge troubles would come.”

Juno sighed and didn’t say anything more. He also knew that there was nothing they could do right now. They can just have their ears open to news about the Elf’s Tree of Life.

Juno looked at Billy and said, “What are you planning to do with Zhao Hai in the next days?”

Billy smiled and said, “Didn’t I tell him that I’d take him around? Although he discovered the Divine Artifact, the prophecy hasn’t been confirmed yet. We naturally cannot just follow him.”

Juno looked at Billy and said, “If we confirm that the Elves’ Tree of Life has problems, would you really follow him?”

Billy’s eyes reflected his resolve as he nodded and said, “We shall. If we really confirm the prophecy, then my Dwarf Race shall follow him.”

Juno bitterly smiled as he shook his head. Although Billy was his old friend, he cannot understand why Billy would be so resolved to fulfill a prophecy. If the Dwarf Race really followed Zhao Hai, people might see them as a joke.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about these, he was currently with Laura and the others as they followed the guide to a mountain cave. When they arrived, the Dwarf stood on its entrance and said, “Mister, if you need anything, don’t hesitate to call me. You can also stroll around, it doesn’t matter.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he expressed his gratitude to the Dwarf. When Zhao Hai and the others entered the cave, they couldn’t help but stare. The interior was actually decorated very well.

The whole cave was covered in wooden boards whether it was the walls or the ground, you can’t even see any part of the mountain inside. The whole room was also designed to be suitable for Humans. Even the supplies inside were very carefully prepared for their daily needs.

Laura and the others looked around, they didn’t expect the place to be like this. The cave was separated into three rooms; a living room and two bedrooms. Because the place was all decorated with wood, it had the appearance of a historical dwelling.

Since the sun cannot penetrate inside, the rooms of the cave were all furnished with magic lamps. The lamps were quite good, their light was very gentle, it wasn’t too dazzling.

Laura and the others explored the area before they returned to the living room. Laura smiled and said, “This place is really good. Compared to the Beastmen, this accommodation is much better. It seems like the Dwarves are doing much better compared to the Beastmen.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Naturally. The Buddha Empire doesn’t dare suppress the Dwarves too much. For them, Dwarven products are too important. Moreover, since the Dwarves’ income is much higher than the Beastmen, they wouldn’t need to contact other Humans for a long time.”

Laura nodded and then said, “Brother Hai, I think that the Dwarves are easy to speak with, they even allowed us to stroll around. Do you think we can get to the Elves through the Dwarves?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and shook his head, “I don’t think so, I think we first need get the trust of the Dwarves. We need to give them the milk wine tomorrow. Also, I didn’t expect them to drink so much. The next batch of delivery is enough to supply the entire mainland.”

Laura smiled and said, “You need to get busy. Although they aren’t as many as the Beastmen, they still had about the same population as a Human empire. With their reputation of drinking, it would be hard to supply them with milk wine.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It looks like we needed to prepare more machines so that Grandpa Green can speed up the production of rice wine and beer. It also seems like the Dwarves preferred beer more.”

Laura was puzzled, “Really? Their tastes are surely strange. But it’s still a good idea to get more machines. Our current production in the winery is just not enough. We also have a shortage of manpower, but I think we should get more people when the lands are fully cultivated.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “I also need to have Lin send the second batch of slaves sooner. As long as we have more slaves, our shortage of manpower would be saved.”

Laura nodded, then she smiled and said, “Brother Hai, why don’t we just have the Undead help work in the wineries? Wouldn’t they count as manpower as well?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “We could, we have a lot of undead at hand. But if we want to stabilize the clan, depending on the undead is not a good idea. Also, we have new slaves in the Wasteland. I don’t think they would feel good if they see countless undead working.”

At this time, a knock could be heard outside. Meg immediately stood up and opened the door to see a Dwarf standing outside. The Dwarf looked at Meg and bowed, “Please, tell Mister Zhao Hai that the Patriarch is inviting him over for a meal.”

Zhao Hai went over and then smiled to the Dwarf and said, “Alright, then please.” Then he went out of the cave and followed the Dwarf.

The Dwarf lead them to another cave. The cave was very big, making Zhao Hai and the others stare blankly for a moment. Inside the cave were a lot of tables. Beside the tables where Billy and Juno were present, the other tables also had Dwarves in them.

Seeing Zhao Hai come, Billy immediately came to welcome him, “Mister Zhao Hai, please come over. I’ll also have to invite the madames to please sit on that table.” He pointed to the table next to them. The table was filled with Dwarf women, with empty seats among them. It seems like those spots were prepared for Laura and the others.

Laura and the others also knew about customs, so they didn’t decline and after thanking Billy, then went and sat down on their table. Then Zhao Hai went to sit with Billy.

After having settled down, Dwarf women immediately came to serve the food. Zhao Hai also paid attention to the female Dwarves. They weren’t tall, at about 1.4m in height. But their statures were very good, they looked quite skilled in the crafts, their skin might be brown, but they look dull of vitality. One could see that they were quite healthy.

Zhao Hai also inspected the dishes on the table. They’re very good, there were some meat as well as vegetables. There were even some dishes that Zhao Hai cannot recognize, it seems like these were unique to the Dwarves.

Then Billy poured Zhao Hai a glass of liquor. This liquor was actually Zhao Hai’s milk wine. Ever since milk wine appeared on the continent, the Dwarves had been buying them in bulk. Since they wanted to entertain someone like Zhao Hai, naturally they cannot serve him potato wine.

After pouring wine for himself, Billy raised his glass to Zhao Hai and said, “I’ll represent the Dwarf Race to welcome Mister Zhao Hai. I hope that our cooperation would become smooth in the future.”

Zhao Hai also raised his glass and smiled, “That is for certain.” Then they drank the wine. Billy immediately turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please have a taste of our dishes, I hope you take a liking to them.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite, he immediately took his knife and fork and tasted the dishes on the table. The dishes of the Dwarves tasted very good, Zhao Hai cannot help but nod and said, “This is very good. It’s different from Human dishes, but it’s very delicious.”

Billy laughed and said, “It’s good that you liked it. Mister Zhao Hai, I heard that when you visited the Divine Palace, you said that the Divine Artifact isn’t ordinary. I want to ask if you can really feel it?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that Billy would ask him about this. However, he also knew that it wasn’t impossible to hide this matter. It was because Juno as well as the Dwarf guide had already heard him saying this. Therefore, he didn’t conceal the truth, he nodded and said, “Of course, there’s no problem.”

Then Zhao Hai wrinkled his brows and said, “How should I describe it? When I first saw the hammer I also thought that it was ordinary. However, immediately after that, I felt a huge pressure coming from it. I thought that the pressure was coming from the Great Hall, however, it actually came from the hammer. Moreover, I felt that it seems to be like an expert, even more formidable than 9th rank experts.”

After that, Zhao Hai put out his hand and unraveled Mu’er who was on his waist and showed it to Billy, “This whip came from my Brother, the Herculean Bull Patriarch, gave to me. It’s called the Beast King’s whip, it’s a very powerful weapon. Without even using Battle Qi or Magic, it can contend against 9th rank experts. But I can feel that the hammer at your Great Hall is much more formidable than this whip.

Billy stared at the the whip on Zhao Hai’s hand. He received the whip and took a closer look at it. He had never seen this whip before, but he can feel a pressure coming from it. It might not be as strong as the hammer, but Billy can feel that it was there.

Not only Billy, but Juno was also inspecting the whip. Like Billy, Juno also felt the pressure from the whip. Juno felt like he wasn’t looking at a whip, but instead a powerful living creature that was a 9th rank expert.

Chapter 572: Asking for Help

For a weapon to feel like this made Juno startled. He had not come across such a matter.

But when Billy looked at the whip, his two eyes shined, after some time, he gave the whip back to Zhao Hai and then said, “I’ll be impolite and ask Mister, does this whip have an Artifact Spirit?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect Billy to know about the existence of Artifact Spirits. But since he knew that there was no point in hiding anything from Billy, he nodded and said, “Yes.”

Billy was moved, he stood up and pulled Zhao Hai outwards. Before he walked out, he instructed the Dwarves, “Bring the food to my room, I have a matter to discuss with Mister Zhao Hai. Old friend, you go with us as well.”

Juno naturally followed Billy and Zhao Hai. He also wanted to know what this was about. Laura and the others were also puzzled as they looked at the three, but they didn’t go and follow.

Before long, the three people arrived at Billy’s room. This was Billy’s personal room, not a place for him to work in. The room was a standard room for Dwarves. It wasn’t very big, it had a living room, a bedroom, and a small comfort room, it seems like it was used for washing.

After the three had sat on the living room, Billy immediately looked at Zhao Hai and said, “The Artifact Spirit of the whip, can it materialize?”

Zhao Hai gawked, Mu’er can indeed materialize, but he hasn’t shown Mu’er’s form to an outsider before. But Billy was knowledgeable, knowing not only about Artifact Spirits but also materialization.

After weighing the pros and cons, Zhao Hai decided to show it to Billy. Billy immediately pulled him over to his room as soon as he found out about the Artifact spirit, so naturally he didn’t want other to know about it. Zhao Hai trusted Juno as well, Juno wasn’t someone who would reveal people’s secrets.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes.”

Billy’s expression turned even more serious, his beard seemed to shake. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, can I ask you to let me see the Artifact Spirit?” His voice seem to be out of tune.

Zhao Hai didn’t understand why Billy was so moved. But he knew that Billy treated this matter seriously, therefore he nodded and said, “Alright.” Then Zhao Hai held the whip and said, “Mu’er come out.”

Just after Zhao Hai’s voice fell, Mu’er’s figure slowly appeared on top of the whip. As usual, Mu’er had the appearance of a little boy. After he materialized, Mu’er immediately bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, you called me.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This is the Dwarf Race’s Patriarch Billy and this is Hurricane Family’s Patriarch Juno, go give them respects.”

Mu’er turned to look at Billy and Juno and then bowed slightly and said, “Mu’er has seen the two Patriarchs.”

Billy and Juno looked at Mu’er, Juno hasn’t seen this matter before, but Billy was startled, he didn’t expect Mu’er to be intelligent. It can actually talk like a Human with them, this was out of his imagination.

In the Dwarf records regarding Artifact Spirits, it said that Artifact Spirits had gained Spiritual Wisdom. It can listen to their master’s words, but it was impossible for them to be intelligent. Therefore, the appearance of Mu’er made Billy, who was quite knowledgeable in this area, quite startled.

After some time, Billy recovered, however his shocked face was till facing Mu’er. His mouth opened and closed repeatedly, as if he didn’t know what to say.

At the same time, Juno was also shocked at Mu’er, he didn’t think that a whip can actually speak with them. He hadn’t heard of such a matter.

Zhao Hai looked at Billy and smiled faintly, “Patriarch Billy, you hadn’t said anything. Is something wrong?”

At this time, a knock was heard from outside. Zhao Hai immediately retrieved Mu’er as Billy and Juno sobered up. Billy then said, “Come in.”

Then Dwarves came in and delivered some tableware and dishes to Zhao Hai and the others before they bowed and left.

After the Dwarves left, Billy had completely recovered his composure. When the three had sat down, Billy immediately drank some liquor before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Is the Artifact Spirit already present when you acquired the whip?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It was. But he cannot do materialization at that time, and he wasn’t intelligent as well. Later on, I used a secret method to make him materialize and become intelligent.”

When Billy heard Zhao Hai, he lost grip of his cup as it fell down to the ground. He looked straight into Zhao Hai’s eyes with unbelieving expression as he said, “You, you, you said that you used a secret method to make the Artifact Spirit materialize?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It’s true. Mu’er wasn’t like this at first. But after I used my secret method, he was able to materialize and become what he is right now.”

Billy stood up, then he walked back and forth. After two laps, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Can I ask Mister for a favor?”

Zhao Hai stared, he was puzzled as he asked, “Patriarch, please say it.”

Billy sat down and looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister has also seen my race’s Divine Artifact. I suspect that it also has an Artifact Spirit inside. Although the Artifact can also communicate with us right now, it was only limited to simple reactions. I want to ask mister to use his secret method and make our Divine Artifact just like your whip. Can you do this?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect Bill to request this of him. He thought for a moment and then said, “I’m still not sure if I can succeed, I can only try. If I become unsuccessful, I hope Patriarch doesn’t blame me.”

Billy became glad as he replied, “That’s not strange, not strange at all, so there’s no reason to blame you. Mister can rest assure. When can mister do it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Tonight, bring the Divine Artifact to my dwelling and make sure nobody disturbs me. If I succeed tomorrow, then it’s good. If I dont, no matter how much time I’m given, I’m unlikely to succeed.”

Billy was elated, “Good, Mister can rest assured, I’ll have everything prepared immediately.” Then he didn’t say anything else as he went outside.

Seeing the excited Billy, Juno turned to Zhao Hai and smiled, “Little Hai, you’re really good, helping the Dwarves so much. But what is this Artifact Spirit?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This Artifact Spirit is actually a unique kind of spirit. It’s just like Lich that has been summoned by a Dark Mage. Because it has some kind of soul, it held resentment and reason. Artifact Spirits manifest in weapons, after a very long time, that weapon would slowly form its own consciousness which would in turn become a Spirit Body. However, this Spirit Body wouldn’t be able to separate itself from the weapon, like how a person’s soul cannot leave its body. I have a method to make this Spirit Body more powerful, this is how Mu’er appeared.”

Juno nodded, Zhao Hai explained it to him in terms that he could understand, but he still couldn’t feel how formidable these Artifact Spirits were. Therefore, the two just stayed and drank as they chatted along.

Meanwhile, Billy has actually been very busy. He used haste in inviting the elders of the Dwarf Race, then he expressed Mu’er’s existence to them and telling them about his plan.

Like Billy, the elders were moved, the Divine Artifact was very important to the Dwarves. If the Divine Artifact can manifest its Artifact Spirit, then the Dwarves would benefit a lot from it.

The elders immediately agreed to Billy’s plan. They believed that Billy wouldn’t deceive them with regards of this matter. Seeing the elders simultaneously agreeing, Billy immediately had them group up inside the Great Hall. He and the elders bathed themselves and changed their clothes as they prepared to hand their Divine Artifact over to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about any of these, after eating his meal with Juno, he immediately returned to his room. At this time, Laura and the others were already back, when they saw Zhao Hai, they immediately greeted them as Laura asked, “Brother Hai, what happened? What did the Dwarf Patriarch call you for? He looked very worried.”

Zhao Hai nodded and smiled, “It’s about the hammer in their Divine Palace, that this is the Divine Artifact of the Dwarves. The hammer also had its own Artifact Spirit, just like Mu’er, however, the spirit is very weak. The Dwarves wanted me to have their Divine Artifact be improved to the level of Mu’er. I agreed to try.”

Laura nodded and said, “So it’s that. So, are you confident?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’m really not. But I think that the Space would be able to improve the spirit. If we help the Dwarves, then they would surely think of us as true friends. When the time comes where we need to get in contact with the Elves, then they might lend us a helping hand.”

Megan smiled and said, “That’s great. I really wanted to go and visit the Elves. I heard that all of them were extraordinarily attractive, and they were born artists. I wanted to see what they are like.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, we will have the opportunity to do so. I think that the Dwarves are getting prepared right now. I told them to not disturb me this evening, I can’t just let them feel like I’ve done it quite easily.”

Lizzy frowned, “But Big Brother Hai, does Mister Juno know?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “He knows, but it’s fine. With his relationship with the Dwarves, I don’t think that he would tell anyone. If he reveals Mu’er as well as the Dwarves’ Divine Artifact, then he would be offending the entire Dwarf Race, he wouldn’t want to do that. Also, even if other people knew about Mu’er, they still can’t do anything about it, given the Buda Clan’s present strength.”

Laura nodded, “Brother Hai is right. It’s much more important to help the Dwarves and make friends with them. I support Brother Hai’s decision.”

Lizzy also nodded. Just like Zhao Hai said, even if the other people knew about Mu’er, how many of them would want to offend the Buda Clan? With the Buda Clan’s present strength, they aren’t afraid of anyone.

Chapter 573: Divine Realm?

The skies outside slowly became dark. While the other Dwarves were heading home, they were still clueless about what Billy was planning to do. Billy didn’t want this matter to be known to a lot of people, therefore, he didn’t announce it.

Zhao Hai didn’t walk around, he just stayed in his room while waiting for Billy to arrive. When the skies turned completely black, Billy and the other elders arrived at Zhao Hai’s room.

After Zhao Hai asked them to come inside, Billy carefully and with full respect, lowered the hammer towards the table. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is our race’s Divine Artifact, we must ask for your help.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll do my best. Please help me maintain the conditions outside. Laura, you and the others please assist me.”

Laura and the others complied and cleaned the table, leaving a big area for the hammer. Upon seeing this arrangement, Billy’s group immediately said their goodbyes and then went outside. The group didn’t move far away, they just stood at the distance, waiting for Zhao Hai. Naturally, they were also prepared to guard Zhao Hai’s dwelling this night.

After Billy’s group left, Zhao Hai immediately held the hammer as he flashed to the Space with Laura and the others. Upon entering the Space, a prompt was then heard, “Item with weak Spirit detected, strengthening the Item’s Spirit.” Then Zhao Hai saw the hammer flash with red light as a figure slowly appeared in front of him.

Zhao Hai gawked, he discovered that the tone of the Space has changed compared to the last time when it upgraded Mu’er. But after he thought about it, the Space had already been upgraded many times, and it also had acquired new abilities and had become more magical, therefore, it was natural for it to change its tone.

The Space was acting like program before, but now it’s speech had gotten much smoother. This was good for Zhao Hai, now he was really anticipating how the Space would evolve in the future.

At this time, the figure had almost completed its appearance, which also stemmed Zhao Hai’s anticipation. It seems like the hammer’s Artifact Spirit was a Dwarf.

The Dwarf looked at Zhao Hai and then said, “Who are you? You’re not a Dwarf, why can you awaken me?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he understood that this Artifact Spirit was more advanced than Mu’er, it might also know something. So Zhao Hai immediately said, “Hello, I am a friend to the Dwarves. I have a method to make you materialize, therefore they asked me to help you do it.”

The Artifact Spirit nodded. And at this time, a prompt was heard from the Space, “Spirit is not willing to submit to the Host, the Space will subdue it!” And as the prompt ended, a bunch of white light suddenly wrapped the Dwarf Artifact Spirit. The Spirit roared for a moment before it turned silent. After the white light vanished, the Dwarf was seen again, respectfully standing in front of Zhao Hai this time.

Zhao Hai was shocked when the heard the Space’s prompt. He wasn’t expecting the Space to help him subdue the Artifact Spirit. He stood there in a daze, waiting for the Space to finish.

Zhao Hai looked at the respectful Artifact Spirit in front of him and couldn’t help but smile bitterly. If the Dwarves were to know that he had subdued their Divine Artifact’s Spirit, won’t they get offended?

While he was bitterly smiling, Zhao Hai looked at the Artifact Spirit and said, “What is your name? Do you remember anything?”

The Artifact Spirit respectfully answered Zhao Hai, “Yes, my name is Iron Hammer. My master is the Artisan God Hom. I was sent by master to the lower realm in order to protect the Dwarves.”

Zhao Hai stared, he was confused, so he looked at Iron Hammer and said, “Lower Realm? What’s that?”

Iron Hammer replied, “Lower Realm refers to the world where beings like humans lived in, the Ark Continent. The Ark Continent is only a plane, a single plane among many in this universe. I came from a place called the Divine Realm. Ten thousand years ago, my master was the most powerful warrior and skilled artisan in the Dwarf Race. When he broke through and reached godhood, he went to the Divine Realm. But in order for the Dwarves to live well, he sent me back and act as the race’s Divine Artifact and protect the Dwarves.”

Zhao Hai was shocked, he didn’t think that this universe would have a Divine Realm, moreover, there were actually Gods.

After some time, Zhao Hai looked at Iron Hammer and then said, “Is there really a Divine Realm? Does that Realm have many Gods?”

Iron Hammer nodded and then continued, “The current elemental density in the continent is very low. But tens of thousands of years ago, it’s density was very high. At that time, people were strong, and there were a lot of 9th rank experts. After passing 9th rank, one would reach godhood. As long as one becomes a God, one could break through the space and reach the Divine Realm, where the elemental density is much higher than here. There are also natives in the Divine Realm. They were immediately 5th rank when they are born. When they reach adulthood, they would reach the power of a 9th rank expert. With enough training, it wouldn’t be difficult for them to become Gods or even stronger.”

Zhao Hai listened to Iron Hammer’s words, he really wasn’t expecting any of these. Then Iron Hammer spoke again, “In the beginning, these natives looked down on those who came from the Ark Continent, causing both sides to repeatedly wage war with each other. In the end, the experts from the Ark Continent went into an alliance, slowly solidifying their footing in the Divine Realm. Later on, they became connected to the natives through inter-marriages, and they fully integrated with each other. However, a time came when Human Gods and the Gods of other races came into conflict. Humans prepared to have a God of their own to descend and kill the descendants of the other races. But since it was difficult for a God to descend to lower realms, they used Divine Power in order to break the Space, sending that God to the continent. However, my Master and the others found out about the plan of the Humans. But since they don’t have a means to make a God descend, they opted to send weapons capable of dealing with that God instead. Therefore, me, along with the Beast God’s Spear, and the Spirit God’s Bow, were sent to the Dwarves, Beastmen, and Elves respectively, making the three races unite together in order to deal with the Human god. With the three of us, the races fought with that God, injuring him in the process, making him return to the Divine Realm. But since the three of us were heavily damaged, we cannot go back. So we returned to our respective races and became their Divine Protectors.”

Zhao Hai and the others were quite startled by all of these. They didn’t expect a conflict of this scale to have happened in the continent tens of thousands of years ago.

Zhao Hai immediately said, “How about the five Forbidden Lands and the Demon Realm? Do you know anything about those?”

Iron Hammer nodded and said, “I know. The Five Forbidden Lands were originally major dwelling places of the races in the continent, they were also protecting a magical formation. When the God descended to the lower realm and waged war with the races, these major cities were destroyed. But along with their destruction, the formation was also destroyed, connecting the Ark Continent with the Demon Realm. The Demon Realm is another place, it’s living conditions were very bad. When the people from the Demon Realm discovered that the conditions in the Ark Continent were very good, their greed immediately seeped in. They sent an army to the Ark Continent to invade it, but was also repelled by the joint alliance of all the races. When the Demons retreated, the cracks on those major cities were still left behind, making the barrier on those places quite thin. This would explain the times where some creatures from the Demon realm would emerge from those places, making it their territory.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “If the barrier between the Demon Realm and the Ark Continent is easily passed through, they why is the barrier to the Divine Realm so difficult to break? Are the people in the Divine Realm not strong enough?”

Iron Hammer shook his head and said, “Not necessarily. Each place has its own unique rules. The Ark Continent is also the same, here, the rules state that God ranked experts cannot stay for a long time. It would be impossible for Gods to stay here for more than six months. This rule made it easy for people to leave the continent and head to the Divine Realm compared to going back. Because of this, not only would it be difficult for person to descend from the Divine Realm, it would also be difficult for them to stay. But since the Demon Realm is on the same level as the Ark Continent, the barrier between the two of them is thinner. However, God ranked experts of the Demon Realm were also similarly restricted by the Ark Continent’s rules. Therefore, only experts below God-ranked were able to come and invade the continent in the previous war.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So as you say, the Demon Realm is not like the Divine Realm but the same as the Ark Continent? Also, if the Ark continent doesn’t allow God-level experts to stay, why are you still here?”

Iron Hammer replied, “We’re only weapons, not experts. People would need to use us first in order to display our power. The stronger the person, the stronger the power we can display. During the war, 9th rank experts needed to join up in order to use me to go against the God-ranked invader.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he now had more understanding about this matter. Iron Hammer was actually from the Divine Realm. Zhao Hai looked at Iron Hammer and said, “Do you have any information about the Divine Realm that you can tell me?”

Iron Hammer nodded and said, “Young Master, the Divine Realm is divided into 13 regions, the largest of which is the central continent. Then remaining 12 continents were placed around the central continent and they were named; Aries, Taurus, Gemini, Cancer, Leo, Virgo, Libra, Scorpio, Capricorn, Aquarius, and Pisces Continents. The way that people from the Divine Realm cultivate is much different that the Ark Continent. The main practice in here is related or offshoots of Magic and Battle Qi. But in the Divine Realm, the people practice Origin Force, which is much more formidable compared to Magic and Battle Qi. Moreover, the weapons that were used in the Divine Realm all had their own Artifact Spirits, one could also remotely control them, increasing their might.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but his mood was heavy. It seems like there are more formidable people in the Divine Realm compared to the Ark Continent. If those people from the Divine Realm were to invade, what would he do?

Most importantly, Zhao Hai was worried. If he goes to the Divine Realm in the future, will the Space still be able to protect him?

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai felt that he needed to increase his strength more. He immediately looked at Iron Hammer and said, “Iron Hammer, when you’ve been on the continent, did you come upon any good things?”

Iron Hammer nodded and said, “I have. The last battle with that God-ranked expert was actually here, in Dwarf Mountain. There is a place deep in the mountains where the God was injured and had his blood spill out. Blood of a God-ranked being is very precious, its full of energy. If ordinary people touch it, they would explode. Therefore, that place has become a forbidden area for the Dwarves.”

Zhao Hai’s two eyes lit up. If people explode when interacting with that energy, then what would the Space’s reaction be?

The Space needed a lot of things to be upgraded. Zhao Hai still wasn’t sure if a God’s blood would be able to level up the Space. But even if it can’t, it would surely bring a lot of benefits to its environment.

Moreover, after Zhao Hai listened to Iron Hammer’s testimony, he suddenly remembered the time when Zhao Wen first entered the Space. Zhao Wen told him that she became a 9th rank expert shortly after drinking some kind of red liquid. Could the liquid that Zhao Wen had drank be the blood of a God-ranked expert?

However, Zhao Hai changed his mind. If Zhao Wen did drink the blood of a God-ranked expert, then she should have already exploded. People weren’t able to withstand that kind of energy, much less a Blood Devouring Mosquito.

But Zhao Hai also thought of another possibility. It might have been a God-ranked expert’s blood, but it might be a diluted version of it. This would explain how Zhao Wen was able to withstand such energy.

The more he thought about it, the more Zhao Hai was convinced of his theory. If this was indeed true, then the more he was eager to get it. Perhaps they can find a way to make 9th rank experts with this method.

After thinking about these, Zhao Hai turned to Iron Hammer and said, “Iron Hammer, you stay here and protect the Dwarves. They still don’t know that you have submitted to me. Right, as far as the matter with the Divine Realm is concerned, do refrain from telling the Dwarves about it for now, understand?”

Chapter 574: Eternal Friend

Iron Hammer nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master, I understand.”

Zhao Hai also nodded and said, “Protect the Dwarves properly, don’t let any trouble come to them, I don’t want to worry. Just tell them that the Gods had sent you as a weapon to protect the Dwarf Race, no need to tell anything about the Gods, understood?”

Iron Hammer nodded, “Young Master can rest assured, this one would surely not tell anyone.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod and then released Mu’er and told him, “That’s great, I’ll be resting now. Mu’er, stay with Iron Hammer for a while, tell him about the Space.”

Mu’er complied, then Zhao Hai and the others returned to the Space to rest. Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid that Iron Hammer would reveal the Space. Iron Hammer was already subdued by the Space, so it was impossible for him to betray it.

The night passed by silently as Zhao Hai and the others took a good rest inside the Space. On the other hand, Billy and the others were wide awake, all of them were anxiously guarding Zhao Hai’s cave, not allowing anyone to approach it at this time. They were afraid that an accident might happen. This matter was truly very important to their race.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others got up and washed themselves before they reappeared inside the cave. After taking care of the layout of the room, Zhao Hai opened his door and allowed Billy and the others to come in. Upon entering the cave, the Dwarves were nervously looking at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he held Iron Hammer in both of his hand and said. “Good fortune truly follows the Dwarf Race. I ask Patriarch Billy to take a look.”

Billy’s hands were shaking as he received Iron Hammer. Then he bowed to Zhao Hai, “Mister’s great kindness would surely go unforgotten by our Dwarf Race. I ask mister to take a rest first, we’ll take care of the Artifact ourselves.” Zhao Hai nodded. Then Billy and the others left the room.

With Iron Hammer in his arms, Billy, along with the other elders, returned to the Divine Palace. Right after placing Iron Hammer on its place and asking all unrelated people to go out, Billy went to Iron Hammer and respectfully said, “I ask Sir Iron Hammer to come out!”

After his voice fell, Iron Hammer slowly appeared in front of the Dwarves. “Dwarf Patriarch, I’ve always been conscious all these years, so I know about all the Dwarf’s matters. However, I wasn’t able to materialize until now. Let me tell you about my origin. I am the Artisan God’s weapon, tens of thousands of years ago, when he was about to ascend, he was worried about the well-being of the race, so he decided to leave me behind to protect it. But I was injured in a war, so I can only recuperate in my hammer form, cannot come out. I’m fortunate that someone with skill managed to assist me. But the thing that I can still do is protect the Dwarves, I can’t do anything else for you.”

The reason why Iron Hammer dared say this was because in the war tens of thousands of years ago with the descended God, the historical records of various nations have vanished. This was the reason why the Dwarves didn’t have any record of Iron Hammer’s appearance in their race. The only thing that they know was that Iron Hammer was their Divine Protector. Therefore, Iron Hammer told this fact to Billy which would also make the latter not ask about any matters in the Divine Realm.

He can tell Billy that he came from the Divine Realm, but he didn’t want to tell them about the Divine Realm. At the same time, Billy and the others didn’t dare to ask anymore. Iron Hammer is their Divine Artifact, so they treated Iron Hammer with the respect that they would give their God. They wouldn’t dare to scrutinize the words of their Divine Protector.

Billy and the others respectfully nodded. Then Iron Hammer said, “I’ve already talked about this next matter with Mister Zhao Hai. He helped me in a big way this time, so I decided to give him a gift. The things in the Forbidden Land would be given to Mister Zhao Hai.”

Billy stared, naturally he knew about the Forbidden Land in Iron Mountain. That place was a red pool which stenched of blood. As long as a person gets in contact with that liquid, they would explode and perish. Therefore, it was named Forbidden Land. How could the Artifact Spirit give such a place to Zhao Hai?

Iron Hammer looked at Billy and said, “That thing is useless to the Dwarves. But Mister Zhao Hai has uses for it, so I decided to just give it to him. Mister Zhao Hai also needed some special Magic beasts and Plants, we must make sure that our Dwarf Race helps him in this matter in the future. There’s no other way for us to repay his benevolence.”

After Iron Hammer told them about these, he looked at Billy and said, “Alright, you still have a lot of things to do as a Patriarch. As long as the Dwarves don’t experience a huge difficulty, I won’t be coming out. You can now retreat.” Then his body slowly vanished into the small hammer.

Billy and the others were fully obedient towards Iron Hammer, so they also turned around to leave. Although they were extremely happy, they also knew that this matter needed to be known to as few people as possible. If a lot of people knew about Iron Hammer, then it wouldn’t be good for the Dwarf Race.

Billy and the others returned to their conference room to work. Billy strictly instructed the other elders that they absolutely should not tell this matter to others.

After discussing this, Billy sat there and looked at the elders and said, “For the Divine Artifact to materialize is all thanks to Mister Zhao Hai. We should also keep this matter from the others, otherwise, we would be doing Mister Zhao Hai a disservice. Moreover, I’ll be sending word later telling everyone that Mister Zhao Hai is our race’s genuine friend. Everyone should respect him, does everyone have any ideas?”

The other elders shook his head, they don’t have any other opinion. Zhao Hai has truly helped them out. They already see Zhao Hai as a true friend.

Seeing that nobody disagreed, Billy continued, “Good, I’ll spread the word later on. Right, have people collect some special Magic beasts and Plants as well. Since Mister needs these things, then we should do our best to help him out.”

The other elders agreed, then they turned around to leave. Billy also changed his clothes as he walked to Zhao Hai’s room. When he was outside Zhao Hai’s cave, Billy felt hesitant, he thought that Zhao Hai was very exhausted of what just happened, so it was possible that he was resting at this time. He didn’t know if disturbing Zhao Hai would be appropriate this time.

At this moment, Zhao Hai opened the room and walked out, he looked at Billy and said, “Patriarch Billy, come in.”

Billy gave Zhao Hai a small nod before entering Zhao Hai’s room. Upon entering, Billy was about to give Zhao Hai a bow before Zhao Hai stopped him hastily and said, “Patriarch Billy is too polite, there’s no need to do so.”

Billy looked grateful at Zhao Hai and said, “We’re very lucky this time due to Mister’s help. Otherwise, Sir Artifact Spirit wouldn’t be able to materialize. Our Dwarf Race would be forever grateful to mister.”

After Zhao Hai invited Billy to sit down, he smiled and said, “Patriarch is too serious, I just happen to have this ability, so since I was able to help, there’s no reason to not do so. Patriarch doesn’t need to take it seriously, I also see the Dwarves as my friends. Helping a friend is no big deal.”

Billy looked at Zhao Hai in gratitude as he said, “Mister is truly a friend. Rest assured, Mister’s Buda Clan would be our Dwarf Race’s Eternal Friends. Right, I’ll have to invite Mister to eat. After the meal, I’ll be taking mister to our Dwarves’ Forbidden Land. Sir Artifact Spirit told us to give the things in the Forbidden Land to mister.”

Zhao Hai nodded and in embarrassment he said, “I’m ashamed to be in front of Patriarch. My family’s refining master is truly curious about these things. Since I have Space equipments, I can handle those things. Sir Artifact Spirit also told me that those things are useless to the Dwarves, so I thickened my face to ask for them.”

Billy smiled and said, “Mister doesn’t need to say anything more. The Blood Pond in the Forbidden Land is truly poisonous. As long as one comes in contact with it, their body would surely explode. Keeping that thing here is only a disaster waiting to happen. For mister to take them away is akin to helping us erase an evil, this is enough to make us happy. As the matter stands, it’s us who have been unfair to mister. If Mister has any need for our assistance in the future, then please don’t hesitate to send word.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then I would take Patriarch’s words at heart, this Zhao Hai’s gratefulness is endless.”

Billy laughed and then said, “Mister should not be polite. Mister, let’s walk and have a meal. After that, we’ll go to the Blood Pond. I also had the others collect Magic Beasts and Plants for mister. I believe that they could deliver those to mister soon. This is a sign of our gratitude.”

Zhao Hai also knew that if he declines or offer something in compensation, he would seem ingenuine and in turn making Billy unhappy. This was one of the differences between Humans and Dwarves. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t decline, he just smiled and said, “Then I have to thank the Patriarch.”

Seeing Zhao Hai receive their gifts, Billy immediately became happy and then said, “Mister is too polite, right, let’s get going and have a meal.” Then he pulled Zhao Hai towards the Dining Hall.

Laura and the others also followed them out. At the same time, they also met Juno along the way. Billy invited Juno for a meal as well. Although Zhao Hai was his new friend, his many years of friendship with Juno isn’t something to be forgotten.

Seeing Billy’s expression, Juno knew that yesterday’s matter had gone very smoothly. Juno couldn’t help but be surprised at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai seemed to be much more mysterious in his mind. At the same time, Juno also resolved himself to establish a relationship with Zhao Hai. Not only because of him saving Kristen, but also because of Zhao Hai’s abilities.

The Hurricane Family was strong by themselves, but the reason why they had their influence was because of their relationship with others. They didn’t offend anyone, whether it be the Buddha Empire or the other Nobles, all of them had good relationships with the family. This was the reason why the Hurricane Family can settle down and live with their current lifestyle.

And since Zhao Hai was the Patriarch of the emerging Buda Clan, his power and influence in the continent had become very powerful. This kind of person wasn’t someone that Juno doesn’t want to neglect.

Chapter 575: Forbidden Land

After the group arrived at the Dining Hall, Zhao Hai discovered that although there were still people in the hall, it wasn’t as many as yesterday. Moreover, the hall before had young Dwarves in it, but this time, only old ones were present.

After Billy introduced them, Zhao Hai understood that they were the elders of the race. Zhao Hai didn’t dare neglect their presence, so he immediately gave them a salute.

The other elders were also very polite to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai, Billy, and the others were sitting on one table. On the other hand, Laura and the others sat on the another table along with similar aged Dwarves.

This Dwarf custom of also inviting the companions of a guests to a dinner was something that Zhao Hai liked very much.

While the group sat down and ate, the elders kept urging Zhao Hai to drink. However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to, drinking during the day was something that he doesn’t do. But since he was been given hospitality, he couldn’t help but drink a few glasses.

Juno has been watching Zhao Hai getting along with the Dwarf elders. Although Zhao Hai had given the Dwarves a huge favor, there was no change in Zhao Hai’s temperament. He was still very respectful to the elders, just like how he acted before. It was as if nothing happened.

This made Juno settle on Zhao Hai. There were very few people on the continent that were like Zhao Hai. One must know that the Dwarves were viewed by other Humans as a different type of people. Because of this, every time a Human interacts with a Dwarf, they would always fish for huge benefits from them. At the same time, Humans were also looking down on the Dwarves. [1] Therefore, general Humans, even if they benefited from the Dwarves, wouldn’t act the same as what Zhao Hai was doing.

After eating their meal, Zhao Hai didn’t go to the Forbidden Lands along with Billy immediately. He first returned to his room and drank one cup of Spatial Water to sober himself up. Only after that did he come out of his room.

Billy and Juno were currently sitting inside Billy’s cave. When a Dwarf led Zhao Hai to the cave, the two who were chatting immediately stood up.

Zhao Hai quickly asked the two to sit down, then he bitterly smiled and said, “I’ll be frank to you two, my alcohol capacity is too limited. Since I drank some glasses, I needed to return to my room to drink something in order to sober up.

Drinks for sobering up was quite common in the continent, especially to the Nobles. Offering and receiving hospitality in the Human lands also involved some sort of drinking. Since being drunk is uncomfortable, the people in the continent asked some potion masters to make them something that can sober them up.

Billy didn’t care about it, he just smiled faintly and said, “it’s no big deal. We Dwarves are already used to it. Haha. Mister, let’s head to the Forbidden Land.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright.”

Billy nodded, and then he stood up, Juno stood up as well. It seems like he intended to come along with Zhao Hai. Seeing Billy’s expression, it seems like there was no problem. This was understandable, after all, Juno was an extremely trustworthy person, and he already knew quite a bit about this matter. Even if one doesn’t tell him anything, he would still know of it sooner or later. As the matter stands, it’s much better to just tell Juno everything in order to not lose his trust.

Billy led Zhao Hai and the others out of the cave and then walked towards another underground river channel. They sat on a boat and then proceeded to travel along the Iron Mountains.

The Dwarves’ Iron Mountains was quite big, but the Dwarves were smart. As soon as they discovered this underground river system, the immediately utilized it to be their transportation channel. When they came to know that this underground system spanned the entirety of the mountains, it became an important line for the entire Dwarf race, which made their travel much more convenient.

The speed of their boat was very fast. After two hours, the group disembarked on a pier. This pier was quite empty and wasn’t as busy as the others. There weren’t any other ships present here at all. After Billy got of the boat, he had a Dwarf wait for them here and went towards the area where the pier was connected to.

The mountain that the pier was located in was just like any other Dwarf Mountain. It seems like this was where the Forbidden Land was, otherwise, there wouldn’t be much absence of Dwarves here.

Zhao Hai was now very amazed at these Dwarves. The map of the Dwarf Mountains were now almost mapped out in the Space. Seeing the display made Zhao Hai feel how extraordinary this race was.

With how long the Dwarves have lived in these mountains, the mountains seemed to become their own underground world. The underground water system looks like an enormous spider web, connecting Dwarves from various mountains together. How much work was needed to do this? Yet the Dwarves were able to accomplish this task, it was unfathomable.

The people came out of the mountain and was placed outside a small canyon outside the mountain. The Dwarves has built some fences made of wood around this canyon. It seems like they didn’t want people to go and enter the canyon.

Zhao Hai investigated the canyon. It wasn’t very big, about a thousand square meters. The middle of this canyon was a several square meter pool. But the water in this pool was actually blood. Moreover, this canyon didn’t have any plants, the stones in this canyon seemed to turn reddish due to the pool’s liquid.

Whether it was Zhao Hai or Juno, both of them felt a massive pressure coming from the pool. Zhao Hai even felt that this pressure was something much stronger than Iron Hammer’s.

Billy stood at the mouth of the mountain’s cave and stared at the canyon before he sighed and said, “I didn’t know when this mountain canyon has started to exist. When we Dwarves came here, this place already existed. We immediately named it as a Forbidden Place not just because of the blood pool, but also because of those red stones. Once someone touched those stones, their bodies would turn violent before they died. We also intended to study this place, but our findings always turn out nothing.”

After introducing the place, Billy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I’ll be clear to you. We’ve dug the places around this canyon and found that there are large volumes of high yield iron ore present here. It’s enough for our race to use for centuries. But because of this place, we didn’t dare to exploit that resource.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the blood of a God-ranked expert would have such a huge energy. Even the stones cannot be touched. Zhao Hai immediately said, “Good, good, this is very good.”

Zhao Hai opened the wooden fence and then walked towards the canyon. Billy also followed behind him and said after a while, “Mister, as long as you don’t touch those stones directly, you will be alright. However, the pool isn’t good. Even if you wore gloves, you would still perish. I ask mister to be very careful.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he stood at the canyon and then looked around. The position that he was standing in right now was something like a cut-off point. If one proceeded for one step, they would be stepping on red stone. But as long as his skin doesn’t touch it, he would be alright.

Zhao Hai took a deep breath, and then with an intention, he absorbed the land in front of him into the Space, including the stones. He made a margin in his action, just in case the stone can influence those around him, so he also dug up about a meter deep.

Since the canyon was almost composed of Iron Ore, he didn’t dare to dig any deeper. Upon seeing that there were no traces of red stones on the ground, Zhao Hai nodded in satisfaction.

On the other hand, Billy and Juno were staring at Zhao Hai with shock. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be able to do this. Both of them had seen the big world, and they both arrived at the same conclusion, Space-related Divergent Ability!

Divergent Abilities were already very strange things in the continent. But there was one kind of ability that was very difficult to ponder over, and those were Space Divergent Abilities. It wasn’t only because this type of ability was very rare, it was also because this ability was far too different from the other abilities, people weren’t able to research it.

Sharing this fame with Space Divergent Abilities were Space Magics. Although Space Magic had its own systematic method of practice, people with aptitude for it was extremely rare. Therefore, both Space Divergent Techniques and Space Magic were very mysterious to the people in the continent.

Zhao Hai’s method was naturally due to a Space Divergent Ability, this was because Space magic would need incantations in order to use it. Even an 8th rank Space Mage would need to mutter incantations in order to cast a spell.

Billy and Juno looked at each other and saw the shock from the other’s eyes. On the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t pay attention to the reaction of the two. In fact, he had the ability to absorb the entire canyon in one go. But since he didn’t want a huge reaction from the two, he decided to do it by parts.

After absorbing a part, he took a few steps before he waved his hand and took another piece from the canyon. He did this action for quite some time.

After absorbing land for a few dozen times, Zhao Hai finally arrived at the blood pool. Zhao Hai inspected the pool, it wasn’t very big, moreover, it wasn’t deep either. However, it still gave people a very strong pressure. Zhao Hai took a breath and then waved his hand, making a Spatial Rift appear. The pool, as well as the ground it was in, was sucked in. Zhao Hai was taking his time with the pool, he even absorbed the ground two meters beneath it. But even with this, Zhao Hai can still see red stones on the pool’s floor. After digging for another meter, Zhao Hai can no longer see any of them.

In the end, Zhao Hai had absorbed the pool as well as the canyon’s walls. The current canyon was much different than it was before. Zhao Hai seemed to clean the valley up. There were no red stones that can be seen anymore.

* * *

Literally and figuratively

Chapter 576: Suspicion

After Zhao Hai completed everything, he finally relaxed. Although he hasn’t heard a prompt from the Space, he also knew that this was because he placed the things inside the warehouse. As long as he released them in the Space, a prompt should be heard.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t prepared to do it this time. When the Space detects these things, the prompts would be extremely disturbing. Therefore, Zhao Hai plans to take them to the Space this evening.

Zhao Hai was given a scare when he turned around. Billy and Juno were looking at him as though they were looking at a monster. Zhao Hai recovered and smiled bitterly and said, “Did the two of you guess it?”

Billy and Juno nodded simultaneously. Zhao Hai forced a smile and then said, “Don’t worry, I’m not afraid of the two of you knowing. As you have guessed, that was my Space Divergent Ability. But this ability is strange as it doesn’t have any attack power. It can only be used like Space equipments, so I didn’t bother to tell anyone about it.”

Billy and Juno nodded, they didn’t hold even a trace of suspicion to Zhao Hai’s words. They only knew that most offensive attacks didn’t belong to the Space element. If Zhao Hai can use his Space to attack, he would certainly be able to contend against 9th rank experts. In that case, his fame should have been larger than what he had right now.

But Billy and Juno knew that even if Zhao Hai cannot use his Space to attack, he still held a huge advantage compared to the others. However, the two didn’t care about any of these. They were now Zhao Hai’s friends, it was much better for them if Zhao Hai was stronger.

Billy laughed and said, “Mister can rest assured. Apart from the two of us, nobody would be hearing about this matter. As for this old guy, you don’t have to worry a lot about him. He’s already this old, so he knows what he should and shouldn’t say. For him, having you as a friend is much better than being your enemy. At the same time, Mister has helped us with cleaning this place up. Now, we can mine this huge lode of iron.”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled. For the Dwarves, acquiring new mineral loads was the most important thing. This has become a core principle of the entire race.

Juno also smiled bitterly, Billy said that he was old and experienced. Although it was true, age wasn’t really an important factor. In any race, Patriarchs would surely not be simple characters. Otherwise, the current existing races wouldn’t have survived.

The three inspected the valley, and when they did not spot any red stones, they left. All this time, the smile on Billy’s face was unbroken, Zhao Hai had surely given them a huge hand in eliminating this scourge.

The three returned to Billy’s place and after having sat down, Billy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, get us some good liquors. Today is a very happy day, we need to share a cup of two together.”

Juno laughed and said, “You old drunkard, you really are quite shameless when it comes to drinking. Do you really think that Mister Zhao Hai would provide you liquor just like that? Right, since we arrived at this matter, how big is mister’s Space? Why do I feel like you have never been on full capacity before?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “You’re quite right, my Space is very big, I really don’t know its full capacity. I only know that I can store a lot of things inside. Moreover, I can also carry out some Teleportations. Aside from that, then there’s nothing else.”

Juno and Billy almost simultaneously asked, “Teleportation? You said that your Space can do Teleportations?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, but it’s quite difficult, I need to do a lot of preparation in advance. Currently, my Teleportations can only send me back to Golden Island, I still can’t go to other places.”

The reason why Zhao Hai revealed this was because he knew that he would be doing a lot of teleportations in the future. Therefore, it’s much better to just reveal it right now.

Even if Zhao Hai’s tone seemed to express the simplicity of his ability, Juno was still quite envious of Zhao Hai’s teleportation. He smiled bitterly and said, “No wonder Mister can have a lot of things while appearing and disappearing every time. For mister to have these abilities, it was no wonder that the Buda Clan can develop to be what it is right now.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “There’s no other way. The Buda Clan already had a weak foundation. When my Buda Clan was exiled to the Black Wasteland, my family’s housekeeper sold off all of our valuable stuff in exchange for grain, daily necessities, as well as equipment in order to survive in the wasteland. At that time, I was unconscious. When I woke up, I discovered the situation that the Buda Clan was in, which isn’t very good. We planned to live like the Hurricane Family, planting Bamboo Rice and Oil Trees in order to survive.”

Juno and Billy knew about the Buda Clan’s past situation. When they heard Zhao Hai right now, they can imagine the hardships that the Buda Clan had encountered.

Then Zhao Hai sighed and said, “We didn’t know that since the Black Wasteland was right beside the Carrion Swamp, magic beast invasions were quite common. Beasts and undead would run out of the swamp and wreak havoc on the wasteland. Because of that we cannot do even a little bit of farming. Because of that, we have to leave the place.”

Juno and Billy also heard about the Black Wasteland, but they haven’t gone there before. The Dwarves had already left the Black Wasteland for a long time, therefore they don’t have any recent information about that place.

Zhao Hai then continued, “Luckily, we managed to leave the place early. Who would’ve known that the Carrion Swamp’s fog would actually invade the Black Wasteland. We wouldn’t have been able to get out alive.” Then Zhao Hai sighed and then said, “We’re also quite fortunate. Back when we were in the Black Wasteland, I’ve become so depressed that I decided to kill myself. When I went to the Carrion Swamp, I unexpectedly came upon my Magic Staff. The staff not only cured the Water of Nothingness in my body, it also allowed me to use Dark Magic. Even if my Divergent Ability isn’t able to attack, the Dark Magic provided me with offensive power, making me create countless undead. Due to this, I was able to establish my reputation in the continent as being a Dark Mage.”

The other matters were also known by Juno and Billy. They knew that after that, the Buda Clan started chiseling their name into history. Because of this, they came to admire Zhao Hai even more.

Although, Zhao Hai didn’t say where he got his 9th ranks from, they didn’t ask him about it. After all, 9th ranks are the Buda Clan or any other family’s trump cards. Nobody would want to reveal information about them easily. What Zhao Hai told them today was already giving them enough face.

Juno coldly snorted and then said, “The Asku Empire is indeed made up of fools. Before being controlled by the Radiant Church, they were already the second most powerful nation in the continent. But now, they had actually placed at the bottom of the rankings. I must say, they deserved what they got today.”

Billy also coldly snorted, “The Radiant Church gives birth to those mad men. Just because they deem themselves as messengers of God, they wanted to control everything, even the affairs of the Dwarf Race. They didn’t know about Sir Artifact’s influence in our race. They actually sent someone to preach here, they seem to be unafraid of death.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Not only the Dwarves, this happened to the Beastmen as well. Last winter, when I was doing business in the Prairie, I met the current Patriarch of the Herculean Bull Tribe, Wales. I met him at that time when he received news that a Prince of their tribe had rebelled and killed the old Patriarch, competing with Wales for the seat. Wales was out when he received the news, so it was too late for him to respond. But who could imagine that the Fighting Bulls would actually take the throne away from him, casting him away after using him. In the end, the Herculean Bulls had no other place to go other than seeking refuge with the Mastiff Tribe.”

Juno and Billy weren’t aware of the matters in the Prairie. They don’t have any way to get information regarding the Beastmen. The grain and fruit oil that Juno produces was mostly given to the Dwarves, therefore they didn’t have any contact with the Beastmen.

Not only them, even if other Humans had businesses in the Prairie, it would be quite difficult for them to hear about the matters of the Herculean Bull Tribe. Because of this, when they heard Zhao Hai talk about the affairs of the Beastmen, the two’s ears immediately straightened out.

Zhao Hai then added, “When Wales got the news, the Fighting Bulls were chasing after him. At that time, I had a lot of grain in my hands, so I accompanied him to the Dog Race’s domain. Using my food, they managed to reinforce their strength inside the Mastiff Tribe’s place. When the winter started, the Herculean Bulls started their counterattack, eradicating the Fighting Bulls in one fell swoop and reclaimed the position of the Royal Tribe of the Cow Race. Because they were grateful to me as well as me having a Beheading Blood Oath with Wales, I managed to become the Herculean Bulls’ Foreign Prince.”

The two never imagined Zhao Hai to be a Foreign Prince of a Beastman Tribe, so they were puzzled before as to how Zhao Hai has a good relationship with the Beastmen. Now that Zhao Hai revealed his identity to them, they now understood Zhao Hai’s standing in the Prairie.

Then Billy looked straight at Zhao Hai and said, “Beheading Blood Oath? Did you really have a Beheading Blood Oath with a Beastman?”. Zhao Hai nodded.

Juno looked at Billy in confusion as he asked, “What is a Beheading Blood Oath? Why does it sound so ruthless?”

Billy forced a smile and said, “A Beheading Blood Oath is the most sacred pledge that Beastmen can settle on. Beastmen generally won’t use it easily. As long as two people have a Beheading Blood Oath with each other, betrayal would cause them to get punished by the Beast God. This pledge is not a joke.”

When Juno heard Billy, he felt relief. Now he was fully convinced of Zhao Hai’s position among the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and then nodded, “Right, it is because of this Beheading Blood Oath and the position of Foreign Prince that I was able to get relationships with the Beastmen. In the end, i managed to get contact with the Beast King and have him agree to having a milk wine partnership with me.”

Juno sighed and then said, “You say it like it’s easy, but it’s actually very difficult. It seems like you don’t look down on the Beastmen when you interact with them, this might contribute to how easily they managed to trust you. Most Merchants would want to get more benefits from their transactions with the Beastmen. And the Beastmen weren’t fools either, so how can they not notice this aspect? In this case, the Beastmen would surely distance themselves from those Merchants.”

Billy sighed as well, “Actually, our situation is fairly similar with the Beastmen. The things that we produce are in demand with the Humans. So every Human Merchant that comes here would want to profit as much as possible, squeezing every mid of benefit that they can get from us. This explains why our Dwarf Race didn’t have a lot of friends among Humans. Except this old fellow, the only other person is you, Mister Zhao Hai.”

Juno coldly snorted and then said, “Actually, the cause of this matter is the Radiant Church. From what I can remember, the Humans didn’t think differently about other races. There were even some Dwarves that would open up blacksmithing shops in major cities in the continent. And their businesses were very good. At the same time, Beastmen would prosper in Human lands, hiring themselves as mercenaries as well as forming a party with Humans in order to hunt Magic Beasts.”

Zhao Hai was startled at Juno’s words, he didn’t know about any of these. Billy then added, “Exactly. I don’t know when it started, but the Radiant Church had started to preach that the other races were lower forms of beings and were not worthy to live along the Human race. Their priests didn’t treat other races whenever they get wounded, claiming that it would be blasphemous to the Radiant God. Because of these actions, the other Humans slowly started to think that the other races were truly of lower status, slowly driving them away from their settlements. The Beastmen suddenly weren’t able to become mercenaries, while the Dwarves were banned from opening up shop.”

When Zhao Hai heard Juno and Billy, he couldn’t help but stare blankly, then his face changed as he thought about Iron Hammer’s words. In the Divine Realm, the Human gods started to wage war with the Gods of the other races. In the war, the Humans wanted to send people down in order to eradicate the other races. And if the Radiant Church really did what Juno and Billy said, then wouldn’t that be like the moves by the Human Gods? If that’s the case, then thing had become more complicated.

But Zhao Hai didn’t express his suspicion. He had just linked all of these in his head and found some connections between them. If he really guessed correctly, then the Radiant Church would be a huge problem. Their background might be very difficult to deal with.

Chapter 577: Level Up

Zhao Hai recalled about the past actions of the Radiant Church and discovered that they were doing things that suppressed the other races. They established their influence and controlled Nobles, these things aren’t something that normal Churches would do. Moreover, all of these were done by themselves, without the help of any influence, this was a difficult thing to accomplish.

Any religious sect has its own beliefs, but one should know that ideas are intangible while people are. Without people to believe in them, then a religion would be useless.

From its establishment up to the present, along with the number of Popes that had passed, how was the Radiant Church able to continually suppress the other races as well as the other churches? One must know that suppressing other religions cannot be done in a day or two, nor was it very easy. For the Radiant Church to do this for quite a long time was quite the mystery.

But if the Radiant Church has a God-ranked expert pulling its strings from behind, then the situation would be different. Although God-ranked experts cannot descend easily, the Artisan God and the others were able to send their Divine Artifacts down. Therefore, it shouldn’t be very difficult for these Gods to send a message down, instructing the Radiant Church about what to do.

The more he thought about it, the more plausible his idea has become. However, Zhao Hai still cannot inform Billy and Juno about this matter. If the two knew about this, who knows what their reaction would be? If the people outside knew, then the matter would become much more complicated.

At this time, Billy and Juno were still talking about the Radiant Church, but Zhao Hai was already not listening to them. He wanted to discuss this matter with Laura and the others as soon as possible and hear their opinions.

Billy and Juno discovered that Zhao Hai’s state was not right, so Billy immediately asked, “Mister Zhao Hai, what happened?”

Zhao Hai recovered and looked at the two before he smiled faintly and said, “There’s no problem, I just feel somewhat tired. I’ll go back to rest first, if there’s any matter, you can just send word to my room.”

Billy and Juno also thought that since Zhao Hai had used his Space Ability, he should be very tired right now. Therefore, Billy replied, “Mister, do you want to be examined by our doctor?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m fine, I’m only a little bit tired. I didn’t get a good sleep yesterday, and then I drank today and then used my ability. I’m fairly fatigued right now, resting for a while would suffice.”

Billy and Juno nodded, then Zhao Hai turned and left the room in haste. Laura and the others weren’t inside the room, so Zhao Hai flashed to the Space and then had Cai’er call them over.

Laura and the others weren’t actually inside the Space. They were currently with the Dwarves as they wandered around the place.

Zhao Hai sat in the Space, calmly ruminating over Juno and Billy’s words. He also had Cai’er get the information that they had acquired about the Radiant Church as he looked over them.

They had found out that even though the Radiant Church had been amassing a ton of wealth all these years, nobody in the church benefited from it. The Popes and Bishops of the Church didn’t use it for themselves. They may use those funds to recruit some Nobles, but the majority of it was used to deal with the other races. Their Popes and Bishops all lived very poor lives, a lot of their Popes died with no money to their name.

This method of the Radiant Church was something beyond common sense. It was impossible for the Church’s founders to immediately develop hatred towards the other races, this was something natural. However, after a few generations, the Church started to hate upon the other races, this matter couldn’t be justified.

Because of these generations of effort, the other races started to disappear from the Human lands. Moreover, the Radiant Church had managed to make the religion their monopoly. Although one couldn’t see it, the Radiant Church had slowly encroached their control on the other religions.

While Zhao Hai was looking up all of these, Laura and the others returned to the room. Cai’er immediately transported the women to the Space. When they saw Zhao Hai in the villa along with a bunch of documents, they stared. Zhao Hai usually didn’t care about these documents, what happened?

Laura immediately stepped forward and then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what happened? What are you looking for in these documents? Wait, these are related to the Radiant Church. Did the church cause trouble again?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and waved his hand to make them sit down. Then Zhao Hai told Laura and the others what he heard from Billy and Juno, as well as expressing his suspicions.

While the women were listening to Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but frown. Then after some time, Laura said, “Brother Hai, your suspicion might be true. So what do we do?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “The only thing we can do right now is to upgrade our strengths. If we spread this news out, people would suspect about the Radiant Church’s connection with the Divine Realm. And if those guys knew that we had found out about their background, then they might send in God-ranked experts ahead of time, while our strength is still weak. When that happens, our losses would be very great.”

Laura nodded, and then she said, “Right, Brother Hai, aren’t you getting some God’s Blood today? Did you acquire it?”

Zhao Hai tapped his head and then he bitterly smiled and said, “I forgot about it. I’ll introduce those things to the Space right now.” Then with an intention, he released the God’s Blood into the Space.

Just as it was released, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “Massively energized liquid has been detected, immensely strengthening the water and the soil as well as the abilities of the Space. The Farming ground has been improved, the crops maturity has been reduced by 100 times, the background would be accelerated by ten times. The Spatial Water has also been improved.

The powerful liquid also strengthened the host’s body as well as his current rank. The seven Divergent techniques of the host are now: metal, wood, water, fire, earth, crystal, and space has been improved to Advanced level. Host’s potential has been further promoted.

The Space has leveled up to 52. Host may use ten ordinary backgrounds, asking the host to try harder.

The undead, phantasmal beasts, magic beasts, and plants in the Space has also been improved. The metals in the Space has now increased its output.

The managers of the Space, Cai’er and Mu’er has also been improved. The Ghost Staff is upgraded and is now renamed to Blood Ghost Staff. Host can now vary its length and form. Host can transform the staff into anything including 108 throwing knives. The host can also fly using the Staff.

Because of the promotion, the Host can also choose one special magic garment that is provided by the Space. Host should choose wisely!”

The bombardment of information made Zhao Hai dizzy. Then, he immediately called Mu’er and Cai’er over. Cai’er’s new form made Zhao Hai stare. Before, Cai’er was only as big as a person’s palm, but now she was as big as an arm, she also appeared much more lovely. Mu’er’s appearance also surprised Zhao Hai. Although he was still attached to the whip, he was now much more solid compared to before, and was now as large as a person’s palm. He seemed much more real this time, compared to his somewhat faint form before.

Zhao Hai knew that the cause for their changes was the Space levelling up. So he immediately looked at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, what’s your rank right now?”

Cai’er thought for a moment and then said, “I really don’t know. But if I were to talk in terms of the Demon Realm, then even Heavenly Demons wouldn’t be able to defeat me, and it might even be possible for me to kill them!”

Zhao Hai asked, “Heavenly Demon? What kind of existence is that?”

Cai’er replied, “Heavenly Demons are the strongest existences in the Demon Realm. Their strengths are much more formidable than 9th rank experts. The Ark Continent doesn’t seem to have those kinds of existences, but I can also feel that the plane doesn’t allow them to be here. But since my main body is inside Young Master’s Space, while the things outside are my branches, I wasn’t expelled by the plane.”

Zhao Hai understood, Cai’er strength shouldn’t be very different from those God-ranked experts. Those Heavenly Demons that she stated seem to be like the Gods in the Divine Realm.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but be moved. Then he immediately said, “Cai’er, what level do you see me right now?’

Cai’er looked at Zhao Hai and then said, “Young master, your current strength is equal to a 9th rank expert. But even if you have reached 9th rank, you still don’t reach the level of a Heavenly Demon.” Zhao Hai nodded and then ribbed his chin. Him becoming as strong as a 9th rank expert is already good. If he has achieved God-rank, then the Ark Continent might be unable to accommodate him, kicking him out in the process.

Then Zhao Hai turned his head to Mu’er and then said, “Mu’er how about you? Is your strength the same as Cai’er’s?”

Without even waiting for Mu’er to speak, Cai’er disdainfully replied, “He needs to wait a bit more. He had become strong, but not as strong as me. However, dealing with several 9th rank experts shouldn’t be a problem for him.”

Then Zhao Hai thought about those 9th rank Magic Beasts in the Space, “What about those 9th ranks in the Space? What level are they right now?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Their potential isn’t very good. Although they are stronger than before, they aren’t as strong as Mu’er.”

When Zhao Hai heard Cai’er, he couldn’t help but relax. He was afraid that those 9th ranks would turn into God-rank experts, that would be very troublesome.

But Zhao Hai also understood that those 9th rank experts were unrelated to the Space. The things that the Space prioritizes in strengthening were only itself as well as the Host. For other creatures inside, they can only receive the scraps. Therefore, this outcome isn’t really a surprise.

Chapter 578: Ability

Zhao Hai still kept asking questions, “Right, how about the undead? I seem to hear that they had been improved. What are their levels right now?”

When Cai’er heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but laugh. Then she smiled at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, you are correct. The undead are now 9th ranks!”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai, Laura, and the others’ bodies couldn’t help but shiver. The undeads have turned into 9th ranks? What kind of concept is that? Does that mean that Zhao Hai now has more than 1 million 9th ranks in his hand?

More than 1 million experts? This, isn’t this too scary? If Zhao Hai released all of those undead right now, wouldn’t conquering the continent be extremely easy?

However, Zhao Hai turned this idea down. If he can’t do it in the past, the more he can’t be allowed to do it now that he knows about God-ranked experts. If he releases those undead and unify the continent, then the Radiant Church might react and deal with him.

Zhao Hai might be able to neglect the Radiant Church, but he cannot ignore the church’s background. Iron Hammer also expressed the existence of the Divine Realm’s natives. They were born as 5th rank and grow up to be 9th, with a little practice, they would also reach God-rank. If those people send their members down as well, Zhao Hai’s 9th ranks would turn out useless.

Zhao Hai turned to Cai’er and said, “What about the Space? In which way did it improve?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, the lands have been improved immensely. Crops that usually take eight hours to mature now only needed 48 minutes to do so. In the past, the background can’t accelerate growth, but now it has the characteristics of the original Farming ground. At the same time, the Magic Beasts have been improved. Inferior beasts, have reached around 7th to 8th rank. Advanced beasts have reached 9th rank. Because of the Blood Hawk’s special lineage, it only reached 8th rank. However, not only could it carry any person, it can also transport a team of people with no problem. Also, the Magic beasts can now become phantasmal beasts, no matter what type they are, they would be able to turn into weapons or armor. Additionally, we should preserve those Bread Trees that we planted in the background. As soon as ample time passes, those trees would be able to gain sentience just like me.”

Zhao Hai was shocked, he didn’t expect the amount of changes that happened to the Space. Moreover, eight-hour crops now take less than an hour to mature. Isn’t this speed just too fast?

Cai’er looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and then said, “Also, Young Master, the Spatial Water has also gotten better. Not only can it detoxify, it can also help the cultivation of people up to 8th rank. But since the Space now has a Blood Pond, even 9th ranks would be able to benefit from it. Young Master can have Laura and the others drink from the pond and make them 9th rank experts.”

Zhao Hai knitted his eyebrows and then said, “Wouldn’t the energy in the pond be too strong? Are they able to bear with it?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master doesn’t need to worry. Most of the Blood’s energy has already been absorbed by the Young Master and the Space. The energy left right now is mild. So there isn’t any problem.”

Zhao Hai gave a satisfied nod and then he said, “Also, the Space told me that I can use ten Ordinary Backgrounds? What are those Ordinary Backgrounds? And are there things other than ordinary ones?”

Cai’er nodded and said, “Yes, the Space’s backgrounds can be divided into four categories. The first one is the Ordinary Background, it looks just like the one that the Young Master has been using. It’s just a piece of land, and nothing else, not even special properties. The second kind is the Mechanical Background. This one has things that can be found in a mechanized civilization. The Young Master can enjoy tall buildings in this background as well as its advanced technology. The Young Master can even use cars and airplanes in this place.

The third kind is a Magical Background. This background is pretty much like the Ark Continent, but much more advanced. The Young Master can learn better Magic Formations than the ones that can be found in the continent. There are also floating islands in the sky.

The fourth kind is the Cultivation Background. This background is very huge, the Young Master would be able to acquire magical treasures inside. However, the Young Master needs a very high level in order to attain this background.”

For Zhao Hai, who came from Earth, he immediately understood everything that Cai’er had said about these backgrounds.

Zhao Hai thought that if the Space can unlock Cultivation Backgrounds, then how awesome would that be? Would he be able to use flying swords at that time?

Zhao Hai calmed down from his shock. He would no longer worry about bad things happening when he gets a high enough rank. Zhao Hai then looked at Cai’er and said, “How about the Ghost Staff? What abilities did it acquire?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “To be short, the Ghost Staff is now renamed to Blood Ghost Staff. It can now become liquid like water and transform into anything that the Young Master wants. It can also fly, lengthen itself, shorten itself, it can even separate and form 108 flying daggers. Under the command of the Young Master, those knives would fly and attack the enemies. Naturally, the scope of this attack is limited to 10 thousand meters. If the Young Master isn’t in trouble, you can turn it into a vehicle, any vehicle that you can think about. At the same time, since it can fly, the Young Master would have an alternative to using the Blood Hawk when circumstances need it.”

Zhao Hai felt so happy he almost forgot to breathe. This was too good. The Staff had become just like flying magical treasures that were seen in Cultivation worlds. It may even be better than those.

Zhao Hai suddenly thought about the final prompt, something about a Magic garment. So he immediately asked Cai’er about it, “Cai’er can I use that Magic Garment now? I want to see what kinds are available.”

Cai’er complied as she waved her hand, making a screen appear in front of them. On the screen were several pictures of clothes, as well as descriptions for each of them.

Zhao Hai almost fainted when he saw these clothes. Why did he see Superman’s clothing first? What does the Space want him to wear outside? This looks too abnormal!

There was also Spider Man’s clothes, the Fantastic Four, X-men, along with many others. Everything that Zhao Hai saw made his head dizzy.

Laura and the others also looked at the garments and couldn’t believe how people could wear such weird clothes.

After looking for quite a while, Zhao Hai finally made his choice. What he chose was a Magic Robe. However, this Robe seems to be made with unusual materials. It looks like it was made of very soft metal, not only did it have strong impact resistance, it also had anti-magic properties. At the same time, it can also automatically purify the wearer’s body. Most importantly, this robe is part of a set, from underwear to the outermost layer. Along with the black underwear, it also had a tight fitting clothes along with gloves and socks. The next layer consists of a long robe. But it wasn’t like the Robes that the continent uses that has a belt in it. This one looks like robes worn in ancient China. Then the next layer was a cloak, connected to the body via shoulder armor. The cloak seemed to be made up of bear fur and was locked to the armor using something in a form of animal claws. One could use this cloak to cover the user’s entire body, only leaving the head and the shoulder armor to be seen. It also had a pair of black boots. He looked very cool while wearing it.

But what made Zhao Hai choose this set was its ability to transform. In other words, he can momentarily change how it looks from the outside.

From what Zhao Hai saw, this set looked something like a prototype of some highly advanced civilization from novels back on Earth, with slight modifications here and there.

Comparing it from the other choices, Zhao Hai thought that this set suited him the best. So he immediately chose this set and after a flash of light, he was already wearing it.

When they looked at Zhao Hai, the eyes of Laura and the others shone. Zhao Hai looks very compatible with these set of clothes. The long robe, matches Zhao Hai’s temperament, making him look very gentle. The shoulder armor gave him a sort of martial aura. The cloak gave him an aura of power and prestige. The black clothing made him mysterious. Having all of this together made Zhao Hai look like a different person.

Zhao Hai was not a specially charming person, he normally just looks like an easily approachable person. But with these clothes on, he looked very different. He seemed to be much more dazzling compared to before, and his entire temperament changed. Those who wasn’t here to see him would find themselves doubting his identity.

Zhao Hai was also very satisfied with these clothes. This surprisingly changed how he looks. Moreover, because of his Metal Manipulation ability, he can turn it into a weapon when necessary.

Chapter 579: Elder

Although Zhao Hai’s new clothes were made of a special type of metal, it didn’t have that feeling of coldness at all. Conversely, they were very comfortable and warm. A warmth that might make you fall asleep, it felt very good.

While Zhao Hai was wearing the clothes, he made it transform into other types of clothing before he stopped and returned to normal. Then he turned to Laura and the others and said, “Do you like these clothes?”

With shining eyes, Laura and the others nodded. They also wanted to have these type of clothing, they can choose what form that they like, so they don’t need to change at all. It was very convenient.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he turned to Cai’er and said, “Right, now that the Space has been upgraded, are we able to plant some special plants?”

Cai’er nodded and said, “Yes, some can enhance physical qualities while some can help with cultivation.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, you go take a look at the Processing Machine if you are able to make those kinds of seeds. Then plant them on the Farming Grounds and see their effects. See if there are those that are like the Goldmetal Fruit, plants that can give Divergent Abilities. We have to get as many of those as possible.”

Cai’er complied, and said, “Alright, rest assured, Young Master. I’ll take care of it.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod, “Right, I want to see what kinds of backgrounds I can use right now.”

Cai’er nodded, then he gave information about the different backgrounds that Zhao Hai can use. Although the backgrounds are ordinary, they were still some differences among them. For example, there were desert backgrounds that would be useless if Zhao Hai was to buy it.

Zhao Hai opted to get backgrounds that can be planted on. They aren’t extraordinary, but among them there were mountains, prairies, and there was also one with a mountain with a river on it. In short, there were a lot of varieties of them.

Naturally, Zhao Hai also listened to the opinion of his wives. Laura and the others were very happy when they were given a choice. Before long, the ten backgrounds have been chosen.

After choosing the backgrounds, Zhao Hai turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, how can we use these backgrounds?”

Cai’er replied, “Young Master can just make me manage them. But if you want to go there, you can just do it with an intention. I shall place plants and Magic Beasts on those backgrounds according to their compatibility. Also, the Young Master doesn’t need to worry about houses, the ten backgrounds have their own. But no matter which background is in use, the Farming Grounds would still be present. Most importantly, these new backgrounds are different from the original background since they cannot accelerate plant growth.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That’s not a problem. Aren’t they just the same as the original background from before? I’ll just leave the management of those to you.”

Cai’er nodded. And just as Zhao Hai was about to lead Laura and the others to explore the new backgrounds, Cai’er suddenly said, “Young Master, the Dwarves have sent someone to see you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and then immediately brought Laura and the others to their room in the Dwarf Mountains. Strangely, even if Zhao Hai had become a 9th rank expert, he didn’t have any imposing aura, his temperament stayed just like before.

Zhao Hai also found out that after crystallizing his body, he can then use the Space to attack his enemy. The root of this offensive attack is the God’s Blood. The Space’s explanation was that since the energy of the God’s Blood has been absorbed by the Space, once it exits it, it can reabsorb that energy and attack the target. Therefore, Zhao Hai can use this method as an attack for his Space Divergent Ability.

But Zhao Hai wasn’t planning to use this attack, he also didn’t have any idea how to do so. Still, he has his metal, wood, water, fire, plant, abilities for attack, and their powers aren’t weak.

Zhao Hai also asked Cai’er to break the crystal bottle that contained the small sun, but Cai’er can’t do it. This reassured Zhao Hai, this meant that even God-ranked experts aren’t able to break his crystal body. So even if he meets God-ranked experts, he still had a way to preserve his life.

Also, Zhao Hai didn’t make Laura and the others drink the God’s Blood at this time. Although they can now become 9th rank experts, Laura and the others didn’t cultivate for the ten days that they had been with the Dwarves. Them advancing at this time would be strange.

Because of this Zhao Hai didn’t make them practice and just brought them along with him outside as he opened the door to see a Dwarf.

When the Dwarf saw Zhao Hai, he immediately gave a bow and said, “I’ve been asked to invite mister Zhao Hai to the Divine Palace. The Patriarch wanted mister to come.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he nodded and walked towards the Divine Palace along with the Dwarf. While walking, Zhao Hai was wondering what Billy intended to do. At the same time, he was compiling everything about the Space inside his mind. And before long, he had finally arrived at the Divine Palace.

Upon reaching the place, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. In the Divine Palace, a lot of Dwarves were present. Moreover, the statuses of these people doesn’t seem to be normal. Each and every one of them had fairly white beards and hairs. One would see that they were quite mature members of the race.

Under the guidance of the Dwarf, Zhao Hai entered the Great Hall. But he was till puzzled about the number of Dwarves that were present. It looked like they were having a grand meeting. But what does he have to do with it?

Before long, he was walking in front of Iron Hammer. Zhao Hai can also spot Billy and the elders there, all of them looked at Zhao Hai with a hint of gratitude in their eyes.

Seeing the expressions of these Dwarves while being next to Iron Hammer, Zhao Hai can faintly guess what was going on. It seems like Billy informed these people about Iron Hammer’s materialization. The people present here seems to hold special status in their race.

But Zhao Hai didn’t say anything. He arrived at Billy’s side and gave Billy and the elders a salute. Then every Dwarf present in the Great Hall immediately returned the gesture. It seems like they won’t dare to accept Zhao Hai’s courtesy.

Zhao Hai also noted that Laura and the others stayed outside the Great Hall, the same was true for Juno. This made Zhao Hai very curious.

After exchanging their greetings, Billy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, this time, you had greatly helped our Dwarf Race. Therefore, we decided to give Mister the position of our race’s Foreign Elder. I’ll ask Mister to accept it.” Then Billy bowed towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai was actually shocked that he couldn’t respond for quite some time. This was because he hasn’t heard about this before, so he didn’t expect Billy to reach this decision.

Zhao Hai’s unresponsiveness scared Juno and the others. Juno knew the Dwarves very well. If the Dwarves wanted you to be their elder, then you better not decline, even if it was out of politeness. Otherwise, the Dwarves would think that you are looking down on them. If Zhao Hai treated the Dwarves like how he treated humans, then their connection might be broken.

Billy not telling Zhao Hai about this beforehand has its reasons. This was the Dwarves’ custom of appointing elders. They think that it was much better for the person’s reaction to be genuine. If Zhao Hai was informed beforehand, then he would be prepared. But if he was suddenly appointed, they would be able to see from his expression if he really wanted to be their elder.

Actually, this regulation is very excessive, but the Dwarves think that this was good, so they decided to maintain this rule. The Dwarves had also bestowed Foreign Elder positions before in such a spontaneous matter, even Juno didn’t know about it.

Zhao Hai quickly recovered, he looked at Billy and then smiled faintly before replying, “Alright, I’ll respectfully accept this position. I’ll be a Foreign Elder.”

This response relaxed the people present. Billy stood up and laughed, “Great! Then I’ll have to ask Mister Zhao Hai to pay respects to the Divine Protector and receive our race’s elder token.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned around to give respects to Iron Hammer before accepting an ancient bronze Command Token from Billy. This token made Zhao Hai stare, since it was made of bronze, Zhao Hai was expecting it to be very heavy. He didn’t expect the token to be as light as a feather.

This Command Token looked very simple, a single character expressing command was written on it. At the back of it was Iron Hammer’s image. It was a very simple Command Token, but Zhao Hai knew that what this token represented was not very simple.

This position of Foreign Elder of the Dwarf Race is not worse than being a Foreign Prince of the entire Beastman Race. Such identity was extremely significant.

After Zhao Hai accepted the token, the ceremony for being an elder has been completed. But Zhao Hai didn’t say anything.

After Zhao Hai received the elder Command Token, the Dwarves simultaneously saluted, “We have seen the elder!”

Zhao Hai quickly responded, “Please get up.” The Dwarves got up as Billy loudly declared “Prepare the banquet, let’s welcome our Dwarf Race’s new Elder!”

The Dwarves present immediately complied as they turned around to leave. At this time, Billy also invited Zhao Hai back to his residence. After entering his office, the only three people left was Zhao Hai, Billy, and Juno.

After the three sat down, Zhao Hai cannot help but smile bitterly towards Billy and said, “Patriarch, this is too sudden. What would you have done if I refused?”

Billy laughed and said, “This is our race’s custom. If you rejected, then it would be impossible for you to become a friend to our race. Even if you help us out big time once more.”

Juno looked at Zhao Hai with envy as he said, “You should be happy. Now that you have become the Dwarves’ Foreign Elder, you will gain huge benefits in the future. My relationship with Billy has always been good, yet I still hadn’t become their Foreign Elder.”

Billy smiled and said, “Unfortunately, the matter of Foreign Elders is not something that I alone can decide. The decision must undergo an elder’s assembly as well as a meeting with various mining heads. Zhao Hai has helped us hugely this time, so it was impossible for him to not be bestowed the position of Foreign Elder.”

Then Billy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Right, aren’t you Humans very modest? When they come across such matters, Humans usually decline first. Why didn’t you?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You forget, but I am also a Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bull Tribe. I have experience in such matters. So I know that if I decline, It would seem like I was looking down on the Dwarf Race. Therefore, I didn’t bother to decline first.”

Billy laughed, “So you have experience. Hahaha. That’s fantastic. Since you’ve become our Foreign Elder, our race’s liquor would depend on you.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. He felt like he just had joined a gang of evildoers. He had become their Foreign Elder, but now he was in charge of their liquor.

But he wasn’t worried, even if the Beastmen cannot catch up to the demand, Zhao Hai now has ten backgrounds to use. These backgrounds can raise some argali as well as cattle. Therefore, their milk production should skyrocket.

Billy smiled and said, “Don’t worry, we won’t be taking your liquor for free. We shall trade them with ironwares. But since you’re our Foreign Elder, you cannot sell it to us with the same price as outside, it should be lower. But since we’ll also sell you our ironwares for cheap, you wouldn’t be able to suffer any losses.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “No problem. But I currently am short on manpower. So I don’t have any means to produce a lot of milk wine. Moreover, the Beastman milk wine output is quite limited, therefore, the liquor that I can provide is quite low. It’s impossible for me to provide a high volume right from the start.”

Billy and Juno nodded, Zhao Hai looked at their eyes deeply before he hardened his resolve and said, “Patriarch, I have a matter to ask your help with.”

Billy stared, then he immediately smiled and said, “You’re our race’s Foreign Elder, you’re part of us now. So can tell me what you want.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I want to ask some Dwarves to settle down in my territory. Helping me produce some ironwares. Is that possible?”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Billy cannot help but gawk. Then he frowned and said, “I’m afraid that this is somewhat difficult. You should know that there are a lot of eyes on Golden Island. Seeing Dwarves there would cause too much of a problem.”

Chapter 580: Laying the Cards Out on the Table

Upon hearing Billy, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly as he said, “That’s not a problem. The place I want to take them isn’t Golden Island, but to my Buda Clan’s true territory. In there, no other people aside from our Buda Clan and the slaves are present.”

Billy and Juno couldn’t help but stare upon hearing Zhao Hai. Then both of their eyes shone brightly, it didn’t take a while before Juno said, “Did you send your 100 thousand slaves to that place?”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he smiled faintly and said, “So you knew, right, the slaves were sent to that place. Not only those slaves but our wineries and factories are in that place as well.”

Billy might not be very clear about it, but Juno knew how many products Zhao Hai sold in the continent. Haven products, Beastmen goods, all of them required a lot of processing.

Billy was confused, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Besides Golden Island, what other territory did the Buda Clan have? I don’t seem to remember the Buda Clan buying other territories in the past two years.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We don’t need to buy any land. Our Buda Clan already has an enormous land, wouldn’t it be a pity if we don’t use it? Our territory is as large as the Aksu Empire.”

Billy and Juno stared, then they immediately reacted. The only territory that Zhao Hai could refer to would be the Black Wasteland. That place was the continent’s biggest territory, one that belonged to the Buda Clan.

However, Billy and Juno, along with the people of the continent, knew the current situation of the Buda Clan. The two looked at each other before Juno turned to Zhao Hai and asked, “Little Hai, isn’t that area filled with the Carrion Swamp’s poisonous mist? How can people live there?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Any poison has its own antidote. Did the two of you forget where my Magic Staff is from? In a sense, our Buda Clan is already somewhat in control of the Carrion Swamp. When the Buda Clan went to war in the past, the 9th ranks that we have are all from the swamp.”

Billy and Juno’s bodies shook. They suddenly remembered the Dwarf Race’s prophecy. One of the five Forbidden Areas has been conquered!

The Divine Artifact has been recognized, and now the Carrion Swamp was under the control of the Buda Clan. Then this meant that they had conquered one of the Forbidden Areas, this was a step to fulfilling the prophecy.

The two looked at each other and saw the shock on each other’s eyes. Zhao Hai was looking at them in confusion, he knew that they would be shocked, but their reaction was a little bit strange.

Billy sighed and said, “Heaven’s Will, is this the Heaven’s Will?”

Juno also sighed as he said, “It seems so. Now we must wait for the news from the Elves.”

Zhao Hai was puzzled at the two, so he asked, “What’s wrong? What are you mumbling about?”

Billy sighed, then he told Zhao Hai about the prophecy of their Dwarf Race. The prophecy was easy to understand, so there was no further explanation needed. Zhao Hai only needed to listen in order to understand.

Zhao Hai’s expression changed, he knew more than Juno and Billy did about this matter. Juno and Billy didn’t know about the war between the races as well as the Divine Realm.

Billy looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and thought that it was caused by the prophecy. Therefore, he sighed and said, “Now I think that the King that was mentioned was you. It’s because you’ve already fulfilled two aspects of the prophecy.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he sighed, then he turned to look at the two before saying, “In fact, even if I didn’t know of this prophecy, i know more than the two of you when it comes to this matter. In the Divine Realm….” Then Zhao Hai told them the things about the Gods that he had heard from Iron Hammer.

After Zhao Hai reiterated everything to Billy, he said, “Actually, I’ve heard all of this from the Artifact Spirit. I’m just afraid that too many people would know, so I asked him to refrain from telling others. Your Dwarves’ Forbidden Land was a place where that God was injured. The blood there wasn’t poisonous, it’s just that the energy contained in it was too strong, people simply cannot bear it. I refrained from telling everyone about this because I suspect that the Radiant Church has relations to a God-ranked expert. If this matter gets spread around, it might reach the ears of the church. If they do, the Gods might send their people ahead of time, far before we have prepared. The strength of the continent is currently lacking. I’m worried that we might lose big in the confrontation. Therefore, I intend to go back and research the God’s Blood and see if I can produce a potion that may improve ranks and train a lot of 9th ranks. If we accomplish this, then we may have a fighting chance against the people from the Divine Realm. I just didn’t expect the Dwarves to have this prophecy. It’s surely the will of the heavens!”

The heads of Billy and Juno couldn’t help but turn blank after listening to Zhao Hai. They weren’t expecting this influx of information, it seems like they needed to prepare.

After some time, Billy recovered. He stood up and said, “So it’s actually the Radiant Church. I always thought that these people are rotten eggs. So it turns out that they have this motive.”

Juno’s expression was also ugly as he said, “I think that Little Hai’s suspicion is highly probable. The things that the Radiant Church has been doing recently cannot be justified. If they really do have a background, just like what Little Hai said, then this matter has turned quite dangerous. If people from the Divine Realm send people down, then it would be very troublesome.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Not only that, besides the Radiant Church, there is also the Engraved Ark. I don’t know what kind of organization they are, but it seems like they are hell bent on the destruction of the continent. In the past, when the Divine Realm sent a God-ranked expert down, that person managed to damage the three Divine Artifacts sent down to defeat him. I need to repair those two other Artifacts in order to improve our chances of coming out on top. However, even if I repair those artifacts, I think that it would still be very hard for us, seeing that the Divine Realm already knows that we possess those three Artifacts. When they come, I’m fairly certain that they would bring countermeasures in order to deal with those.”

Juno and Billy frowned, their expression weren’t very attractive. The matters that were involved in this was just too big. They simply cannot handle this just by themselves.

Zhao Hai looked at the two and said, “I think we’re fine for now. We just need to find solutions in order to deal with it. I’m requesting Patriarch Billy to come in contact with the Elves as soon as possible while I go to the Beastmen and see their Beast God’s Spear. If possible, I’ll go and fix their Artifact. When that time comes, we can get ourselves more leeway. But the most important thing right now is to keep this matter a secret. We can’t tell anyone, even the people that we trust. These words would only stay inside this room. What do the two of you think?”

Billy and Juno thought for a moment before they succumbed to the fact that they had nothing to solve this matter with in the meantime. So the can only sigh and say, “Alright, it seems like this is the only thing that we can do at this moment.”

Zhao Hai looked at their faces and smiled faintly, “You two don’t need to worry too much. Our Buda Clan’s potion making is very advanced. Perhaps we can make use of the God’s Blood and prepare some potions in order to mass produce 9th rank experts. When that time comes, then we would be able to deal with the attack coming from the Divine Realm.”

Billy and Juno couldn’t help but bitterly smile, they understood that those words were only said in order to console them. Then suddenly, Billy’s eyes shone, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, the prophecy included the Five Forbidden Areas. In other words, if mister can conquer those five, then you might come to find some benefits that can help in dealing with this matter.”

Juno’s eyes turned bright as well, “Right, Little Hai, you might as well do that. If you can do that, then we would have more confidence in confronting the Gods. Do you think you can do that with your current ability?”

Zhao Hai were thinking about their proposals. Actually, he also wanted to explore those five areas, but he just didn’t have the time. But after this meeting, it seems like Zhao Hai really does need to explore the Five Forbidden Areas. But before he explores those places, he wanted to go and visit the Elven Forest first.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I will certainly go if given the opportunity. But I need to see the Beastmen first and see whether I can fix their Beast God’s Spear. Patriarch Billy should also get news from the Elves while seeing if they can allow me to fix their Elven Bow. After completing these, I think it wouldn’t be too late before I can explore those Forbidden Areas.”

Billy nodded and said, “Alright, then it’s settled. I’ll send word to the Elves as soon as possible. I’ll ask for the Elven Bow first before asking about their Tree of LIfe. If their Tree did indeed dry up or has any problems, then the prophecy might as well be realized.”

Zhao Hai and Juno nodded. The hearts of the three felt quite heavy, not because of anything else but the matters of the Divine Realm. These people represent the pinnacle of strength in the Continent. If they go against this legend one day, then they would need a lot of firepower. This was the Divine Realm, they cannot be underestimated.

Chapter 581: Banquet

*Knock* *Knock* *Knock* Three knocks were heard before the three woke up from their thoughts. Billy looked at the door and said, “Who is it?”

A voice was heard from outside, “Patriarch, the banquet for Mister Zhao Hai has been prepared.”

Billy couldn’t help but pat his head. Because of the weight of their conversation, the three had forgotten about the banquet.

So Billy immediately responded, “Alright, we’ll be heading there soon. You go first.” Then the person outside complied as he retreated.

Billy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Sending Dwarves to your territory wouldn’t be a problem. How many people do you want to be sent there?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The more the better, but there aren’t a lot of iron back in my place. After all, my main products are crops and processed goods. The thing that is abundant there is liquor.”

Billy laughed and said, “That wouldn’t be a problem. Also, you being the prophesized person is very good for us. Don’t forget, the prophecy stated that you would be the King of all and the hero that would save us all.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I can be fine as a hero, but I don’t think I can handle being the King of all. It’s those bastard Gods’ fault. We didn’t do anything but they dare to disrupt our lives? Such bastards.”

Zhao Hai normally watches out for the words that came out of his mouth. But he let that rule off this time. This matter had truly filled him with anger, he couldn’t bear but scold the perpetrators.

Billy laughed loudly as he said, “Good, you curse quite well. Those Gods really aren’t very good people. Right, don’t go away soon. Let’s drink a lot this time. No matter what, today’s a happy day.”

Zhao Hai had no choice but to nod. Juno smiled as well. Then the three of them walked out of Billy’s office. However, Billy didn’t lead them to the Dining Hall, instead, he brought them to the Divine Palace.

The scene made Zhao Hai stare. The Divine Palace’s square was very big, it was more than 100 thousand square meters. And yet, the square was chock full of tables right now. A lot of Dwarves were already sitting down while women were serving them dishes.

Upon looking at this scene, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but turn blank. He had seen Beastmen banquets before. But he hadn’t seen a thing such as this before. The didn’t think that the Dwarves would also have such large banquets like this.

Zhao Hai discovered that Laura and the others were already at the square. Moreover, they were already sitting down and chatting with Dwarf women.

Billy didn’t say anything as he pulled Zhao Hai to sit at a table that was already reserved for them. At this time, they were served with special dishes of the Dwarf Race.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation before he turned to Billy and said, “I have a lot of liquor. Can I serve them here to drink?”

Billy laughed and said, “That’ll be great. Quickly take them out.” Then he stood up and announced, “Today, we celebrate this banquet in order to honor our Dwarf Race’s new Foreign Elder. Elder Zhao Hai is also very happy, so he had prepared some liquor for everyone to drink!”

Just as Billy’s voice fell, a resounding applause was heard in the entire square. Zhao Hai didn’t delay as he faintly smiled and waved his hand took out some liquor bags, each no less than 100 jin in weight.

Zhao Hai stopped as soon as it reached 500 bags. The Dwarves currently present here numbered about 10 thousand people. If he didn’t take these many out, then a shortage of liquor might happen.

After Zhao Hai took out his liquor, Dwarf women immediately took them and served the liquor on the various tables present. Looking at how these Dwarf women were carrying two bags of liquor quite casually, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. It seem like even the women of the Dwarf race contained astonishing strength. They can certainly take up weapons and fight as soldiers. Such a race cannot be underestimated.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t given enough time to dwell on his thoughts. Even if the dishes were already served, nobody ate even a single thing. All of them were holding their wine cups as they looked at the direction of Billy.

Billy stood up and raised his glass as he said, “Today is a good day for our Dwarf Race. In nearly 300 years, we haven’t managed to invite a new Foreign Elder. Mister Zhao Hai accepting to be our Foreign Elder is a huge honor to our race. Together, let’s give a toast to Mister Zhao Hai!”

All the Dwarves stood as they held their wine glasses up and loudly said, “To Elder Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting this reception. He also discovered a difference between the Dwarves and the Beastmen. In the Herculean Bull Tribe, announcing him being a Foreign Prince was very straightforward. After drinking three glasses, everything was over.

But for the Dwarves, they held a lot of terminologies in their announcements. They seem to say that they invite someone to be their Foreign Elder. It wasn’t an appointment or anything of the sort, it was very polite.

Zhao Hai raised his wine as well as he returned the gesture, “Becoming a Foreign Elder of the Dwarf Race is a huge honor for this Zhao Hai. I will certainly serve the Dwarves well!” Then he lifted his cup and drank all of the liquor in one go!

Then without any words left to say, Billy and the other Dwarves shouted, “Cheers!” Then they downed their liquor as well.

After drinking one cup, Billy poured himself a second cup as he lifted it again and said, “This second cup is my respects for Mister Juno. Mister Juno has been my friend for a long time. Even if he hadn’t help us Dwarves greatly these past years, he brought us Mister Zhao Hai. To express our gratitude, I want to dedicate this second cup to Mister Juno. He is a genuine friend to our Dwarf Race!”

The other Dwarves, who had also refilled their cups, also said, “To Mister Juno!”

Juno hastily lifted his glass and replied, “The Hurricane Family shall always be a friend to the Dwarves, Cheers!” Then the place became busy as the people downed their wine glasses.

After drinking this liquor, Billy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “You can offer this third cup. After that, all the formalities will be done.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and then he lifted his wine class and said, “I want to thank Mister Juno for bringing me here. I also thank my Dwarf brothers for inviting me to be your Foreign Elder. This Zhao Hai wants to share this cup with all of you, cheers!” Then he finished the wine in his cup.

Since the other Dwarves were aware of the ceremony, they didn’t sit down after the second cup. So after they heard Zhao Hai’s toast, they also cheered loudly before they sat down and indulged on the dishes on their tables.

After the people sat down, only then did Zhao Hai discover that the Dwarves had drank three full glasses of wine. Although their glasses aren’t very big, the liquor that they drank was still of a higher degree than normal. One should know that if one survives drinking just one glass of this liquor, one’s capacity was already deemed to be not bad.

This fact made Zhao Hai figuratively perspire. These Dwarves are truly huge drunkards, Zhao Hai was now doubting whether he can supply them with enough liquor. But on the positive side, the dishes that these Dwarves made tasted very good.

The meal went down in a stellar manner, a lot of Dwarves happily ate and drank. And after the banquet finished, Zhao Hai and the others immediately returned to their own room.

After returning to their room, Zhao Hai immediately drank a cup of Spatial Water. Due to the upgrade, the Spatial water had become much more effective in detoxification. So Zhao Hai’s drunkenness was almost instantly cured.

Laura and the others drank a cup as well. Then after the group flashed to the Space’s villa, Zhao Hai told them about the prophecy of the Dwarves.

Laura and the others didn’t make any noise as Zhao Hai talked to them. Only after the story did Laura comment, “I think that the probability of Brother Hai being the person in the prophecy is very high. Brother Hai already recognized the Divine Artifact, we still don’t know about the Tree of Life. Of the Five Forbidden Lands, the Carrion Swamp is already under our control. If we analyze this disaster, then it might very well be related to the Divine Realm. What I think Brother Hai should do right now is to solve the five Forbidden Lands first, that wouldn’t be very difficult, given our current prowess. If Brother Hai unites the five lands, then Brother Hai would take the seat of King of all as stated in the prophecy.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly and say, “I actually prefer all of this to not happen. But from what I can see, it seems like this matter would be inevitable. Alright, no need to think about these for now. In any case, we still need to prepare everything. In the following days, we’ll trade our goods with the Dwarves before we leave for Golden Island. After that, we can then head to the prairie and see the Beastmen’s Divine Artifact while Patriarch Billy collects news about the Elves. If we fix the other two Divine Artifacts, then we can have a sort of guarantee for the future.”

Laura nodded, “I agree. Our opponent will be God-ranked experts. These three Artifacts also have some understanding of the Divine Realm. So we can prepare for the time when the God’s would come.”

Megan nodded as well, “They’re Gods after all, they’re not people to be underestimated. Since those three Artifacts have battled Gods in the past, then they would prove to be useful for our cause.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “If we fix those three Artifacts, then we can immediately go to the other four forbidden areas and conquer them. If there are good things there, then we might even upgrade the Space.”

At this time, Lizzy knit her eyebrows as she said, “Big Brother Hai, can we tell this matter to father? Wouldn’t it be better if he knew about this?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It’s currently not the time to do that. If we tell father-in-law now, then it would be possible for other people to know about it. If the Radiant Church finds out, then we would be in big trouble.”

Chapter 582: Engraved Ark’s Background

Lizzy nodded, she knew that what Zhao Hai said was true. From the ancient times to the present days, there weren’t any secrets that an Emperor can keep for themselves. Therefore, talking to the Emperor right now wouldn’t be a very good idea.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “It seems like we don’t have anything else to do right now. In the meantime, let’s head back to Iron Mountain Fort and let Grandpa Green and Grandma Merine be 9th ranks first. After that we can let Grandpa Kun, Rockhead, Blockhead, Shun, and Shue take turns.”

Laura nodded but said, “No need to be anxious. After all, we still have a large number of 9th ranks in the Space. Right, Brother Hai, I think we should check up on the Processing Machine and see if it can make potions that can make 9th ranks into God-ranked experts. Wouldn’t it be great for us if that is possible?”

Zhao Hai stared, he had forgotten about this point. He immediately said, “I had Cai’er look over it yesterday. Cai’er, how was it?”

Just after Zhao Hai’s voice fell, Cai’er immediately appeared in front of Zhai Hai. She faintly smiled and said, “Young Master, rest assured, I already planted some plants that can make God-ranked experts in the Farming Ground. However, there are still some other plants that cannot be grown. But when the Space reaches level 55, all of those can be cultivated. Since the Space is still level 52, I can only put aside the seeds of those plants. When time comes, I shall immediately cultivate them. The Young Master doesn’t need to worry too much about it.”

Upon hearing Cai’er, Zhao Hai laughed and nodded, “Good, Cai’er. Having you really relieves me of some worries”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Thank you, Young Master. Also, Young Master, I can now eat. Please bring me some good food next time.”

Zhao Hai laughed and replied, “That’s not a problem. Just tell me what you’d like to eat, your Young Master wouldn’t treat you unjustly. But isn’t your main body a plant? Isn’t it just fine if you don’t eat?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “I get envious of people sometimes. Even if I don’t need to eat, it doesn’t mean that I can’t.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright. Rest assured, I’ll certainly bring you some food next time. Right, I think there are still a lot of delicious food in the warehouse. You can eat some snacks from there in the meantime” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as he withdrew some snacks from the warehouse and gave them to Cai’er.

Although Cai’er was the Space’s manager, she wasn’t able to touch the Warehouse, that place was under the sole control of Zhao Hai. She doesn’t have the authority to access it.

Seeing these things that she hadn’t ate before, Cai’er began to munch on the snacks like a happy little child. Laura and the others smiled, they seem to see Cai’er’s actions quite cute.

Seeing Cai’er happily eating, Zhao Hai became happy as well. He turned his attention away from Cai’er as he faced Laura and said, “It seems like the Space needs to reach level 55 as soon as possible. Otherwise, we would be on a disadvantage in the war against the Gods.”

Laura gave a sigh and said, “We’re already at quite a great position. If we go to the Elven Forest as well as the other Forbidden Areas, then wouldn’t we be able to reach that level by then?”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled, he didn’t think that it would be that smooth. One must know that the higher the Space’s level was, the harder the next step would be. Now that the Space had reached level 52, levelling up to 55 would be very difficult.

This time, he used God’s Blood, but it only upgraded the Space by three levels. Where could be find something much stronger than God’s Blood in the future?

But at the very least, they now have a target, which was good. Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he turned to Laura and said, “Let’s go to the backgrounds and explore them. After all, we still haven’t seen them yet.”

Laura and the others nodded. They also wanted to see the contents of those backgrounds. The pressure has been great to them recently, they needed a short time to relax themselves in some new scenery.

Especially now, after knowing about the matters with the Divine Realm. They felt that their nerves were already quite stretched out to the point of collapse.

The group played around inside the backgrounds for quite some time. They also found the houses inside those backgrounds and rested inside. The rooms were very good, it had quite the modern touch to it, which made Zhao Hai and the others enjoy their stay.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others appeared inside the room in the mountain that Billy had prepared for them. Just as they came out, a Dwarf arrived and immediately bowed to Zhao Hai’s door and said, “Elder, the Patriarch is inviting you over to the Dining Hall for a meal.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Thanks” Then the Dwarf smiled before he turned around to leave, looking somewhat shy. Zhao Hai smiled faintly before leading Laura and the others towards the Dining Hall.

Besides Billy and Juno, there were no other people present in hall.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this and just sat with Billy and Juno. Laura and the others sat on another table as Dwarf women served them their meals before leaving.

After Zhao Hai had sat down, Juno gave a smile and said, “How are you feeling? You’ve drank the same amount of liquor as the Dwarves yesterday.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and replied, “Fortunately, we managed to recover after taking a good night’s sleep. But I don’t think I can drink that much anymore.”

Juno and Billy chuckled, Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Yesterday, I’ve sent some Dwarves to get plants and Magic Beasts for you. We’ve also included some special ores in the lot. I hope that those things would be useful to you. We’ve made a pile of those things outside. You can take them away later. Will you be leaving after that?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “After getting those things, I’m planning to leave and head to the Prairie hoping to see the Beast God’s Spear. Right, Patriarch, you should keep a warehouse open for me. I’ll be supplying you milk wine every month, it’s total quantity wouldn’t be less than 1 million jin. When that time comes, I’ll be trading them for some ironwares that I would list on a letter along with the milk wine delivery. You can put those things in the warehouse. It’ll make it possible for me to come here and fetch them regularly.”

Billy nodded and said, “Alright, this is not a problem. I’ll keep a warehouse free just for you. At the same time, I won’t be telling your secrets to anyone, you can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. I also still need a period of time to research that God’s Blood. If we succeed, we would be able to gain a method to make 9th ranks into God-ranked experts. So when the Gods come, we won’t be in a huge disadvantage.”

Billy knit his brows as he replied, “I’m afraid that this wouldn’t be easy. Moreover, after people in the continent reaches 9th rank, they would immediately need to ascend to the Divine Realm, otherwise they would receive Divine Punishment. If we make God-ranked experts, then I’m afraid we won’t get much use of them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I also know about this. But even if we don’t have God-ranked experts, at the very least, we can still have a lot of 9th ranks. We shouldn’t forget that it’s already been tens of thousands of years before the war with the Gods. But in these tens of thousands of years, the technology in the continent haven’t progressed by a lot. However, I think that it would be impossible for the Divine Realm to be unable to come up with new things. It might be possible for them to create a process to weaken the barrier to the Ark Continent. If they send an army to attack, our own forces wouldn’t be able to resist.”

Billy sighed and said, “Not only the Gods, I’m also quite worried about the Demons. The God’s might take a long time before coming. However, the Demons have also been taking their time. I heard that the Five Forbidden Areas were somewhat related to the Demon Realm. If you head to the Five Forbidden Areas, make sure to check for signs of the Demons. Right, since you have explored the Carrion Swamp, is the situation under control over there?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, that place is already under control. From what I had heard for Sir Artifact Spirit, the war with the Divine Realm had caused the barrier to weaken, allowing the Demons entry to the Ark Continent. However, I cannot see any connection to the Demon Realm at this time. So you don’t need to worry about it.”

Juno then felt a connection as he said, “Right, why do I think that the Engraved Ark is connected to the Demon Realm? They don’t seem to act like the Radiant Church who wants to control the continent. On the other hand, it seems like they are hell bent on destroying it. Isn’t this the main goal of the Demons?”

Zhao Hai stared, he hadn’t thought about this possibility. But now that Juno had said it, the Engraved Ark’s purpose of destroying the continent’s races really did seems like it connects to the goals of the Demons.

Gods are different to Demons. Although the Gods were at war with the other races, they still select which of them to deal with while they sided with the Humans. If Humans become Gods, then it would give them much more fighting prowess. The Gods might even make the Ark Continent a place where they can produce a lot of God-ranked experts.[1]

But Demons were different, what they want was the Ark Continent. From what was heard from Cai’er, the environment in the Demon Realm was very bad, so they had been drooling at the sight of the Ark Continent. They held zero regard towards the people living in it, so it wouldn’t be an issue for them to eradicate the entire population. Unlike the Gods, where they want to hold monopoly over the population, the Demons wanted to completely erase it.

Seeing Zhao Hai staying quiet, Juno knew that there might still be some things that Zhao Hai had kept secret from them. Juno and Billy didn’t disturb Zhao Hai’s thoughts, they stayed quiet and let Zhao Hai ruminate over his ideas.

After thinking about this point for some time, Zhao Hai was convinced that the Engraved Ark had something to do with the Demon Race. But if it this was really the case, then the troubles for the Ark Continent had now been increased.

Seeing that Zhao Hai had recovered, Billy immediately said, “What happened? Did you think of something?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I did just think of something, I’m afraid that the Engraved Ark might have a relationship with the Demons. When I investigated the Carrion Swamp in the past, I had discovered some ancient records detailing the matters of the Demon Race. When the barrier was damaged, people of the Ark Continent came to know of the existence of the Demon Realm while at the same time, the Demons were also made aware of the Ark Continent. It has been known that the Demon Realm is a very hard place to live in. For the Demons, the Ark Continent would seem like Heaven. It had become their goal to live in here, it become a must for them to occupy the continent. Because of that, the Demons held no interest in the beings that are currently living here. It wouldn’t be a problem for them if everyone here were to be eliminated. This is very much like the motives of the Engraved Ark. Therefore, I’ve felt a very high probability of the Engraved Ark having contact with the Demon Race.”

When Juno and Billy heard Zhao Hai’s speculations, their faces couldn’t help but turn ugly. Juno’s earlier inquiry was only a shallow prediction, he wasn’t confident in it being true. However, after hearing Zhao Hai, he came to know that this matter was highly possible.

Billy knit his brows and said, “That can’t be right. Why would the Engraved Ark help the Demons? All of the people in the continent hated the Demons.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and answered, “Don’t forget how greedy people can get. They would do anything in order to fulfill their ambitions. If the Radiant Church can brainwash people using religion. Then who can say that the Demons can’t do the same? There is nothing strange about the existence of Engraved Ark.”

Juno’s face became uglier. Others might not know, but he was very clear about how good the Radiant Church was in brainwashing people. His family had suffered because of this aspect. If the Radiant Church didn’t have effective methods of brainwashing, then they wouldn’t have grown this fast. If the Engraved Ark was really a religion set up by the Demons, then Zhao Hai’s speculation might as well be true.

Billy nodded and said, “This Demon Race’s secrecy is much deeper than the Radiant Church. It seems like we need to me more cautious of them.”

Zhao Hai actually shook his head, “Not necessarily. The reason why the Radiant Church had resorted to their present actions was because of me continually interfering with their plans. Because of them being in the light, they had more room for development. On the other hand, the Engraved Ark being very secretive only meant that they have a lack of members. If this is the case, then the threat of the Radiant Church should be bigger.”

Juno coldly snorted as he said, “No matter which one, both of them are very difficult to deal with. Because of Little Hai’s actions, the Radiant Church has been pushed back while the Engraved Ark has always been living in the shadows. This is a very bad situation. It may be possible for them to collaborate in dealing with Little Hai, so you need to be careful.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but force a smile as he said, “This is really ironic. On one side are Gods, and on the other are Demons. If they join forces to deal with us, then we’re done for.”

* * *

From what I can understand, it seems like the natives of the Divine Realm were also Humans. Need to read far ahead to make sure, I’ll update it when I get there.

Chapter 583: Raising One Level

Zhao Hai has been cursing people a lot recently. He felt very incensed, Gods, Demons, two people who are on the opposite spectrum were pining to occupy the Ark Continent. They might even cooperate in order to deal with its inhabitants. How unfortunate was this situation? How could he be the male lead in this story!!

When Juno heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but coldly snort, “Little Hai, you don’t need to think that the people of the Divine Realm are good. Although a lot of Humans there are from the continent, from what Iron Hammer said, most of its inhabitants are native. Therefore, we don’t need to consider them as people from the Ark Continent.”

Billy snorted as well, “These fellows really cannot be considered to be good. Little Hai, I hope you can develop ways to be God-ranked experts as soon as possible. Perhaps when that time comes, we would feel a lot better when outsiders decide to visit.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, he knew that what Billy and Juno said was right. The God-ranked experts in the Divine Realm cannot be considered to be one of them.

Juno then looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Alright, let’s not talk about these anymore. Let’s eat. After the meal, Little Hai can get his goods then we’ll take our leave.”

Billy turned to Juno and said, “What? You’re already leaving? I thought that you would need to stay for a few days?”

Juno forced a smile and said, “Forget it. I’ve already been away for too long. Also, I’ve managed to know a lot of things here. The things that are left for me to handle should be piled up right now.”

Billy nodded, “Alright. Dealing with the invaders is the most important thing, I won’t be holding you back. Let’s eat and then let Little Hai get his goods. At the same time, I’ll also be handing over a letter to be given to the Beast King. If Little Hai gives that to the Beast King, the probability of him seeing the Beast God’s Spear should increase.”

Zhao Hai understood what Billy was trying to do. Although Zhao Hai’s standing in the Prairie was already high, he was still a human that Beastmen wouldn’t generally trust, especially with the matter of their Beast God’s Spear. But if he had a letter from the Dwarves, in addition to the Elder’s command token, everything should go by smoothly.

The three didn’t waste a single breath. After having their meal, they immediately proceeded to go outside. When Zhao Hai saw the display, he couldn’t help but stare blankly at it. On the ground were more than a hundred types of things. It included about 30 species of unique Magic Beasts, more than 50 types of plants, and more than a dozen kinds of ores. These ores were very rare in the continent, they might not have even seen the light of day before.

However, these nuances aren’t important. What was important were the alive plants and animals. For Zhao Hai these things were too useful.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite as he immediately received everything into the Space. A prompt was then heard, most of them about the plants and animals. But around the end, the ores were addressed as well. The ores were indeed rare and special. But because the quantity was too little, it would be impossible for them to be like Pure Iron, able to form their own lode inside the Space. However, the Space informed Zhao Hai that when those ores grow in a few years, each one of them would develop their own vein inside.

Because of the Space’s recent upgrades, it had become possible for the ores to grow. In the past, if the amount of ore was this low, then it would be impossible for them to increase. For Zhao Hai, this development was very good news.

But what made Zhao Hai very surprised was the fact that all of these things were able to increase the Space’s level by one. This made Zhao Hai gawk.

With his understanding of the Space, it was impossible for these things to make it increase by one level. The current development truly gave him a surprise.

However, after a moment of thinking, Zhao Hai had found the reason why this was such. It was possible that after the God’s Blood had been absorbed by the Space, increasing its level by three, there were still some energy left behind but was unable to raise the Space’s level. The recent pile was just the final push needed by the Space in order to level up.

Zhao Hai didn’t make a big deal out of it. Although the Space had increased by a level, he still needed two levels for something significant to happen. These two levels wouldn’t be very easy to get. He just hopes that the Beastmen had good things for him.

After receiving these things, Zhao Hai and the others immediately went to the empty warehouse that has been prepared by the Dwarves beforehand. Actually, this warehouse was just a very huge cavern inside the mountain range. Moreover, this cavern was completely unused, so there won’t be any fear of any Dwarves stealing stuff that was inside.

When Zhao Hai was finished inspecting the warehouse, the things that he needed to do in the Dwarf Mountains was now almost finished. Arranging Dwarves for the Black Wasteland would still need some time, it was already quite good that Billy was working on it.

Upon finishing these two matters, the group immediately returned to Billy’s office. When they sat down, Billy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I’ve already set up some ironwares for you to bring, but it needs a day to collect. Are you alright with getting them tomorrow?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment, in any case he wasn’t really anxious in leaving, he nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll wait until tomorrow before we leave.”

Billy nodded, then he turned to his workplace and started to write a letter. Zhao Hai knew that Billy was writing the letter that was to be given to the Beast King, so he didn’t disturb him. Instead, he turned to Juno and whispered, “Patriarch Juno, after we leave tomorrow, I can only drop you off in your territory before heading to Golden Island. I still need to prepare for my visit to the Prairie, I’m afraid I won’t be able to stay for long.”

Juno understood, he nodded and said, “That’s not a problem. Dealing with this matter is much more important. After all, we still have a lot of time in our hands in the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Certainly there’ll be a chance. But there is one thing I’ll need your help with. Since my territory is far from the Ocean Waves Dynasty, I wouldn’t have a huge opportunity to observe it. It’s possible for the Dynasty to have already fallen to the Radiant Church’s hands. I’ll have to trouble you to keep your eyes on them.”

Juno smiled and said, “No problem. We’ll handle this matter with care. If we have any information, we’ll pass it to Billy and have him place the letter along with the goods in the warehouse. This way, news arrives to you much quicker.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. About the Gods and the Divine Realm’s matter, please refrain from telling anyone about it. We cannot afford to make a stir if this gets spread out. This would only bring us harm.”

Juno nodded, “Rest assured, I understand the implications. I won’t tell anyone about it. Right, I’m planning to send some people over to Golden Island to do business, can you see to it that they are settled properly?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “That’s not an issue. I’ll go inform the island’s manager about this later. When your people arrive at the island, just tell the people in charge that you’re the Hurricane Family. They shall help you get settled in.”

Juno patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Thank you, Little Hai.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You’re too polite. We’re now allies, so you’re absolutely welcome in my territory. Besides the people of my Buda Clan, only you and Patriarch Billy knew about my secret, even my father-in-law doesn’t now. You should also keep that secret from the others.”

Juno gave a smile and said, “Rest assured, I’m not that neglectful. But I really didn’t expect that the poisonous fog in the Black Wasteland was your doing. Moreover, that poisonous gas can actually harm 9th ranks. No wonder nobody discovered your roots. With that place as a den, nobody would be able to guess it.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s no other way. In the past, our Buda Clan was still very weak. If people found out that we’re still in the Black Wasteland, they might go and deal with us immediately. And although we have the strength right now, I still don’t want to restrict my freedom. There are too many greedy people in the continent. If they came to know the situation of my Buda Clan, then they might develop ideas and might turn their attention away from the Radiant Church. That would bring me a lot of troubles.”

Juno smiled bitterly, he knew that what Zhao Hai said was true. Now that the matter with the Divine Realm must be kept in secret, the only thing that can shift people’s attention was the news that the Buda Clan was occupying the entirety of the Black Wasteland, and had made it possible to be cultivated. This news would definitely would cause a huge reaction. In the end, there would be a lot of eyes that would be turned towards the Buda Clan.

The area of the Black Wasteland was too big, and it held a large amount of now arable land. This land of pure wealth would surely cause people to develop greedy thoughts.

The reason why people of the continent were suppressing the Radiant Church was because the church had threatened their rule, posing a threat to their interests. If a huge piece of meat such as the wasteland suddenly appears in the continent, people would take their attention off of the Radiant Church, and then shift towards the Buda Clan.

While they were talking, Billy had already finished writing the letter. He didn’t use paper for it, but instead processed skin of the Iron Beast. The Iron Beast had a lot of uses aside from it being a good material for leather armor. Because of this, the significance of the Iron Beast to the Dwarves was just like what the Argali was to the Beastmen.

Billy rolled up the beastskin and then sealed it. He handed the letter over to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, take this letter to the Beast King. He should be able to recognize that the seal is from our Dwarf Race. I wrote everything about the Divine Artifacts here. I believe that after reading the letter, he should be able to agree to your request.”

Zhao Hai received the letter and nodded, “Alright, I also think that he would agree. My relationship with him is very good, there shouldn’t be any more problems.”

Chapter 584: Also Wants to Marry?

Zhao Hai was currently standing on the Haven’s bow with Juno. Although they look like they were appreciating the scene of Iron Warhorse River, their minds were on something completely different.

The didn’t have the mood to enjoy the scenery. The Gods and the Demons had given them enormous pressure. It was like they had mountains stacked on their shoulders, making it hard for them to breath.

Two days had already passed from the time that they had left the Dwarf Mountains. In the two days that they were hurrying along, even if they already have a plan to deal with the Gods, they still thought of the matter with a heavy heart.

After some time, Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Since the Dwarves had already started to prepare for war, it seems like the Black Wasteland would need to do the same.”

Juno sighed as well as he said, “Not only you, we’ll be preparing as well. What a pity, our Hurricane Family’s domain is too small. Moreover, we don’t have any good produce in it. Preparing for the future would be quite a problem.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Grandpa Juno doesn’t need to worry. As long as you keep your eyes on the Radiant Church, it’s already enough of an effort.”

Juno sighed, “That’s the only thing that we could do. We’ll have to pass the other matters on to you. Also, Billy needs to convince the Elves to be our allies, otherwise, it would be troublesome.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’ll also head to the Prairie and talk to the Beastmen. I hope that they can agree based on my merit. Right, let’s not talk about this anymore. Grandpa Juno, what business are you preparing to do in Golden Island?”

Juno smiled bitterly and said, “The usual, basic goods. Our Hurricane Family hasn’t done much business all these years, so we really don’t know anything else.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “How about this. If you really want to do business in Golden Island, you can approach the administrator there. His name is Kun, he’s my wife Laura’s Grandpa. I’ll tell Grandpa Kun to help you set up a business that can turn a profit.”

Juno smiled and said, “Thank you. Our people really aren’t very suitable for business. In the younger generation, the only one with an eye for business is Kristen. When we send people to Golden Island, she’ll be placed in charge.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly inside without changing his outside expression, he just nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll help them get settled in. However, they might not regularly see me in the island. I’m mostly on other places all year round. If they need anything, they can just ask Grandpa Kun for help.”

Juno didn’t say anything but just nodded. He knew that Zhao Hai had already guessed his intentions. Juno wanted to send Kristen to Golden Island in hopes that she can marry Zhao Hai.

If Juno wasn’t aware of the matter with the Divine Realm, then it would be impossible for him to have such an idea. After all, the Hurricane Family doesn’t seek profit, so it wouldn’t be in their best interests to be married to the Buda Clan.

But now that he knew about the Gods, he couldn’t help but develop this plan. From what he had felt from Zhao Hai, Juno can faintly sense the might of the Buda Clan. Getting good relationships with the Buda Clan would immensely aid the Hurricane Family in the future.

Moreover, Juno somewhat believed the prophecy of the Dwarves that Billy had told him. If that was indeed true, then Zhao Hai would become the saviour of the entire continent. If he didn’t use this early opportunity to establish a connection with Zhao Hai, then he wasn’t worthy of being the Patriarch of the Hurricane Family.

Although the Hurricane Family wasn’t known for its ambition, no Great Clan can completely survive without it. The reason the Hurricane Family was able to survive was because they had maintained their current status. In the Buddha Empire, the Hurricane Family wasn’t the biggest Clan nor was it the smallest. Their status in the empire was just average, attracting the goodwill of the Imperial Clan as well as the other Nobles. Their unambitious ways made it possible for them to maintain their status and interests.

However, with the looming threat of the Divine Realm, the situation had changed. If people from the Divine Realm came, the continent would certainly fall into chaos. In this case, rankings and status would be useless, only strength can decide everything.

Because he clearly knew about this point, Juno wanted to arrange Kristen to marry Zhao Hai. Having Kristen do business in Golden Island was the first step.

But Juno a wise old person. He already saw the relationship between Zhao Hai and his wives. And seeing that Zhao Hai’s wives were already very attractive, Juno didn’t directly offer Zhao Hai the marriage. He wanted to make Kristen go to Golden Island first to do business and maybe have a few interactions with Zhao Hai. Juno hopes that the two might develop feelings for each other in the near future.

Zhao Hai telling Juno that he wasn’t in the island most of the time was akin to informing Juno that he was aware of his plan. Zhao Hai wanted to express that there was almost no chance of any marriage happening. But although Juno got Zhao Hai’s message, he still wanted to give it a try.

Zhao Hai looked at Juno’s perseverance and sighed. He had already lived for quite some time in the Ark Continent, so he now understood the thoughts of the people living here. Because of this, he found Juno’s decision to be understandable. But Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on marrying Kristen.

Therefore, he told Juno that he cannot stay in Golden Island for most of the year. So even if he were to get in contact with Kristen, there wouldn’t be a lot of chances to do so.

After another day of sailing, Zhao Hai and the others had finally arrived at the Hurricane Family’s port. The reason why they were able to come back quickly was because they were travelling downstream. Therefore, the ship’s speed was very quick.

Zhao Hai didn’t stay for long, a short time after Juno disembarked, he immediately set sail. And after the ship has sailed, he immediately went to the Space along with Laura and the others. It was time to increase their ranks.

After arriving at the Space, Zhao Hai first went to Iron Mountain Fort to bring Green and Merine over. Then he went to Golden Island to call Kun, Blockhead, and Rockhead. Karen joined the group as well.

Green and the others had no idea why Zhao Hai took all of them to the Space. After the group had sat in the villa, Zhao Hai immediately informed them about the information that he had acquired while he was with the Dwarves. The Divine Realm, the Radiant Church, the Engraved Ark, all of it was told to the others.

Quite some time after they were shocked by the news, Green looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, do you mean that the Radiant Church was tasked by the Divine Realm to control the continent? And the Engraved Ark was tasked by the Demon Realm to destroy it?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, it seems like so. Although I’m not completely sure that the Radiant Church wanted to control the whole continent, we are certain that their intentions aren’t good. If they can control the continent, then they would definitely enslave everyone in it.”

Kun’s face sank as he said, “This matter is too troublesome. Do you have any plans for it?’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then told them about the God’s Blood as well as the Space levelling up. After Zhao Hai ended his report, Green and the others immediately expressed their happiness. For them this was really good news.

Green laughed and said, “This is fantastic! I’ve waited for this day! Hahaha. I must become a 9th rank expert immediately.”

The others were happy as well, everyone except Karen. He seems to not care about it, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, give me more blueprints. I’ve discovered how marvelous those ideas were just in my small time researching them. Although those didn’t have any Magic Formations, they can actually mimic a formation’s effects. I’m preparing to combine those with Magic Formations, as long as it succeeds, then it might lead to something that can change the continent.”

Zhao Hai was simply speechless about this madman father-in-law of his. When others heard that they can become 9th ranks, they immediately became happy. It was only Karen that didn’t care about it and instead only asked for more blueprints.

When she heard what her father just said, Laura couldn’t bear it as she said, “Father, leave the matter of the blueprints to another time. You can now be a 9th rank expert, aren’t you happy?”

Karen nodded and said, “Of course I’m happy. However, I’m much more interested in Little Hai’s blueprints. If we can use Magic along with those machines, we can make a lot of extraordinary things. We can make machines that do our work for us, we can make carriages that can run by themselves, we can use a new type of energy to power our lamps. These things can immensely help the entire continent’s living conditions.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly at Karen, he really underestimated this father-in-law of his. Zhao Hai didn’t expect Karen to come up with these things, it was surprising.

After some time, Zhao Hai recovered as he looked at Karen and said, “Father-in-law, let’s deal with being a 9th rank first. If you become a 9th rank, your lifespan would be lengthened. Then, you would have more time to do research. What do you think?”

When Karen heard Zhao Hai, he thought about it for a moment before he nodded and said, “Alright, let’s deal with that matter first. But if I become 9th rank, you better give me those blueprints.”

Zhao Hai helplessly nodded, he was really speechless about Karen’s ideas. He replied, “Father-in-law can use the Blood Pond in order to become a 9th rank now. Grandpa Green, Grandpa Merine, Grandpa Kun, Blockhead, and Rockhead, can you wait for a day or two? We need to decide which one goes first. People still need to cultivate for some days to become 9th rank. If all of you do it at the same time, nobody would be left to manage Iron Mountain Fort and Golden Island. That wouldn’t be good.”

Chapter 585: Invited by His Majesty

Green nodded and said, “Alright, Iron Mountain Fort and Golden Island needs to be taken care of. Otherwise, things would go chaotic. I think we need to do it in batches. We’ll have Rockead and Blockhead go first. Then when they’re done, we can have them replace Brother Kun. Then after Brother Kun, Blockhead and Rockhead can go to Iron Mountain Fort in order to replace me and Merine. Shun and Shue can cultivate immediately.”

Nobody disagreed with Green’s proposal. In any case, the Space had now levelled up, it doesn’t matter to them if they delay being 9th rank for a couple of days.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, we’ll do it just as what Grandpa Green said. Also, after you go back to Iron Mountain Fort, do find some loyal slaves, and then teach them cultivation. Now that the Spatial Water can increase practice speed, we won’t need to worry about making experts. Select some people from the Giant-horned bulls as well. If we have members from their tribe get strong, then it’ll be good for us.”

The way Beastmen and Humans cultivate is very different. For Beastmen to cultivate successfully, they would need a strong soul beast to be their partner. And with the Space’s recent upgrade, a lot of magic beasts had now become high-grade. So if the Giant-horned Bulls used Space-grown bulls, they would certainly rank up easily.

Green nodded and said, “Alright. Actually, there were already people who had entered my eyes. I’ve known slaves, about 100 of them, that would fit your description. They’ve now become commoners, and are very loyal to our clan. I’ll have them be the first batch to be cultivated.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good, then I’ll leave this matter to Grandpa’s judgement. Right, everyone, let’s take a look at some of the backgrounds in the Space. The sceneries are quite good.”

Green and the other complied, then Zhao Hai took them to the newly obtained backgrounds. The views on those places were indeed very good.

After having looked at the ten backgrounds, Zhao Hai and the others returned to the villa. Then Zhao Hai took out some water from the Blood Pond for Laura and the others to drink. Green, Merine, and Kun, on the other hand, left the Space.

Laura and the others were quite nervous. The effects of the Blood Pond water wasn’t like Zhao Hai’s Space, promoting him instantly to 9th rank. After drinking the water, they still need to cultivate in order to rank up.

When Laura and the others drank the Blood Pond water, the immediately felt the intensity of the energy that was present inside. They felt their entire bodies heat up as their Battle Qi became agitated. For them, it felt like their bodies had been broken down.

They felt that their skin was about to be blown away. It seems like their bodies cannot handle the enormous energy that was just ingested.

Laura and the others didn’t dare to let this go on, so they immediately used their own cultivation methods to practice. But since Meg was a Mage, the energy didn’t wander around her body as it immediately went straight to her head. Meg felt an influx of pressure in her mind, making her almost lose her consciousness. However, Meg knew that she couldn’t faint at this time, therefore she endured.

Meg gave it her all in order to stay sober. At the same time, she also called upon the elemental laws and slowly digested the energy that was present.

The other people were practically doing the same thing. Seeing that there seems to be no accident, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh in relief. He knew that the most dangerous time was the moment the water was ingested.

Now, although their expressions were still in pain, it had slowly turned into calmness. Seeing them going stable, Zhao Hai smiled and then went out of the Space to return to the Haven.

The Haven was still cruising along Iron Warhorse River, it still hasn’t entered the sea. Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about this as he just enjoyed the scene on the two banks of the river. This Iron Warhorse River was indeed worthy of being called the most important river of the Buddha Empire. Whether it be a city or a village, all of them had piers connecting to the river. At the same time, ships were constantly flowing through it, the scene was extremely lively.

While looking at these people, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. Ignorance is really bliss. These average people didn’t need to worry so much. They may get sad, but they can just recover in just a short time. It was impossible for them to have such huge burdens. But this was part of life, Zhao Hai has his advantages and troubles, while the commoners had their own matters as well.

In the past, back on Earth, Zhao Hai couldn’t understand how people from higher statures in life would get into drug addiction, and some even commited suicide. Zhao Hai couldn’t fathom why those people could end up in such a state. Was the pressure on them really that great?

But after arriving at the Ark Continent, especially after knowing about the Divine Realm, Zhao Hai came to understand how much pressure and stress people from high status can have.

This pressure felt like a mountain constantly crashing into your body. Ever since he got the information, Zhao Hai had always felt that his nerves were constantly being stretched out. Zhao Hai was afraid that he might snap one of these days.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh once again. He looked at the people at both banks and couldn’t help but feel envy. Zhao Hai had always wanted a simple life, but it seems like that life was getting farther and farther away from him.

At this time, the Haven had reached a region near a big city. However, Zhao Hai didn’t plan to stop, he knew that after this city, it would only take two more days before they can reach the sea. Therefore, Zhao Hai planned to go through the river as fast as possible.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect there to be an iron chain lock in front of him. It seems like its main purpose was to block the Haven from passing.

Zhao Hai gawked, he didn’t say anything and just had the undead stop the ship. He went to the ship’s bow and then looked at the blockade.

On both sides of the iron chain lock were two five masted battleships. The emblems on the two battleships emanated a faint yellow tint and had the image of a heavily armored soldier.

Zhao Hai was very familiar with this emblem, this was the Buddha Empire’s Imperial Badge! The people who were blockading the river was actually the Empire’s navy!

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t know what the other party wanted. But he didn’t worry much about it, so he just stayed put and waited for the other party to make the move.

Just as expected, just as the Haven came to a full stop, a person suddenly appeared on one of the two ships. Behind him were people who were wearing Heavy Armor as well as people with Magic Robes. After appearing on the ship, the man said, “Is this the Buda Clan’s Patriarch Zhao Hai’s ship?”

Zhao Hai looked at the other ship and replied, “This is Zhao Hai. May I know why you are blocking the river?”

The man replied and said, “I’ve seen Mister Zhao Hai. I am the Buddha Empire’s Vice Admiral Ironwood. His majesty is inviting Mister Zhao Hai over to the capital. We’ll have to apologize for causing mister any trouble.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he knit his brows. He knew that he has to go, otherwise, he wouldn’t be giving the Buddha Empire any face. That action would definitely offend the Empire, so after thinking for a moment, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll have to ask the Vice Admiral to lead the way. I’ll have my ship follow you afterwards.”

Ironwood’s voice was heard, “Then we’ll be escorting mister.” After that, they released the chains and slowly hoisted it up. Then the ships turned around and sailed in front of Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai didn’t delay and also followed behind the ships.

Their current location wasn’t very far from the Buddha Empire’s Imperial Capital, Iron Knight City. As long as they take a branching river not far away from here, then it would only take less than a day before they arrive.

Constructing Iron Knight City in such a place was due to the Empire’s first King. When he was struggling, he had met his Iron Warhorse Mount in the exact spot where Iron Knight City was built. Wanting to commemorate his meeting with his mount, the old Emperor decided to establish a city in this place, making it the capital of his Empire. He also made a statue of his mount, erected in the middle of the city’s largest square.

Iron Knight City was placed at the largest branch of Iron Warhorse River. The volume of ships passing through this branch can only be trumped by the main river. There were more than a hundred piers here. With a variety of ships in it, including five-masted ships. There were a lot of people in the place as well, one could say that the city is the busiest hub in the entire Iron Warhorse River.

Zhao Hai stood on the Haven as he looked at the city getting closer and closer. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but force a smile, the Buddha Empire truly had given him good face. The Haven was sandwiched between two five-masted ships. Even if he wanted to escape, he wouldn’t have any avenue to do so.

But Zhao Hai didn’t care much about it. Rosen Empire was the most powerful nation of the continent, and he was the Emperor’s son-in-law while at the same time being the Patriarch of the Buda Clan. He believed that the Buddha Emperor was not planning to do anything bad to him.

The three ships slowly stopped in front of a pier. The undead prepared the springboard as Zhao Hai disembarked from the ship. On one of the two Buddha Empire ships, five people came down. Three of these people had full body armor, while two of them wore magical robes.

After the five disembarked, they immediately went to welcome Zhao Hai. The five arrived in front of Zhao Hai as a robust man in the front gave a bow and said, “Ironwood has seen Patriarch Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai looked at this Ironwood. This fellow easily surpassed two meters, he had a silvery while armor that seems to be made from high purity iron. Zhao Hai felt strange when he remembered that this person was a Vice Admiral. If he wore a full armor, then wouldn’t he have a hard time if he fell to the water?

But Zhao Hai still gave a smile and returned the salute, “I’ve seen Vice Admiral Ironwood. For this Zhao Hai to have a Vice Admiral escort him to the capital should be a capital offense.”

Ironwood quickly replied, “We don’t dare. His Majesty gave us explicit order to treat the Patriarch with hospitality. It’s us who have been disrespectful to Patriarch Zhao Hai. Please do accept our apology.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Vice Admiral didn’t do anything wrong, so there’s no need to ask for forgiveness. I’ll also ask f the Admiral for forgiveness in behalf of my wives. They’re quite busy cultivating inside the ship. I’m afraid that they wouldn’t be able to visit His Majesty together with me.”

Ironwood replied, “The Patriarch doesn’t need to be polite. Since your wives are busy, then we cannot disturb them. The Patriarch can rest assured, I’ll have people standing guard here in order to maintain your ship’s tranquility.:

Zhao Hai gave his gratitude to Ironwood, “I thank the Vice Admiral. I think we should be going, I don’t want to make His Majesty and the others wait for so long.”

Ironwood smiled faintly and said, “We’re just in time. Follow me, Patriarch.” Then he led Zhao Hai to exit the pier. Naturally this pier was used exclusively by Nobles. This was the reason why this place was hardly populated and was very clean.

When Zhao Hai and the others left the pier, they were immediately met by a horse carriage. The carriage was very stylish, it also sported the Imperial Clan’s emblem.

Zhao Hai immediately knew that this carriage wasn’t something that anyone can just ride on. At the very least, the person that can ride this should be a prince.

Sure enough, Ironwood smiled at Zhao Hai and said, “Patriarch, this is His Majesty’s personal carriage. I didn’t expect his Majesty to send his carriage for mister to ride on. It seems like the matter is quite urgent. Patriarch, I’ll have to ask you to please board the carriage.”

Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude before boarding the carriage. Ironwood followed Zha Hai in as well. The inside of the carriage was quite luxurious. Thick beastskin were draped on the chairs, making sitting very soft and comfortable. The temperature inside the carriage was carefully moderated as well. At the same time, one couldn’t feel any shaking inside. It seems like this carriage was very special.

There were also some things inside this carriage that Zhao Hai had found to be familiar, like the magical stove with a kettle. After Ironwood boarded the carriage, he immediately heated the water for them to drink.

Seeing Ironwood’s thick hands handling the drinks very delicately made Zhao Hai feel funny. In fact, Ironwood’s movements were very quick. Before long, the tea was already prepared.

The flavor of this tea was mellow compared to the ones that Zhao Hai had drunk before. Ironwood handed Zhao Hai a cup of it and then said, “To thank mister for coming, let me offer you this cup of golden tea. This is a high-quality good rarely purchased in the continent.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s also the first time that I had drank this type of tea. It’s flavor is also very good. Right, Vice Admiral, if I may inquire, what was the reason for His Majesty deciding to summon me?”

Ironwood smiled and said, “In all honesty, I also don’t know. But from His Majesty’s expression, he looks like he was happy. Mister’s reputation had already spread throughout the continent. And since you came to the Buddha Empire, how couldn His Majesty miss this opportunity to meet you?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s an unwarranted reputation. If we consider everything, it’s my fault for not sending prior word to his Majesty when I decided to visit the Empire.”

Ironwood smiled and said, “The Buda Clan is a Great Clan of the Continent. For Patriarch Zhao Hai to visit the empire himself, how could it be disrespectful? After all, there are also a lot of businesses that the Empire can cooperate with Mister.”

Chapter 586: Banquet in the Great Hall

Zhao Hai didn’t refute Ironwood’s words. There were only a few people on the continent that didn’t know about the Buda Clan’s goods. The clan was now a very famous Merchant Family.

The Buda Clans wasn’t that reputable before, but now that they had absorbed the Markey Family, nobody dared to neglect them.

The Markey Family was originally one of the biggest Merchant Clans of the continent. Their factories and connections were something that only few can compare to. Although the Markey Family had shrunk its influence and changed its philosophy, it didn’t negatively affect them. Conversely, it actually made them even more famous.

In the past, the Markey Family had been very overbearing in doing business. Although they had worked with a lot of people, these people didn’t necessarily like the family. It was only because of the family’s potential and the benefits that these people chose to cooperate with them.

On the other hand, the present Markey Family was actually acting very fair. Because of this, they had gained immense popularity. Although their business had shrunk, the money that they had acquired by selling Haven Products as well as their current structure made their everyday profits stay the same.

At the same time, the Buda Clan holding Golden Island made it so that people in the continent wanted to win the clan over. Because of the special location of Golden Island, it had quickly become a major marine hub, it immediately became very lively. Therefore, almost every family in the continent decided to do their business there.

The reason this profitable situation stayed tranquil and devoid of problems was the background of the Buda Clan. In the recent months, the Buda Clan had made a lot of world-shaking events. They had shown that they had more than one 9th rank expert in addition to Zhao Hai being a very powerful Dark Mage. It was said that their military strength surpassed that of a Duchy. In this situation, there were only a few people who would dare to offend them.

Now that the status of the Buda Clan was very high, even Empires would need to think twice before provoking them.

Due to all of this reasons, Zhao Hai believed Ironwood’s statement that the Buddha Emperor might do business with him.

While they chatted, the carriage finally arrived in Iron Knight City’s Imperial Palace. The carriage didn’t undergo inspection as it immediately entered the outer courtyard. Then the two disembarked from the carriage and walked towards the palace.

At this time, the skies had already turned a bit dark. However, the Imperial Palace had already lit their magic lamps ahead of time, making the place bright as though it was still daytime. Under the lead of a eunuch, Zhao Hai and Ironwood then proceeded to the inner courtyard.

The Buddha Imperial Palace looked quite similar to the Rosen Imperial Palace. The ground was paved with stone that shone with a tint of blue as it was illuminated by the lamps.

There were quite a lot of trees all around, but none of them were quite big. This was also something common to Royal Palaces. Although trees were allowed to grow, they very regularly trimmed, making them unable to fully develop. This was done in order to prevent assassins from hiding in those trees to wait for ambush.

Under the court eunuch’s leadership, they finally arrived at the Imperial Palace’s Great Hall. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stay silent before entering the hall, , this was because he had heard clamoring inside. This made Zhao Hai very curious, what was this place? And who would dare to be noisy inside the Imperial Palace?

Before long, they arrived in front of the Great Hall’s door. Upon seeing them arrive, the two eunuchs guarding the entrance immediately announced, “Vice Admiral Ironwood and Patriarch Zhao Hai has arrived!”

The voice of the eunuch sounded high-pitched, however, it still resounded inside the Great Hall. When the announcement was heard, the people clamoring suddenly became quiet. Then a voice was heard from another eunuch, “We  invite Patriarch Zhao Hai and Vice Admiral Ironwood inside”

Only then did Zhao Hai and Ironwood enter the Great Hall. Upon entering, Zhao Hai paused. There were a lot of people inside, they should be the Nobles of the Buddha Empire.

With his familiarity with palaces, Zhao Hai knew that the Emperor was holding a banquet. No wonder sounds were heard outside.

Zhao Hai saw a throne present on  a meter-high platform in the far end of Great Hall. It was entirely made of gold and was also inlaid with a lot of gemstones, it looked very beautiful.

Sitting on the throne was a person who seems to be quite young, maybe only about 40 years old. However, the person’s stature looked very big. From what Zhao Hai can see, this person was more than two-meters in height, he should be as tall as Ironwood. Although the person was wearing his Imperial Robes, even it cannot hide his enormous body.

This person’s skin had darkened and was like bronze, one might even see reflections on his skin as light hit his face. Although the beard on the person’s face was arranged very neatly, one could still feel a sense of overwhelming aura in them. Zhao Hai was almost certain that this person cultivated Battle Qi, otherwise his body wouldn’t have reached this state.

Zhao Hai understood that this person was the Buddha Empire’s Monarch. Ironwood took a step forward and bowed, “Ironwood has seen His Majesty!”

The person nodded and said, “Stand up, no need to bow, take a seat.”

Ironwood replied, “I thank his Majesty.” Then he retreated before sitting in an empty seat.

Zhao Hai then went forward and gave a small bow, “Zhao Hai Buda gives his respects to His Majesty.”

The Buddha Emperor looked at Zhao Hai and chuckled, “Mister Zhao Hai is too polite. Mister coming to the Buddha Empire is our greatest honor.”

Zhao Hai straightened his body and then smiled faintly, “Zhao Hai came to do some business but didn’t inform His Majesty. This one should be punished.”

The Buddha Emperor waved his hand and said, “What is mister saying? Mister is an honored guest in my Buddha Empire. Mister, have a sit beside me, then we’ll go have a meal.” Then a eunuch issued a command before a team quickly assembled a chair and table right beside the Buddha Emperor.

The seat and table was naturally much inferior compared to the Emperor’s. However, sitting this close to him was already a monument to Zhao Hai’s status.

Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude before moving to the table that was prepared for him. After sitting down, the court eunuch immediately offered Zhao Hai a glass of fruit wine. At this time, the Buddha Emperor, “Serve the food.” Then eunuchs came in to the Great Hall to serve a variety of dishes, they also came in with additional jugs of liquor.

After the food and wine were served, the Emperor lifted his glass up and said, “Mister Zhao Hai’s arrival today is my Buddha Empire’s pride. Let’s offer mister Zhao Hai our hospitality!”

The Buddha Empire Nobles immediately lifted their glasses and said, “To mister Zhao Hai!”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “This one doesn’t dare. This Zhao Hai is thankful for His Majesty’s toast” Then he drank his glass of Fruit wine, it tasted very good.

The Buddha Emperor drank from his glass as well. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, let me personally offer you a cup.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Thank you, Your Majesty.” Then he drank another glass.

After drinking the wine, the Buddha Emperor then said, “I don’t know why mister visited this time, is it for business?”

Zhao Hai whispered inwardly, “I knew it”. He knew that the Buddha Emperor would ask him about this matter. In fact, it was impossible for the Buddha Emperor to know about his trip to the Dwarf Mountains. The Emperor’s question was only for formality.

Zhao Hai didn’t take long before replying, “Answering his Majesty’s question. I came this time to do business with the Dwarves. I heard that they loved wine, and I happen to have a liquor business. Therefore, I came this time to see if I can sell them some.”

The Buddha Emperor’s eyes flashed for a moment before he replied, “Oh, did the transaction go smoothly?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Very smooth. But my business with the Dwarves wasn’t that big. I only traded for some ironware.”

The Buddha Emperor smiled and said, “If mister sells those ironwares to the Rosen Empire, then mister would definitely gain a hefty profit. Let this Emperor congratulate mister in advance.”

Zhao Hai gave a smile and said, “His Majesty misunderstood. I indeed have people to sell these ironwares to, but they aren’t in the Rosen Empire. In fact, the Rosen Empire didn’t have a huge demand for ironwares. Although the ironware I got was made by the Dwarves, they are still ordinary products. And with my transportation cost, I don’t think these ironwares would sell well in the Rosen Empire.”

The Buddha Emperor stared, then he asked, “Oh, if Mister isn’t selling them to the Rosen Empire, then where would mister be taking them?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I know Your Majesty has already heard this, but I have some business dealings with the Beastmen. The Prairie had a severe lack of iron, so I’m planning on bringing these ironware to the Prairie. Moreover, when i made a deal with them regarding liquor, I also agreed to their proposal of trading them with iron. And since I’m also quite curious, I went to the Dwarf Mountains and see if they have some to spare.”

The Buddha Emperor nodded and said, “So it’s for the Beastmen. Mister’s contacts are indeed very broad. I didn’t expect that you’d supply the Beastmen to this extent. That’s fantastic.”

Zhao Hai said, “My time trading with the Beastmen was quite short, however, I’ve managed to help them at times, making them trust me in doing business. And now, after the war, the Beastmen didn’t have much need for food, but instead, what they wanted was iron. I originally traded grain with them, but now I can only trade for some ironware. To tell you the truth, I won’t be gaining too much with this transaction. The operating costs alone would cut a huge chunk of the profits. But since I made an agreement with them, I had no other choice but to do it.”

The Buddha Emperor can only smile faintly as he replied, “Mister and the Beastmen’s relationship is indeed very good. After the war, there weren’t a lot of Human Merchants who can come to trade in the Prairie. On the other hand, a big business such as ironware was actually given to mister. It’s quite obvious how trustworthy mister seemed to them.”

Chapter 587: Magic Beast Business

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Majesty thinks too highly of me. The Buda Clan only does business fairly, that’s why the Beastmen decided to trust us.”

The Buddha Emperor faintly smiled, “Mister doesn’t need to be too modest. Actually, I invited Mister over because I also have a business matter to discuss.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately replied, “Your Majesty can tell me.”

The Buddha Emperor nodded and said, “When our Empire started, our crowning glory was our cavalry. At that time, we were unmatched in the continent. But in the recent years, the Magic Beasts that we had reared were very weak. Moreover, their numbers had shrunk more and more. This is an important matter for the Empire. Therefore, I’m here to ask mister to see if you can buy some Magic Beasts in the Prairie for us. What does mister think about this?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately thought that the Emperor was describing the situation of their breeding grounds. Probably because of the unfavorable conditions, their Magic Beasts have started to dwindle in numbers while degrading in quality. For a cavalry-oriented nation, this was a fatal development. At this time, there were close to no Merchants that were trading in the Prairie aside from the Buda Clan. Therefore, the Buddha Emperor decided to invite Zhao Hai over and propose this business of Magic Beasts.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then asked, “What Magic Beasts does Your Majesty want to buy? There are a lot of Beastman races, and each of them had their own unique magic beasts. However, the way these races protect their magic beasts is very strict. For ordinary tribes, maybe this business might go through. But if it involves Warring Races, then the situation would be different. I’m afraid even your name wouldn’t suffice.”

The Buddha Emperor didn’t get angry at Zhao Hai’s words, instead, he just nodded and said, “Mister is really a straightforward person. This Emperor wasn’t deceived. Mister, I mainly want some bull or horse magic beasts. Can mister agree to that?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and replied, “I won’t hide the truth from your Majesty. My relationship with the Cow Race is very good. If his majesty wanted some bulls, then I can guarantee that I can buy you some. However, for horse magic beasts, I’m still not quite sure. I didn’t have any dealings with the Horse Race before, so I’m not confident in assuring your Majesty about their magic beasts.”

The Buddha Emperor gave a nod and said, “Mister’s words already gave me relief. I want to ask mister to buy at least 5th rank magic beasts. The more the better. The same goes true with the horse magic beasts. I’ll buy as many as mister can supply. I also won’t blame mister if you cannot manage to buy some.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, rest assured your Majesty, I can at least guarantee the supply of bull magic beasts. As for the horses, I can only give it a try.”

The Buddha Emperor held his wine glass up and said, “I’ll have to thank mister for the trouble. Rest assured, this Emperor wouldn’t treat you badly in terms of price.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Majesty is too polite. I’m originally a merchant. Your Majesty giving me this huge business means that you trusted me. Your Majesty can also rest assured that I would give you a fair price.”

The Buddha Emperor laughed and said, “Alright, mister gave me relief. Listening to mister speak doesn’t really give me a feeling that you’re a merchant. Other Merchants sound so calculating, very unlike mister’s refreshing tone.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Majesty might not know, but Beastmen doesn’t like people that are too calculating. If you squeeze them of profits, the Beastmen wouldn’t like you. When I do business with the Beastmen, I always give them a fair price along with good quality products. This is the reason why Beastmen liked doing business with me.”

The Buddha Emperor smiled and said, “I see. There are a lot of people who did business in the Prairie, but there aren’t a lot of people who think like mister. They always think about how to profit off of the Beastmen. Not knowing that it would actually produce such dislike towards them.”

Zhao Hai replied, “That’s right. And now that the war with the Beastmen was still fresh in their minds, nobody would dare come to the Prairie. I think this is a good opportunity. If it was before, I wouldn’t be as confident about buying magic beasts. But now, I think the beastmen would agree.”

The Buddha Emperor laughed loudly and said, “Mister is really wise. Unwise people don’t think about the big picture. Mister is truly a person of great wisdom.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’m not worthy of His Majesty’s praise. I’m just a Merchant. Merchants who only chase small profits are not good businessmen.”

The Buddha Emperor’s laughs got louder as he lifts his wine glass and said, “Talking with mister is truly a unique experience. This Emperor hopes to be mister’s friend.”

Zhao Hai hastily lifted his glass and replied, “This one is unworthy. His Majesty giving me his regards has already brought huge honor to this Zhao Hai. If Your Majesty needs anything from me, then please don’t hesitate to send word.”

The Buddha Emperor gave a faint smile as he drank his glass with Zhao Hai. Although they were talking normally, their voices weren’t loud enough to be heard by the Nobles below. However, when the Nobles noticed how friendly Zhao Hai and the Emperor were, even repeatedly sharing drinks together, they couldn’t help but shake in anticipation.

Some of them knew why the Emperor had invited Zhao Hai over. Now that they saw the two’s interactions, it seems like the deal had come through.

The Buddha Empire’s cavalry crisis not only affected the Emperor, the pressure was also passed down to the Nobles. Because of this, all of them were hoping that this deal with Zhao Hai would go through.

After the banquet ended, Zhao Hai gave his farewells to the Buddha Emperor. The Emperor then had Ironwood arrange some rooms in the embassy for Zhao Hai to stay in. Zhao Hai didn’t decline this invitation. He had noticed that Laura and the others were now awake. He wanted to see them before he took a rest.

This embassy was a place where envoys from other countries would stay. Therefore, the place’s interior was very well decorated. Moreover, it was regularly cleaned all throughout the year. Although Zhao Hai wasn’t an envoy, his status wasn’t low enough to merit him staying in one of the Nobles’ place. Therefore, the only place that he can stay in was this embassy.

After entering the embassy and his room, Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate before flashing to the Space. When he arrived at the Space, he saw Laura and the others in the living room, chatting.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Laura and the others immediately stood up to welcome him. Laura spoke for the group and said, “Brother Hai, after drinking the Blood Pond water, there were a lot of dirty things that came out of our bodies. However, we didn’t become 9th ranks. What’s going on?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s just fine. Your bodies are just expelling some impurities, there’s no need to worry about it. You can just drink some Spatial Water and go back to cultivating. I’m certain that you would reach 9th rank by then. If you feel uncomfortable, you don’t need to rush it, you can just take your time.”

While he was talking, Zhao Hai also inspected the conditions of Laura and the others. He discovered immediately that their skins had become much more delicate. It looked as delicate as a drop of water.

Zhao Hai knew that the reason for this was the expulsion of toxins from their bodies. They seem to have become much healthier compared to before.

When Laura heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but nod and said, “I’m not really feeling uncomfortable with my body. I just feel very weak. I’ll rest for the evening and resume cultivating tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai gave a smile and said, “Alright, cultivating later or now wouldn’t make much of a difference. Right, what’s with the situation with Blockhead and the others?”

Laura smiled and said, “They’re currently inside the Hot Springs, accompanying father to a bath.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, that’s good. When they come out, I’ll also have them take a rest. It’s not too late to cultivate tomorrow.” Laura and the others nodded, then they turned to rest in their rooms.

While Zhao Hai sat in the living room, Blockhead and the others came out, along with Karen. Each of their complexions looked very good. It seems like the Blood Pond water has benefitted them a lot.

After the group sat down, Zhao Hai turned to Karen and said, “Father-in-law, I just listened to Laura about how your bodies felt weak. You can just rest first and continue cultivating tomorrow. What do you think?”

Karen nodded and said, “Alright. Even cultivating makes me feel tired. I’ll continue cultivating tomorrow.”

Then Zhao Hai turned to Blockhead and said, “You also, go rest and cultivate tomorrow. No need to be anxious about this thing. Don’t stress your bodies out, it also needs to take a rest.”

Blockhead and the others nodded, then they turned around to return to their room. After that, Zhao Hai called Cai’er over and said, “Cai’er, go count how many 5th rank bull magic beasts we have. The type that’s suitable for the Buddha Empire’s use.”

Cai’er said, “Young Master, didn’t you plan to buy the magic beasts from the Beastmen? Why would you sell the Space’s beast to the Buddha Empire?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m just asking because I’m planning on having Big Brother undertake this business. But you should know that the beasts in the Prairie doesn’t live well in the human lands. I’m planning on buying some magic beasts from big brother and raising them in the Space while selling the pre-existing magic beasts here to the Buddha Empire.”

Zhao Hai knew that this magic beast business was very big. Although he was capable of handling it by himself, he just cannot neglect the situation of Wales’ tribe. For Wales, this business was very important. The Herculean Bulls had just suffered from a disaster, their strength have been severely injured. If this business goes through, then it would greatly help them in their recovery.

Cai’er nodded and then counted in her mind before saying, “Young Master, there are a lot of bull magic beasts in the Space. But these magic beasts are all common bulls. I’m afraid these would look strange outside.”

Chapter 588: A Series of Promotions to 9th Rank

When Zhao Hai heard Cai’er, he couldn’t help but knit his brows. He knew what Cai’er meant. Because the Space levelled up, the Magic Beasts inside were upgraded as well. Therefore, the most common bull present had turned into 5th rank magic beasts. But its form still remained the same.

In the continent, the common bull was one of the most common magic beast. If Zhao Hai took his common bulls and sold them to the Buddha Empire, then they would definitely be identified at first glance. And if the common bulls reached 5th rank, then they would attract suspicion, which wouldn’t be good.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before saying, “So the only thing we can do right now is to get Big Brother’s magic beasts to the Space and have them drink some Spatial Water to improve their ranks. Let’s just hope that they can survive in Human lands. Otherwise, we can only provide the beasts from the Space.”

Cai’er didn’t respond. After the Space had been upgraded, even the most inferior magic beasts, like rabbits have become 4th rank beasts. One couldn’t see a low ranked beast anymore. Other people were troubled because their beasts were too low ranked. However, Zhao Hai’s problem was that he had a lot of high ranked beasts.

At this point, the beasts in the Space can only be processed before being sold out. Otherwise, when people find out that even Zhao Hai’s rabbits have gotten to 4th rank, they would immediately assume that he has a way to increase a magic beast’s rank. At that point, nobody would be paying attention on the Radiant Church and would instead shift their attention to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to reach that state. Although he now had the strength to conquer the continent, there were still the Gods and the Demons that were in front of him, towering like mountains. Zhao Hai knew that if he would take any big actions, then the Radiant Church would possibly start their plan ahead of time. At this point, Zhao Hai cannot make any mistakes.

Since he had destroyed the Radiant Church’s plans time and time again, then it would be impossible for the church to not pay any attention to him. If he shows any flaws in his action, then the Radiant Church would definitely know about it.

The Radiant Church had been operating in the continent for a lot of years. Although they were being pressured by the Great Clans, they still had people in hiding in sight and were gathering news for the church. They definitely still had influence in the continent, Zhao Hai just cannot neglect them.

Zhao Hai can only hope that when he reaches the Prairie, Wales would have the appropriate magic beasts that he needs.

The next morning, Zhao Hai got on board the Haven in order to leave. The Buddha Emperor also sent out a ship in order to escort Zhao Hai to the sea. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t decline this hospitality. This was a courtesy that even envoys from other continents didn’t get, which also made the nobles of the Buddha Empire very surprised.

The Buddha Emperor did this because he really wanted Zhao Hai to bring him some magic beasts. And another reason was in order to look good in the eyes of Zhao Hai.

The Buddha Emperor had a lot of contact with different merchants. Although these Merchants had high status, the Buddha Emperor found that he didn’t like them. On the other hand, Zhao Hai was different, he acted like he wasn’t a merchant at all. Because of this, the Buddha Emperor was inclined to give special favor to Zhao Hai.

Monarchs tend to get used to not have any genuine friends, but the Buddha Emperor was quite different. In the past, he was not the most appropriate person for the throne. At that time, he was only the Eighth Prince and was seen as a fool by other people. While the other princes struggled for the throne, he actually ran to the army in order to cultivate.

However, nobody thought that among the princes, he was the one that the old Emperor saw was the most dazzling. In the end, the old Emperor found an excuse in order to deal with the other princes and give all of the power to the Eight Prince, making him the Emperor in the process.

The Buddha Emperor didn’t think that he would obtain the throne. He also thought that his character was very inappropriate for the position. His character was too straight, but since he already had the throne, he can only do his best to protect it.

The Buddha Emperor was not a fool. The reason why he didn’t join the struggle with his other brothers was because he didn’t like killing one another. Naturally, even if he already had the throne, he still stuck with this philosophy.

In the beginning, the other nobles thought that he didn’t know anything, therefore they started to suppress him. However, they didn’t expect that the Buddha Emperor had experience in the army, and were also in good relations with them. When the nobles were about to make their move, the army suddenly appeared on their borders, and with the Buddha Emperor’s own strength, he crushed the ambitions of those nobles.

By personally breaking their resolve, the Buddha Emperor immediately gained huge authority. And from that point on, the empire’s nobles didn’t dare to underestimate their Emperor.

However, the Buddha Emperor had found out that he wasn’t happy even after becoming the monarch. He was used to the army where everyone is in close terms with each other. Quite different from the Imperial Palace, where everyone was out to compete with one another. Even if these people were your officials, you wouldn’t want to be intimate with them. This made the Buddha Emperor very lonely.

But when he chatted with Zhao Hai, the Buddha Emperor felt that Zhao Hai was the right person to be friends with him. Therefore, he expressed his friendship to Zhao Hai. Moreover, he didn’t do this out of courtesy, he really does want to be Zhao Hai’s friend. This was why he sent a ship in order to escort Zhao Hai.

ZHao Hai didn’t know about any of these, he wasn’t an Emperor, so he couldn’t understand an emperor’s thoughts. What he only saw was the Buddha Emperor attaching great importance to him.

After the Haven left Iron Knight city, he left the undead behind and then flashed to the Space. Laura and the others had already started to cultivate, Zhao Hai wanted to see them get to 9th rank today.

When Zhao Hai came to the Space, Laura and the others were already cultivating. Zhao Hai looked at their expression and saw that they didn’t have the pained reaction from before, this made him relieved.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think that they would cultivate for a long time. After a whole day and night, Laura and the others had finally started to wake up one after another, but now they were all 9th rank experts. Among them, the strongest was Shue. Not only was Shue a 9th rank expert, he also possessed a Divergent Ability, which meant that his shadows were also 9th rank.

But if they rank themselves in terms of threat, Shue wouldn’t take the first place, instead it would be Shun. Shun was now a 9th rank assassin. His skills had now become much more formidable, he was now close to being unparalleled in his profession.

Blockhead and Rockhead weren’t weak as well. With their mental connection, no 9th rank expert can deal with them working together.

Laura and the others had become 9th rank as well. Although they weren’t the strongest, they weren’t the weakest as well. After all, the energy of the God’s Blood was very potent.

Among the group that had become 9th rank, Karen was the only person who seemed unenthusiastic about it. After becoming 9th rank, Karen didn’t express his glee, he just left the Space and immediately sank into his research.

Zhao Hai was helpless against Karen’s character, he could only go along with Karen’s whim. However, he didn’t give Karen the blueprints immediately. He asked Karen to try out his new ideas first, and when results come out, only then would the new blueprints get handed over.

Karen didn’t care about this, there were still some blueprints from before that he hadn’t fully researched. Therefore, after becoming 9th rank, he immediately went back to Iron Mountain Fort to continue.

After the first batch had become 9th rank, Zhao Hai immediately transferred Blockhead and Rockhead to Golden Island and had them take Kun’s place. Then Zhao Hai asked Kun to drink the Spatial Water and had him cultivate.

What surprised Zhao Hai was the smoothness of Kun’s process in becoming a 9th rank expert. It didn’t take a long time before Kun became 9th rank. Although his body expelled some impurities as well, it wasn’t as much as Laura and the others.

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai finally found a reason why. Kun had been 8th rank for a long time, sl he only needed a small push in order to become 9th rank. On the other hand, Laura and the others had depended on the Space to quickly become 8th rank. They lacked the experience of cultivation, explaining their slow progress.

After Kun finished cultivating, he immediately returned to Golden Island while Blockhead and Rockhead went to Iron Mountain Fort in order to replace Green and Merine. Green and Merine were also 8th rank for a long time, so their progress to 9th rank was smooth as well. Zhao Hai’s worries had become useless.

When the two left, Zhao Hai also gave them a lot of Spatial Water. The Spatial Water was to be used to cultivate the 100 slaves that they had already picked. Now that the slaves had regained their status as commoners, they decided to give their all to the Buda Clan, becoming loyal and devoted members of the family. Because of this, Zhao Hai gave them the gift of cultivation.

Zhao Hai wasn’t stingy when it came to his people. Since these 100 people were loyal, then it was natural for them to enjoy some benefits. They may even prove useful in the future.

While Green and Merine cultivated, the Haven had reached the sea. At the same time, the Buddha Empire escort ship also left. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t need to sail on the ship for the entire trip to the Prairie. So he went to the Space and teleported to a place near the Herculean Bull tribe.

Zhao Hai still rode his Blood Hawk when he went to the Herculean Bull tribe. He didn’t want the people of the continent to know that he had become 9th rank. He wanted to keep his rank as an ace to be used in the future.

The Herculean Bulls had been living better days recently. With the support of Zhao Hai as well as having suffered no losses in the war with the Humans, they were now slowly recovering.

Zhao Hai only brought Shue and Shun this time. He was already used to bringing the two along with him. Although the two had already become 9th rank, they were still loyal to Zhao Hai. The two of them were very clear about Zhao Hai’s true strength.[1]

Three blood hawks descended from the skies as it landed at the Herculean Bulls’ main camp. When the Herculean Bulls noticed Zhao Hai, they immediately flocked around him as Zhao Hai gave them gifts before jokingly driving them away.

Zhao Hai was now like a family to the Herculean Bulls, he was now regarded by the tribe members to be one of them. Because of this, Zhao Hai was very comfortable in joking with them.

Wales and the others were inside the golden tent. Zhao Hai didn’t give any notice as he directly entered the tent. Wales was doing something inside, Yale was present as well. However, Mendez was nowhere to be seen.

When Wales heard that Zhao Hai came, he was about to come out of the tent as Zhao Hai entered. Wales then laughed as he hugged Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, how did you have time to visit? Did you miss your brother?”

Zhao Hai returned Wales’ hug before they let loose. Then after sitting down and had a drink of hot milk wine, Zhao Hai looked at Wales and said, “Brother Wales, I came here this time because I brought business.”

Wales replied, “Business? What business? Also, no need to ask permission from me, just take the goods that you want.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “i know, but this matter is a bit sensitive. The Buddha Empire wanted me to go to the Prairie and buy some magic beasts for them.”

Wales stared, then he knit his brows and said, “They want to buy magic beasts? So it seems like it isn’t argali? Otherwise, there’s no need for you to discuss it with me. What do those fellows want?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Brother should know about the Buddha Empire’s cavalry, especially their renowned Heavy Cavalry. Even facing the Beastmen, those units wouldn’t fall behind. However, they discovered that their magic beasts had been degraded these past few years. This will hugely affect their military strength. Therefore, they asked me to go to the Prairie and buy some 4th to 5th rank bull and horse magic beasts. They want to make those into their mounts.”

Wales knitted his brows, “Brother,how can you agree to this matter? If the Humans get stronger, then it would be disadvantageous to the Beastmen. I cannot sell them these magic beasts.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Brother, you think too much. Even if their strength improves, don’t forget that the Buddha Empire is three nations away from the Beastman Prairie. Even if they want to attack the Beastmen, it would be nearly impossible. Moreover, you seem to forget that the Buddha Empire houses a race that has something that the Beastmen lacked.”

Wales stared, then he looked at Yale as their eyes shone brightly. Then the two looked at Zhao Hai and simultaneously said, “The Dwarves!”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Right. It’s the Dwarves. This time, I also went to the Dwarves under the request of His Majesty the Beast King. He wanted me to go to the Dwarves in hopes of purchasing some ironware for the Beastman race. But as you know, the Dwarves are in the Buddha Empire. If we decline the Buddha Empire’s request, then they might make it harder for us to trade with the Dwarves.”

* * *

This has to do with their previous oath, I think. That oath becomes useless after becoming 9th rank.

Chapter 589: The Divine Artifact is Lost

What Zhao Hai said was the truth. The Buddha Empire was very protective with regards to the Dwarves’ ironware. If Zhao Hai starts to massively buy from the Dwarves, then it would certainly be known to the Buddha Empire.

Although Zhao Hai has the Space, enabling him to not need to go through the Buddha Empire in order to reach the Dwarves, one shouldn’t forget that the Buddha Empire would certainly have their own merchants that would do trade in the Beastman Prairie. And these merchants would be very familiar with Dwarf ironware. If these people discover that the Beastman had a lot of Dwarf goods, then they would certainly find out where the Beastmen got it. If at that time Zhao Hai didn’t help the Buddha Empire with their magic beasts, then the Buddha Empire would immediately take action.

If the Buddha Empire pressures the Dwarves to refrain from selling Zhao Hai their goods, then Zhao Hai would be placed in a tough spot. Even if the Dwarves supported Zhao Hai, in the end, the Dwarves were still located inside the Buddha Empire’s territory. If the Buddha Empire were to wage war with the Dwarves, then things wouldn’t be so good.

In addition to being the Foreign Prince of the Herculean Bulls, Zhao Hai was also now the Foreign Elder of the Dwarves. In this case, he would not only need to consider the Beastmen, he also would have to think about the Dwarves. Neglecting people close to him was not Zhao Hai’s style. Therefore, he would need to facilitate this magic beast trade between the Beastmen and the Buddha Empire. If this goes through, then the trade between the Dwarves and the Beastmen would go smoothly as well.

When Wales heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but knit his brows. At this time, Yale said, “Patriarch, I agree with Little Hai’s plan to sell our magic beasts to the Buddha Empire. After all, the Buddha Empire is too far from us, it is near impossible for us to get into a war with them. In the war with the Aksu Empire, the Rosen Empire might have been able to help, but that was only through their navy. For the Buddha Empire, it is impossible for them to directly affect our state in the Prairie. If they were to attack by sea, it would take them an extremely long time to do so, so there’s no need to worry. Also, we have a severe lack of iron. If we use our magic beasts to get those, then our Herculean Bull tribe’s strength would be greatly promoted. Lowering the chances of us being bullied in the future.”

Wales held Zhao Hai and Yale in great regard, so he was completely convinced after hearing the two. After he listened to Yale, Wales nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll agree. But Little Hai, you need to supply us with Dwarf ironware.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Sure. I’ve got some of them with me right now, but not a lot. Moreover, I need to spare some of them for His Majesty the Beast King. So I cannot give a lot of them to you. But rest assured, when I return to the Dwarves, I would get you some more ironware.”

Wales knew that Zhao Hai cared for the Herculean Bulls, so he didn’t doubt it. He just nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll leave this matter to you. Rest assured, I’ll certainly help you with regards to this magic beast matter, whether it be bulls or horses.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “Alright, then I thank brother for the trouble. Brother, I have another matter to talk to you about. This is very important, you shouldn’t tell this to anyone. Master Yale, the same applies to you too.”

The two saw that Zhao Hai’s expression had gone serious, informing them that this matter very important, so they immediately nodded. Zhao Hai made Wales vacate the area surrounding the tent, leaving only the three of them in the area. After that, Zhao Hai told them about the Divine Realm as well as the Radiant Church.”

Upon hearing this, Wales and Yale couldn’t help but frown. They didn’t think that the situation would turn out like this. If the Divine Realm was indeed involved, then a huge trouble was coming their way.

After Zhao Hai talked, Wales bitterly smiled and said, “Little Hai, you came this time to see the Beast God’s Spear and fix its Artifact Spirit?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right. This matter is very important. Therefore, I’ll be hurrying to Beast God City after meeting you here.”

Wales and Yale looked at each other as they forced a smile. Then Wales turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I’m afraid that you would be disappointed on this trip. Our Beastman Race’s Beast God Spear has been lost.”

Zhao Hai stared, then with surprise he said, “Lost? How could that be possible? That’s the Beastman Race’s Divine Artifact? How could it be lost? When did that happen?”

Wales and Yale smiled bitterly and answered, “This matter occured more than 5000 years ago. In our records, the Beast King of that time wanted to conquer the Northern Icefields. He brought a team of ten thousand people as well as the Beast God Spear in this expedition. After that, they weren’t heard of again.”

“5000 years?!” Zhao Hai called off in alarm. He didn’t expect that the Beastman Race’s Divine Artifact would be lost for more than 5000 years. Moreover, it was lost in the Northern Icefields.

Yale sighed and then said, “5000 years ago, the position of Beast King wasn’t held by the Lion or the Tiger race. But it was held by the the strongest fighting race at that time, the Diamond Ape Tribe. It was the Patriarch of the Diamond Apes that brought the Beast God’s Spear to the Northern Icefield. When the Divine Artifact was reported to be lost, the entire race was exiled to the Icefields. They can only return to the Prairie after retrieving the Beast God’s Spear. At present, nobody knew about the fate of the Diamond Apes. And since the Diamond Apes are gone, the position of Beast King was then handed over to the Lion and Tiger Races.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Beastmen to have such a phase in their history. He couldn’t help but knit his eyebrows and say, “It looks like I need to head to the Northern Icefield.”

When Wales heard Zhao Hai, his expression couldn’t help but change, he loudly reacted, “What?! Little Hai, did you just say that you want to go to the Northern Icefield? That’s not good, it’s too dangerous, you cannot go there.”

Zhao Hai knew that Wales was sincere, therefore he smiled faintly and said, “Brother Wales, Elder Yale. I’ll lead you to a place, no matter what happens make sure to control your reaction.”

Wales and Yale looked at each other before they nodded towards Zhao Hai. And then with an intention, Zhao Hai brought Wales and Yale to the Space.

The Space was Zhao Hai’s biggest secret, only people that he trusted came to know about its existence. Since he had contact with Wales and Yale for quite a long time, Zhao Hai had come to trust the two of them, and in addition to the recent developments, Zhao Hai decided to bring Wales over to the Space.

After arriving inside, Zhao Hai then told Wales and Yale about the details of his Space. Then he led them to the Farming Ground, the Bread Trees and then to the Magic Beasts that the Space has raised.

In the end, the three went to the Space’s Villa where they saw Laura and the others. The women had already prepared a table for them to eat. After the group had sat down, Zhao Hai lifted his wine glass to Wales and Yale, “Brother Wales, Elder Yale, I have been hiding things from you. Please accept my apology.”

Wales was not someone that was easily offended, moreover, he also knew that this secret was vital to Zhao Hai’s survival, so he wasn’t angry at all. Instead, he just laughed it off and said, “It’s fine. Brother actually has such a good place. Fantastic, your Big Brother would have to depend on you for our food in the future. So how could I be angry with you about this? Come, let’s drink!”

Zhao Hai laughed, and then drank his cup along with Yale. Zhao Hai turned to Wales and said, “Big Brother, you’ve seen the Space’s magic beasts. Even the most common of them has exceptional strength. I’m thinking of handing some of the high level ones to you and see if your tribe can find a compatible soul beast among them. After that, we can change your mounts, making the tribe much stronger. What does Brother think about this?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai’s proposal, Wales stared for a moment before he laughed and said, “Good, good. That’ll be great. I’ll go and see which ones are compatible with us. Right, I think we should exit as soon as possible. Otherwise, we would be making the others wait. They have already prepared a banquet just for you.”

When he heard Wales, Zhao Hai immediately turned to the monitor. There he saw people outside Wales’ golden tent, preparing a lot of delicious food. It doesn’t need to be said that they were preparing a feast and was only waiting for Zhao Hai and the others to go out.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then let’s head out to eat. We can’t let the others wait for too long. Let’s take these liquor out as well, let everyone share the good stuff.”

Wales laughed, “Alright, but sister-in-laws wouldn’t be able to come out. Otherwise, the others would get suspicious. However, sister-in-laws doesn’t’ need to worry, I’ll have Little Hai take some roasted argali later for you to eat.”

Wales was already familiar with Laura and the others. And in addition to the Beastman’s straightforward attitude, they get to crack jokes with each other quite regularly. Laura and the others were also quite used to this.

Laura smiled and said, “Alright, we’ll wait for it here.” Then the group smiled as the three left the Space and headed outside the tent.

Since Zhao Hai had told Wales about the abilities of the Space, Wales was now quite confident in Zhao Hai’s trip to the Northern Icefields. He even hoped that Zhao Hai would come back with the Beast God’s Spear.

If Zhao Hai retrieved the Beast God’s Spear, there would be two advantages that would happen to them. First was the fact that the Beastmen would once more be under the protection of a Divine Artifact. And the other was Zhao Hai getting a much higher position among the Beastman Race. This would hugely benefit Zhao Hai’s future actions in the Prairie.

As the three walked outside, the other Herculean Bulls immediately went and greeted them. All of those present greeted Zhao Hai with a smile. They liked Zhao Hai very much, not only because he was their Prince that helped them go through tough times, but also because he made the Herculean Bulls live the best life compared to the other races in the Prairie.

Chapter 590: Meeting the Beast King

After staying the whole day with the Herculean Bulls, Zhao Hai brought Wales and Yale back to the Space. He had them pick a bull magic beast that would suit the Herculean Bulls, the one that was the most compatible to be their soul beast.

In the end, they reached a result that didn’t make them smile. Surprisingly, the beasts most suited for the Herculean Bulls were actually the stoneskin bull as well as the earth cow. It seems like the choice of the Herculean Bulls’ ancestors wasn’t wrong.

Unfortunately for them, the stoneskin bulls and earth cows that the Herculean Bulls were using were very low-levelled. The stoneskin bulls are 6th rank while earth cows are 5th rank.

However, those bulls were upgraded inside Zhao Hai’s Space. The stoneskin bulls were now 8th rank beasts while the earth cows were 7th rank. These were much higher levelled than the ones that the Herculean Bulls were using right now.

One shouldn’t look down on merely two levels. Magic beasts were different from humans and the like. For humans, as long as they had innate talent in cultivation, it wouldn’t be impossible for them to be 8th or 9th rank experts. However, magic beasts have an innate ceiling in their ranks. For a stoneskin bull, 6th rank was the maximum rank that it can achieve, it was almost impossible for it to rise by two ranks. Only if they come across a fortuitous encounter would they rank up from 6th rank.

Therefore, these two extra ranks were extremely important for magic beasts. And with the Beastman’s cultivation heavily relying on their soul beasts, having these high rank stoneskin and earth bulls were very important to the Herculean Bulls.

If the previous strength of the Herculean Bulls were only described as exceptional, with these stoneskin and earth bulls, their strength can now rank within the top ten in the entire Beastman Prairie.

Being in the top ten was an extraordinary thing. One must know that there were a lot of races in the Prairie. But Warring races only numbered less than a hundred. In the future, only a few would dare to annoy Cow Race.

Zhao Hai left 1000 stoneskin bulls and 1000 earth bulls to Wales while getting 2000 ordinary stoneskin and 2000 ordinary earth bulls in exchange. These bulls would be the first batch that would be sent to the Buddha Empire. At the same time, Zhao Hai also gave Wales some Dwarf ironware before he headed out to Beast God City.

Then Zhao Hai went to Beast God City through the Space. When he came out, he was already on top of a Blood Hawk as it descended down on the city. Ah Tai was already waiting for him there.

When Ah Tai saw Zhao Hai, he immediately went forward and gave a bow, “Young Master, you came. Please board the carriage.”

Zhao Hai looked at Ah Tai and smiled faintly, “Ah Tai, you’ve been working hard, how is the business going?”

Ah Tai smiled and said, “It’s fine, the business is doing very well. After our cooperation with the Beastmen, they would approach us first whenever they need to buy anything. We’re now the most popular merchant in the Prairie.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “That’s good. You’ve been working hard. Doing business with the Beastmen isn’t easy. But remember, as long as it’s not too much, having some losses is fine.”

Ah Tai smiled and said, “Young Master, rest assured, I know what to do. No need to be worried.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and then he rode the carriage to Beast God City. When he saw Magic Lily store inside, he couldn’t help but feel something different.

Although the store was doing great before, it wasn’t that good. Now, when he arrived, Zhao Hai saw that there were a lot of Beastmen inside the shop’s tent, looking at the goods that were sold.

Moreover, Zhao Hai also discovered that the Beastmen were very enthusiastic while talking to Ah Da and Ah Er. In the past, it was impossible for this to happen.

Then Sister-in-law invited Zhao Hai over to another tent and asked him to sit down. After being served some milk tea, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Ah Tai, Sister-in-law, you don’t need to get busy in receiving me. I’ll only be resting here for a while before going to meet the Beast King. I have something to talk about with His Majesty.”

Ah Tai nodded, he couldn’t help but praise Zhao Hai in his heart. There were a lot of merchants who did business in the Prairie, and none of them had the luxury to see the Beast King. But Zhao Hai was different, he can actually see the Beast King.

Zhao Hai drank some milk tea for a while before he left. With Ah Tai driving the carriage, Zhao Hai headed towards the Beast King Palace. Since the guards already knew Zhao Hai, they immediately lead him to the tent for registration.

Since the people inside the tent already knew him, when Zhao Hai came in, they immediately stood up and gave a small bow to Zhao Hai. After that, one of them said, “What brings Mister Zhao Hai here?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he immediately replied, “This Zhao Hai requests to see His Majesty the Beast King. I have a matter to discuss with him, I’ll have to ask for your help to send word.”

The Beastman then smiled and said, “Mister, please wait here. We’ll immediately send someone to inform his Majesty. His Majesty has been asking for Mister for a long time.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ve made his Majesty wait. Please do send word as soon as possible.” Then the Beastman gave a command as a Tiger beastman rushed to the palace.

Before long, the Tiger Beastman came back and made Zhao Hai follow him. But before leaving the tent, Zhao Hai gave each person inside a bottle of milk wine.

The Tiger Beastmen quickly led Zhao Hai to the Beast King’s study. Upon arriving, they were immediately allowed entry by the guard. The Beast King was already in the resting area waiting for Zhao Hai. When he met the Beast King, Zhao Hai immediately gave a salute. The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I’ve been waiting for mister for these past couple of days, you’ve finally arrived. Does Mister bring any good news?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I have good news for Your Majesty. I’ve gotten in contact with the Dwarves and got an agreement with the milk wine. They also agreed to sell me some ironware.”

The Beast King heartily laughed and then said, “Good, that’s fantastic. Mister really helped our Beastman Race. Mister, please have a seat, tell me everything in detail.”

Zhao Hai sat down, and then he looked at the Beast King and said, “Your Majesty, when I went to the Dwarves, I got more than some business. I also gained a new status.” Then Zhao Hai turned his hand and retrieved a token.

Upon seeing this token, the Beast King’s eyes couldn’t help but light up. He received the command token and carefully looked at it. After some time, the Beast King nodded and said, “This is the Dwarf Race’s Foreign Elder Command Token. I didn’t’ expect mister to become a Foreign Elder to the Dwarves. That’s good news.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Majesty overpraises. This time, I helped the Dwarves with a small matter. Since they are grateful for it, they asked me to be their Foreign Elder. Right, the Dwarf Patriarch has also prepared a letter for Your Majesty.” Then he retrieved Billy’s letter and gave it to the Beast King.

The Beast King received the letter and took a look at the seal before nodding. He unraveled the parchment letter and carefully read its contents. While he was reading, the Beast King’s pupils couldn’t help but contract. Then he focused more on reading the letter.

The Beast King took some time in reading the letter, and while he was doing so, Zhao Hai paid attention to the his expression. Although the Beast King’s expression didn’t change, the slight changes in his eyes was noticed by Zhao Hai.

After reading, the Beast King placed the letter down and then turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Is Patriarch Billy telling the truth? Can you have me take a look at your whip?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he untangled the whip on his waist and called Mu’er out. Mu’er gave a bow to the Beast King who then received the whip.

The Beast King asked Mu’er about several matters before nodding. Then he gave the whip back to Zhao Hai before he turned his head to the guard and said, “Make sure that nobody comes in here. If someone comes, tell them that I have no time.” The guard gave a bow and then turned around to leave the room.

When the guard left the room, the Beast King turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, is this letter real? Do Gods really exist?”

Zhao Hai answered, “Your Majesty, I wouldn’t lie about this matter. This was told to me personally by the Dwarves’ Divine Artifact Spirit. If your Majesty wants to prove it, you can make me take an audience with the Beast God’s Spear. I can assure you that I can make its Artifact Spirit materialize. After that, Your Majesty can ask him all the questions in your mind.” Although Zhao Hai already knew that the Beast God Spear was lost, he didn’t want to make it known to the Beast King. This was because this matter was held in extreme secrecy. If he lets the Beast King know that he knew about the Beast God’s Spear, then he couldn’t prove that he hadn’t told this matter to other people. Then the Beast King might not believe him.

The Beast King smiled bitterly and said, “My Beastman Race’s Divine Artifact has been lost for more than 5000 years. Even if Mister has the ability, it would be impossible for me to see the Artifact Spirit.”

Then Zhao Hai said in great surprise, “Lost? How could it be lost?”

Then the Beast King forced a smile and said, “5000 years ago, the Beast King of the Diamond Ape tribe led ten thousand people to the Northern Icefields along with the Beast God Spear. He wanted to conquer the area but was consumed by it instead. In the end, the entire Diamond Ape tribe was exiled to the Icefield, giving them the punishment of looking for the Beast God’s spear.”

After some time, Zhao Hai said, “So it was like this. Your Majesty, this one has a small request. I want to enter the Northern Icefield and retrieve the Beast God’s Spear.”

When the Beast King heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare at him. Then his expression changed as he said, “That’s no good. Absolutely no good. Mister, the Northern Icefield is too dangerous. You cannot go there. If what Patriarch Billy said was true, then Mister would be the saviour of the continent. And as the hero, you cannot perish in the Icefield.”

Naturally, the Beast King didn’t doubt Billy’s words. This was also related to the characteristics of the Dwarves, they never like to lie and hated people who do. Their honesty is very famous in the continent.

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Your Majesty, there’s no other way. I think your Majesty already believes Patriarch Billy’s statement. So if those three artifacts aren’t fixed, then it would be difficult for us to deal with the Gods. And if the Dwarves’ prophecy is true, then I should be able to safely go out of the Icefield.”

Chapter 591: The Icefield

The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, you should know that you’re gambling. If you bet wrong, then you’ll be forfeiting your life.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Your Majesty, we’ve been pushed to a corner, so why don’t we gamble? If we don’t get the three artifacts when the Divine Realm comes, we’re done for. Even if we aren’t killed, we would still become their slaves. And I don’t want to live as a slave.”

The Beast King knew that what Zhao Hai said was true. It’s impossible to know when the Divine Realm would attack, Zhao Hai doesn’t need to take the risk. The Beast King thinks that the reason he did this was for the Beastman Race as well as the Ark Continent.

The Beast King stood up and looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister’s heart is broader than the Prairie. Let this king offer you his respects.” Then he gave Zhao Hai a bow.

Zhao Hai quickly stood up and said, “Your Majesty, there’s no need to be too polite. With your Majesty’s agreement, I’ll prepare for two days before leaving for the Northern Icefield.”

The Beast King nodded and said, “Alright, since Mister is settled on this matter, if Mister is able to bring back the Beast God’s Spear from the Northern Icefield, then I shall bestow Mister with the position of the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince. Even if the Beast King changes in the future, your position would still remain.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I thank His Majesty. Your Majesty, please arrange a warehouse for me. This time I’ve brought over some ironware from the Dwarves.”

The Beast King nodded, then he called for the guard and had him arrange the warehouse. Zhao Hai gave the Beast King a bow before leaving with the guard.

After depositing the ironware, Zhao Hai followed the guard back to the Beast King’s study. The Beast King then invited Zhao Hai over to a meal before letting Zhao Hai leave.

At this point, Zhao Hai’s goals had been achieved. He believed that the Beast King trusted Billy’s letter, and would take this matter seriously. The Beast King would certainly make proper arrangements.

After returning to his shop, Zhao Hai began to prepare for his expedition to the Northern Icefield. Since all that he would need is in the Space, Zhao Hai had a meal with Ah Tai’s family first before taking a rest in the Space.

Zhao Hai only stayed in Beast God City for two days before leaving. The Beast King also sent a secret letter to the White Tigers, Polar Bears, and the Hawk King, who were stationed near the Icefields, commanding them to treat Zhao Hai with hospitality. He also told them what Zhao Hai was about to do in the Icefield.

The Beast King didn’t tell them that Zhao Hai was going to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear in order to deal with the Gods, that information must be kept confidential. The Beast King only told them that he had sent Zhao Hai to the Icefield in order to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear.

The Beast King sent the letter two days prior to Zhao Hai’s departure. Therefore, when Zhao Hai reached Hawk King mountain, he was immediately warmly received by the Ice Hawk King.

Although their cooperation had just started, the Hawks had gained a lot of profits. Since Zhao Hai was also going to the Icefields in order to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear, this made the Hawks look at Zhao Hai in a much better light. They immediately regarded him with more respect compared to before.

Beastmen respected heroes, not to say about Zhao Hai retrieving the Beast God’s Spear, his courage alone made him a hero in the eyes of the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai didn’t stay in Hawk King mountain for too long, he only stayed there for one day. Moreover, he also deliberately told the Hawk King that no matter what happens to him, the milk wine cooperation would still continue, so the Hawk King wouldn’t have to worry.

When the Hawk King heard what Zhao Hai said, he couldn’t help but respect him much more. In his opinion, this was equal to Zhao Hai handling the matters after his death.

When leaving the Hawk King mountain,  Zhao Hai sat on the back of a Blood Hawk and headed directly to the Northern Icefield. He didn’t bother to visit the White Tigers and the Polar Bears. He wants to quickly settle the matters in the Icefields and then look at the other Forbidden Areas to see if he can get something from them.

After crossing Hawk King mountain, Zhao Hai received the Blood Hawk and retrieved his Blood Ghost Staff. He had the staff transform into a white v-shaped object and invited Laura and the others over as he sat inside to explore the Icefield.

This was the first time that Laura and the others had seen the transformation of the Blood Ghost Staff. It was too mysterious, they curiously explored the inside of the somewhat red and somewhat transparent room that they were in.

This room wasn’t very big, it was about 40 square meters. This room that was made by the staff has the ability to see the outside from the inside. However, there was a tint of red in it, it was like seeing through a red tinted glass.

Zhao Hai didn’t fly too high. Although he can just let the Blood Ghost Staff fly while they enter the Space and look through the monitor, they didn’t do it. Zhao Hai wanted to personally experience the scenery of the Icefield.

The outside was a world of ice and snow, but the inside of the room was actually very warm, one cannot feel even a point of coldness. Zhao Hai retrieved some furniture such as some table and chairs as they sat inside and drank while looking at the scenery.

The Northern Icefield looked like a huge stretch of desolate land. There wasn’t anything in it except ice and snow. Zhao Hai hadn’t met a single living being ever since entering the Icefield.

The place was indeed worthy of being called an Icefield. Zhao Hai looked through the monitor and discovered that beneath the layer of snow, there were actually at least ten thousand years worth of ice deposits. The ice was very thick, the snow on the surface seemed to be a small film in comparison to the ice beneath it.

After some time, Laura sighed and said, “This place is indeed to beautiful, however, it is also very cold. It seems like there aren’t any products that we can get here.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “That’s not necessary. You see that land? Although it seems like there’s nothing there, if you look carefully, you will find that there’s something white on top of it. That isn’t snow, but a living creature.”

Laura and the others focused their eyes on the area that Zhao Hai pointed to. And indeed, there was a very thin, thinner than paper, layer of white below the snow. It might look like snow, but if one carefully looks at it, one would discover that it was different. It was like a type of moss, a lifeform.

Megan said in disbelief, “Is that really a lifeform? That’s very weird, how can it survive in this environment? Brother Hai, let’s go down and take some of that stuff.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “Alright.” Then with an intention, he had the Ghost Staff descend. After that, Zhao Hai retrieved the Staff.

Retrieving the Ghost Staff essentially made the group come in contact with the Icefield. Because of this they flew slowly towards the area. The moment Zhao Hai retrieved the staff, the group immediately felt coldness envelop their bodies. This coldness was different from what they had felt during wintertime. This cold seems to have an essence, it’s like water, squeezing down on their bodies.

One must know that Zhao Hai and the others were already 9th rank experts, their vitality was extremely strong. Even if one doesn’t mention their vitality, their equipment were made to withstand cold and heat. Normal changes in temperature usually doesn’t affect them.

However, the Northern Icefield was different. The coldness present there threatened to freeze their blood, even their minds were starting to slowly come to a halt.

When Zhao Hai discovered this, he immediately moved and had the Blood Ghost Staff cover them, immediately removing the coldness in their bodies.

Laura and the others were panting. Lizzy couldn’t bear it and said, “What was that coldness? I’m 9th rank right now, but I was actually about to be frozen. With this low temperature, is that thing really alive?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he cleared the snow in front of him. The snow was thick and also quite hard. While Zhao Hai was stepping on it, Zhao Hai felt that it was no different from standing in stone.

After clearing some layers of snow, Zhao Hai stopped. Then with an intention, he retrieved a patch of land and absorbed it to the Space. The group entered as well.

It didn’t take too long before a prompt was heard, “Special lifeform discovered. Lifeform can survive in extremely low temperatures. Extracting the life form’s properties. Increased the Host’s resistance to cold.”

Then Zhao Hai threw the patch of land on the ground before turning to the others and said, “I’m not mistaken, that thing is really alive.”

Laura and the others looked at the patch of land that was thrown on the ground by Zhao Hai. After it fell, none of the snow fell down, it seems like the ice and snow was harder than stone.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and smiled faintly, “So what do you think? You still want to go and sightsee?”

When they heard this, Laura and the others couldn’t help but shiver. Laura said, “It’s fine, let’s just stay in the Space and have the Blood Ghost Staff fly outside.”

Zhao Hai smiled at the staff. To be honest, he didn’t want to go out of the Space. The scenery looked good, but it wouldn’t take a long time before he would get bored of it.

The group sat down in the living room as Zhao Hai retrieved a bottle of rice wine. After the group drank a cup, they couldn’t help but let out a long breath. The cup of wine made their bodies warmer, the coldness had finally started to leave their bodies.

After placing her glass down, Megan let out a long breath and said, “That was scary, too scary. Indeed worthy of being one of the Five Forbidden Areas. Even 9th rank experts would freeze to death here. I think that this place is much more frightening than the Carrion Swamp.” Laura and the others nodded in agreement.

Seeing their reactions, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “We’re just unprepared this time. If we had, then wouldn’t we know what we are going to encounter? And since we haven’t seen any Diamond Ape corpses, then it means that it’s possible to get into a deeper part of the Icefield. I want to go further until we spot some of them. After we do so, we’ll be able to gain some insights on where the Beast God Spear is.”

Laura knit her brows as she said, “Brother Hai, do you really think that there are any Diamond Apes left? This is the Icefield, how could that be possible? It’s impossible for those apes to be all 9th ranks. The coldness of the Icefield would be enough to freeze them solid. How would they be able to survive?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You shouldn’t underestimate the potential of people. Think about it, our Human bodies are much more inferior to the Beastmen, yet here we are having close to equal military power. Even if we cannot beat the physique of the Beastmen, we can breach the gap through cultivation. Not to say about the original Royal Race of the Beastmen. For a long time, the Diamond Apes had the seat of the strongest, it would do them disservice if we compare them to the current Royal Tribe.

Laura thought for a moment and then said, “Alright, then let’s go look for them. I really want to see what the Diamond Apes looked like.”

Zhao Hai smiled and then controlled the Blood Ghost Staff to continue flying in the Icefield. But to Zhao Hai’s disappointment, they didn’t meet any other living being aside from the white moss. They saw some ice cold bodies on the surface, but these were already here for a long time, their bones were now made of stone.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about it and just controlled the staff to search the Icefield. In any case, they were in the Space, so there was no reason for them to stop searching.

After two days of looking at the Icefield, the only moving people that Zhao Hai can see were some Polar Bears doing their own thing. Zhao Hai made sure that the staff goes unseen as he continued to search.

After two more days of searching, Zhao Hai still hasn’t seen anything besides the white moss. Aside from that moss, the only thing that he constantly saw were ice and snow.

These past couple of days of searching, Zhao Hai solidified his belief that some Diamond Apes have to have survived. And even if some of them died, he should still be able to spot some of their corpses. But until now, he wasn’t able to spot a large number of bodies.

The search went very tasteless, but Zhao Hai insisted. He didn’t believe that he cannot find a single clue about the Diamond Apes. Even if he didn’t, he was still sure that he would be able to see another kind of life form. It was impossible for the Northern Icefield to only house those white moss, there should be other beings living here.

The reason why Zhao Hai had such confidence was his experience back on Earth. Even in the most unforgiving environments of the planet, there were still lifeforms that managed to survive. The North Pole and the Antarctic of the Earth was just like the Icefield, so he firmly believed that other life forms was present here.

Chapter 592: Discovery

The Northern Icefield was much bigger than what Zhao Hai had imagined. He reckoned that the place was much larger than the Carrion Swamp. Even after investigating for ten days, Zhao Hai still didn’t have a substantial harvest. What he saw were only some frozen bones, but those had already been ruined by the winds of the Icefield, making them incomplete. Because of this, Zhao Hai has no way to know what race of people those bones belonged to.

But Zhao still insisted on pushing through, watching the screen everyday. Laura and the others had stopped doing so long time ago. The scenery in the Icefield was very monotonous, it might even drive people crazy.

There was only one thing that they can see here, and that was the plain white landscape of the Icefield. Aside from that, there was virtually nothing.

Zhao Hai stared at the screen carefully, he didn’t want to miss anything. He just took some rest from time to time.

In fact, Zhao Hai’s trip didn’t have much of an impact to his usual operation. After all, he has the Space, he can return to the continent at any time. He can still handle his businesses as well as the Buda Clan’s matters.

The Buda Clan’s matters were already on track, so Zhao Hai didn’t really need to manage it too much. The Buda Clan wasn’t the same as the other families that were to centralized on their patriarch. Zhao Hai’s matters were now mainly taken care of by Laura and the others, leaving him with very little to do.

The feelings of Laura and the others towards each other were also very good. And they also knew about Zhao Hai’s personality, so there was no jealousy present that was common in noble households, saving Zhao Hai lots of worries.

Actually, this was partially due to the Space. The Space can slowly change a person’s thinking. And since Zhao Hai was the host, people would slowly see him much more favorably.

Laura and the others also underwent this change and were now centered around Zhao Hai. Because of this, they didn’t become jealous of each other.

But in the end, this change was vastly slower compared to the Space subduing the 9th rank Magic Beasts. Because of this, nobody knew about it, even Zhao Hai.

On Zhao Hai’s 12th day in the Icefield, he was still staring at the blank landscape. Zhao Hai was also starting to get tired at this point.

At this time, a strange thing attracted Zhao Hai’s attention. It was a piece of rock, just an average piece of rock.

If this rock was placed on other places, then it wouldn’t be very strange. However, this was the Northern Icefield, rocks were foreign existences here.

Zhao Hai looked at the the rock while the staff slowed down. He directed his focus in order to inspect what this rock was.

The monitor seems to understand Zhao Hai as it enlarged the rock’s image. It even allowed Zhao Hai to see the entire thing.

When Zhao Hai saw this rock, he couldn’t help but get shocked. He couldn’t be blamed, the rock’s form resembled an animal that he knew, a giant ape.

The bodies of giant apes are very huge. Aside from Little Jin, all of the other apes were very enormous, especially those who didn’t break through.

This ape in front of him, however, had a much bigger build. From the looks of it, this ape was about ten meters in height, it looked like it had a body that defied common sense. But the ape was now sealed in ice.

Upon looking at this ape, Zhao Hai immediately related it to the Diamond Ape Tribe. He knew the Beastman custom of having their unique magic beast. Moreover, he also asked the Beast King about the Diamond Ape tribe’s magic beasts, so that he can track the Beast God’s Spear much easier. Since he was doing it for the Beastmen, the Beast King didn’t hide anything from him. The Diamond Apes were the sole race in the Prairie that didn’t have any mounts. But even if they didn’t have a mount, they still have their beast relatives by their side. These beasts not only provide the Diamond Apes with great strength, they also increase their defensive power. This ability also made true that they share their life and death with the Diamond Apes. Once their master dies, these Magic Beasts would perish as well.

Because of this symbiotic relationship, the spiritual connection between the magic beasts and the Diamond Apes gave them even more benefit and higher power than the other Beastmen. And in turn, this strength made the Diamond Apes the Kings of the Beastman Race.

Zhao Hai looked around but cannot see a corpse of a Diamond Ape. This made Zhao Hai feel odd, if a diamond ape died here, then there should certainly be a Diamond Ape Beastman present. Why can’t he see one?”

While Zhao Hai was puzzled, Cai’er said, “Young Master, the Diamond Ape is in this thing’s belly.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he focused the monitor to look at the diamond ape’s belly. Upon looking, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get shocked. It was because in the internal organs of this diamond ape, there was actually someone, a Diamond Ape.

Zhao Hai clapped his hands as he laughed loudly. He was happy because he had finally found something in the Northern Icefield after a long time. He had finally found a Diamond Ape corpse, and in a good condition at that!

Zhao Hai’s excitement certainly alamred Laura and the others. They immediately went to the living room and looked at the monitor.

It didn’t take a long time for them to gawk at what they had seen. They also expressed their happiness, every one of them was very excited.

Zhao Hai gave a smile, then a white flash appeared as the Diamond Ape was observed inside the Space.

Zhao Hai didn’t place the corpse inside the villa, but placed it outside. Then he led Laura and the others to it.

The diamond ape was sealed in a bunch of ice, the same applied to the Diamond Ape inside its body. The diamond ape was curled up, so with it was no wonder that it looked like a rock from far away.

Although it was already dead, the diamond ape still looked very fierce. It’s imposing aura was very astonishing. One could see for frightening it would be too meet it when it was still alive.

Laura and the others gathered around the body of the diamond ape. They didn’t find the corpse strange, after all, Zhao Hai had millions of them. They were already used to it.

After looking at the corpse, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “I didn’t expect the Beastmen to have such a race. Compared to Little Jin’s tribemates, these fellows were much more larger, they looked more frightening as well.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They were once the rulers of the Prairie, people who made the other Beastmen bow. So it was certain that they were fearful. Alright, let’s melt them first before turning them into undead.”

Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as water from the Hot Spring was slowly sprinkled on the ice. However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the ice to be so hard. Spraying Hot Spring water to the corpse had become just like spraying water into glass.

Zhao Hai stared, then he waved his hand once more as a he fired a Fireball towards the ice. Only after that did the ice start to melt.

Zhao Hai released more fireballs in order to melt the ice. He also paid extreme attention to his movements in order to not burn the corpse.

When the two bodies seem to have thawed, Zhao Hai waved his hand as a mass of black mist surrounded the body. He wanted to turn the diamond ape as well as the Diamond Ape beastman into undead.

But to his disappointment, the diamond ape as well as the Beastman in its belly remained unresponsive, it didn’t turn into an undead.

This startled Zhao Hai, his Dark Magic had always been effective to all corpses, why did it not work on this diamond ape? Zhao Hai was puzzled as he re-cast his spell, which still ended up in failure.

Zhao Hai was confused, so he knocked his staff onto the corpse, discovering that it was still hard as a rock. It seems like it had been frozen for a long time that it had been petrified.

This made Zhao Hai feel relief, he stored the corpse and then returned to the villa. Then he released his staff once more and searched for other diamond ape corpses.

Completely different from the more than ten days of nothing, Zhao Hai had suddenly come up with diamond ape corpses one after the other. Zhao Hai discovered that these corpses were also sealed in ice, with the Diamond Ape beastman inside the bodies of the diamond apes. At the same time, all of them were also petrified.

In the next three days, Zhao Hai found about a thousand diamond ape corpses. All of these corpses were the same, they all contained a Diamond Ape inside. Moreover, the corpses seem to extend in a straight line.

While looking at these corpses, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but picture a scene. The Beastmen’s most powerful race, exiled to the Northern Icefields, facing the brutal environment. All of them were fueled by this obsession of retrieving the Divine Artifact. All of them were undergoing this journey of death.

In the days before, it seems like they hadn’t discovered how to take care of their dead bodies. But in the place where Zhao Hai saw the first diamond ape, it seems like they already found out a method, It’s a special way of burial in which they would bury the Beastman inside their soul beast.

Chapter 593: Volcano

Although deaths have appeared among them, the Diamond Apes that have survived still pushed on. Some people might die, but their pride as the Royal tribe of the Beastmen gave them the motivation to not back down. They just buried their loved ones before resuming on their death march.

This scene jolted Zhao Hai, the Diamond Apes were truly worthy of being the Kings of the Beastmen. With such determinations, it wasn’t a wonder why their status was too great.

Laura and the others were similarly shocked, they cannot believe how an entire race would share the same obsession. They clearly knew that they would die, but they also knew that they were duty-bound to not come back, the Beast God’s Spear was just too valuable.

Zhao Hai calmed himself before having the Blood Ghost Staff proceed forward. With the number of corpses that he received getting more and more, he didn’t have the time to try turning them into Undead. He wanted to bring these corpses to the Prairie and give them a proper burial. They belonged to the Prairie, and it was proper for them to be buried there. In Zhao Hai’s mind, they already had the qualifications to do so.

Ten days after discovering the first Diamond Ape corpse, Zhao Hai had already stored about 10 thousand Diamond Ape corpses. The majority of these corpses were the elderly and children.

Zhao Hai didn’t explore other places right now, the trail of corpses were already his guide. As long as he follows them, then he would surely reach a destination.

After a month of flying around, the Diamond Ape corpses had already numbered to about five hundred thousand. This wasn’t a small number.

Most large tribes in the Prairie had about 1 million members. And for a huge warring tribe like the Tiger race, it might even be less. The more powerful the race, the more difficult it would be for them to multiply. Less powerful tribes, on the other hand, had great fertility.

Since the Diamond Apes were the strongest at their time, then it would be impossible for them to have very large numbers. By the time he reached 500 thousand corpses, Zhao Hai can no longer see elderly and children among them. Most of what he acquired at this point, were young and able men.

One must know that although Zhao Hai took a long time to collect these corpses, he was someone who was flying in the Icefield. Now imagine the state of these Diamond Apes, how long did they have to walk this way without stopping, how long did they kept their resolve? Zhao Hai doesn’t dare to imagine it.

It was very difficult for Zhao Hai to think about how these Diamond Apes were able to survive in such a climate. Their ability to penetrate this far into the Icefield was a monument to the tyrannical strength of their race.

After three days of flying, Zhao Hai discovered from the monitor that some black spots were spotted at a distance. He immediately enlarged the image and couldn’t help but get shaken. This was because he had discovered a mountain, but what’s most surprising in this mountain were the trees that were present. How could fully grown green trees be present here?

This might not be strange in the continent, but what shocked Zhao Hai was the fact that it was here, in the Northern Icefield. There was almost nothing here aside from snow and ice. Who would’ve thought that a mountain would be present here, and with a tree growing on it.

Zhao Hai immediately commanded the staff to fly to the mountain, while simultaneously collecting the corpses along the way. The number of corpses that he had received has now numbered to about seven hundred thousand.

Because he was still storing the corpses, Zhao Hai took a little over two days before he arrived at the mountain. At the same time, Zhao Hai discovered that the area close to the mountain was devoid of any Diamond Ape corpses.

This fact made Zhao Hai excited, it was just like what he had thought, the Diamond Apes didn’t die out. The tree in the mountain represented the fact that there was warmth present there, which would in turn allow a person to survive. It was possible for the Diamond Apes to thrive on this mountain. The absence of corpses in the surroundings meant that the surviving Diamond Apes had already retrieved them.

Zhao Hai was elated, he immediately had the monitor focus on the mountain. He wanted to know what this mountain was and see if there were people present.

Upon further investigation, Zhao Hai discovered something that made him excited. There were roads paved in the mountain! It was artificial, moreover, there were evidence that some people had walked on them.

With his excitement still present, Zhao Hai immediately came out of the Space and turned the Ghost Staff into a shuttle before flying towards the mountain.

After he came out, he had discovered that the temperature near the mountain was quite high. It had the same temperature as the middle of the day in the continent, no wonder a tree can survive here for so long, it was actually very warm.

The higher one gets to the summit, the temperature get warmer. Moreover, traces of activity can be seen, the roads looked to be constantly maintained, but Zhao Hai cannot see a single person yet.

When Zhao Hai was halfway up the mountain, he couldn’t help but stare. What he saw looked like a city. A stone wall was present, although it wasn’t very high, it was certainly something that a person had built.

Then Zhao Hai saw something move, it was a person. He immediately opened the monitor to look, and there he saw a leather-clad Diamond Ape Beastman.

Zhao Hai flashed into the Space and carefully looked at the city using the large screen. The city was not very big, it can probably house about 100 thousand people. The outer walls was made of large stone, it had a height of 20 meters, and a thickness of 10. On the walls, Diamond Apes can be seen on sentry duty while wearing their leather armor. Every Diamond Ape were next to their diamond ape partner, a beast 10 meters in height. These diamond apes were either sitting or lying down. They looked very docile, but Zhao Hai didn’t doubt their fighting prowess.

Another thing that made Zhao Hai surprised were their weapons. The weapons that the Diamond Apes were using were actually made of wood, they seem to have no ironware.

Their weapon looked like a thick wooden club, this club was no thinner that Zhao Hai’s arm. Moreover, it looked pitch black, but its appearance looked very sturdy.

Zhao Hai also noticed that the Diamond Apes seemed to be quite anxious. They were constantly looking for something in the distance. This made Zhao Hai feel strange, he didn’t understand why the Diamond Apes were anxious. Are there any enemies on this mountain? Even if there were, with the fighting strength of the Diamond Apes, what were they afraid of?

Zhao Hai also noticed that there were no gates on this wall. The whole stretch was made as solid as possible, there was no way out.

He was confused with such an arrangement. Even if the Diamond Apes had their giant partners to carry them, wouldn’t leaving the city be very inconvenient? Why would they do this?

While he was inspecting the walls, he discovered that there were traces of fighting present on it. The traces were very strange as well, some of it looked like it was caused by wild beasts, some looked like traces that a blade or a sword might make.

Then Zhao Hai shifted his gaze towards the city. The houses on this city were made of stone, and were of two stories, the lower one probably housed the diamond ape beasts. On the upper floor, there were some hay mats on the ground, each one occupied by a person. Anything else that was inside the houses were either made of stone or wood.

The city was quite lively, there were small Diamond Apes frolicking around the streets. Women of the Diamond Ape tribe were making leather armor, the elderly were making wooden clubs. These clubs looked just the same as the weapons that they were using. Some of the children used these clubs while learning how to fight.

Zhao Hai looked to another part of the mountain and discovered some magic beasts that were being raised. The beasts looked just like the blue eyed rabbit, but they were evidently bigger, about as big as a pig. There were a lot of these beasts, and they were partitioned by wooden fences.

After further inspection of the mountain, Zhao Hai finally discovered how these people were able to live in this place, and why trees were growing here. It was because the mountain was actually a volcano, an active volcano. The crater on it summit was constantly spewing steam.

Because the thermal energy of the volcano was negated by the cold environment, it had allowed the Diamond Apes to survive in it. It seems like this place was where the Diamond Apes had ended up in.

But Zhao Hai can also see that the overall strength of the Diamond Ape tribe had been damaged severely. Their entire race was now reduced to about 100 thousand people, and that was including the old and weak. Moreover, they seem to have met an enemy here, otherwise the guards on the walls wouldn’t be looking so anxious.

Zhao Hai took a closer look at the mountain. The area of this volcano was very huge. There were also places where traces of people can be seen. At the same time, he also found out that there wasn’t only only mountain, there were actually 13 peaks. The outer parts of this group of mountains was the only one with traces of activity.

Zhao Hai turned to the other peaks and discovered why they were virtually unexplored. The place was too hot, the only lifeforms that were able to survive here were fire element plants. Most importantly, the volcano seems to be unstable, like it could erupt at any time.

However, there weren’t a lot of lifeforms that could be seen on the other peaks. There were some fire element magic beasts, but Zhao Hai can see that their levels weren’t very high. So naturally, these beasts weren’t the enemies of the Diamond Ape tribe.

After looking through the huge mountain, Zhao Hai decided to meet the Diamond Apes in order to acquire some information. If they had found the Beast God’s spear, then it was good, but if they haven’t, a heading would still suffice.

Chapter 594: Excitement

Zhao Hai flashed out of the Space and then released Alien. He watched from inside the undead’s body as it slowly crawled towards the mountain.

Before long, Alien had arrived in front of the Diamond Ape tribe’s city. While inside Alien, Zhao Hai looked at the city with his own eyes. Just as Alien was halfway up the mountain, the people on the walls started to spot him. The Beastmen immediately took into action, the giant apes stood up, seemingly ready for combat.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when he saw what just happened, he immediately had Alien stop and then loudly introduced himself, “Beastman brothers, don’t panic. I’m not an enemy, I didn’t come to attack you.”

Zhao Hai’s words took the attention of the people on the walls. When his voice was heard, the Beastmen were shocked. Then they looked at each other in utter disbelief.

Zhao Hai understood the reactions of these Diamond Apes. They were in this place for over 5000 years. 5000 years wasn’t a short period of time, and in those years, they didn’t have any contact with the outside world. Otherwise, the Beastmen wouldn’t be clueless about their situation. Now that they heard someone else talking to them, they couldn’t help but doubt their ears.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything else. He wanted to see what the reaction of the people on the wall would be and judge whether the enemy of the Diamond Apes were beasts or people.

While thinking about these, Zhao Hai walked out of Alien’s body. He appeared in his Magic Robes and staff. After going out, he stored Alien back into his body.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai come out, the Beastmen couldn’t help but see the excitement. Zhao Hai looked at the Beastmen on the walls and couldn’t help but smile. He could imagine what these people were feeling right now.

He had no worries as he walked up to about only 12 meters away from the wall. Making the people see him clearly.

Zhao Hai looked at the wall and the Diamond Ape beastmen that were present, The Diamond Apes stood still at the walls while looking at Zhao Hai, their bodies seem to be trembling.

Then Zhao Hai gave a salute to the Diamond Apes and said, “Beastman Brothers, I’m called Zhao Hai. I came from the Beastman Prairie.”

An elderly Diamond Ape’s face looked emotional as he suddenly shouted in grief, “It’s been 5000 years! My Diamond Ape tribe…” Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please wait a bit, I’ll immediately have someone come over and get you.”

Then he gave an order to a Diamond Ape, who then brought his diamond ape down the wall and appeared in front of Zhao Hai.

The Diamond Ape beastman was more than 2 meters tall, from Zhao Hai’s eyes, they seem to be 3 meters. Zhao Hai looked at the Beastman and smiled, “Zhao Hai has seen Beastman brother.”

The Diamond Ape returned the courtesy and said, “Human Brother, did you really come from the Prairie?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I did.”

Then the Diamond Ape asked, “Can sir please tell me what the Prairie looks like?”

Zhao Hai stared, but he immediately thought that since the Diamond Apes have survived for 5000 years here, the current generation were people who hadn’t been to the Prairie before. So in their minds, the Prairie was a foreign place. To them, the Prairie was a place of legend, a beautiful place, their origin.

When Zhao Hai was about to answer the Diamond Ape, the elderly Diamond Ape shouted loudly, “Little Six, what is taking you long? Don’t ask mister any questions yet, quickly take him here.”

When this Little Six heard the old man, he embarrassingly scratched his head and said, “I’ve been unfair to mister. I actually forgot about my taks. Mister, please sit down on my Liwa’s shoulders. We’ll be taking you to the city.”

The Liwa that the Diamond Ape mentioned was naturally the gigantic ape right beside him. Zhao Hai looked at the diamond ape that was standing there like a human. It towered at a height of ten meters, it was a true colossus. For it to be called Liwa was actually very intriguing.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright.” Then Little Six beckoned to the diamond ape as it squatted and extended its hand towards Zhao Hai.

The hand opened up as Zhao Hai stood directly on it.

Then the ape placed Zhao Hai on one of its shoulders before placing Little Six on the other. Then it stood up and crawled up the wall.

It didn’t take a long time before the ape had climbed up the wall and placed Zhao Hai back down. The old Diamond Ape then arrived in front of Zhao Hai and said, “Human friend, I am Patriarch Tess of the Diamond Ape tribe.What is your purpose in coming here?”

Zhao Hai gave respects to the Patriarch before he smiled faintly and said, “Patriarch, I’ve received a task from the current Beast King to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear inside the Northern Icefield. I didn’t expect the Diamond Apes to still be living here, if I bring this news back, I’m sure the entire Beastman Race would be very shaken.”

When Tess heard Zhao Hai, his face couldn’t help but turn gloomy as he said, “My tribe is deemed to be criminals. If we return to the Prairie, we would certainly not be popular. Mister, please come with me and discuss this matter some more.”

Zhao Hai complied and then walked together with Tess towards his house. The people of the Diamond Ape tribe came over and surrounded Zhao Hai. He seemed to be regarded as an attraction, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly.

Before long, Zhao Hai and Tess finally arrived at a house. This house was quite ordinary. It didn’t have much of a difference compared to the other Diamond Ape houses.

Below the house were seven diamond apes, four big and three small. The three small apes followed Zhao Hai and Tess inside the house, the others were driven out.

Tess welcomed Zhao Hai to the second floor to see his family. Tess’ family was quite simple, he and his wife were a couple, and then he had a son and a daughter in law as well as three grandchildren.

Zhao Hai exchanged greetings with the family before they sat down. Then Tess turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, did you just say that you were sent to the Icefield by the Beast King in order to search for the Beast God’s Spear?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes. My relationship with the Beastmen is quite good. In the entire continent, it was impossible for this matter to be revealed. Because of this, the Beast King gave me an order to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear inside the Icefield.”

Tess then sighed and said, “In the past, my tribe has lost the Divine Artifact in this Northern Icefield, which was a serious offense that we had committed. In the end, the tribe was sent into exile here. It has been 5000 years since the first Diamond Apes were recorded to have penetrated the Northern Icefields, with a resolve to die here if they couldn’t retrieve the Beast God’s Spear. In the end, only 5000 members were able to reach the volcano and had settled here. We still haven’t given up in looking for the Divine Artifact. But it has not been very easy these past thousand years. We don’t know when it started, but ice beasts had started to desperately attack us. Because of them, we were forced to bunker up and defend, causing the retrieval of the Divine Artifact to be delayed.”

The only thing that Zhao Hai knew was how serious the losses of the Diamond Apes were. Stored in his Space, there were about 700 thousand Diamond Ape corpses. Surviving with 5000 people was just short of being extinct as a tribe. Only after 5000 years of development did they had manage to recover and become 100 thousand. One could clearly see how severe the price they had paid just because of the Divine Artifact.

But Zhao Hai didn’t think about these now, from what he heard from Tess, the Beast God’s Spear was still lost. It was still somewhere inside the Northern Icefield.

Zhao Hai quickly responded, “Patriarch, what were these ice beasts and ice people that you were talking about? I’ve seen some traces of attack on your walls, were they the cause of it?”

Tess sighed again and replied, “That’s right. According to the records of my tribe, these people appeared more than 1000 years ago. I don’t know what they are, but their bodies were all made up of ice, may they be in the shape of a person or a beast. Despite the composition of their bodies, they can still move freely. They didn’t seem to be intelligent, but they were very difficult to deal with. If you don’t break their heads, they would not die. Fortunately, the volcano had somewhat weakened them. Otherwise, our tribe would have already been exterminated a long time ago.”

Zhao Hai stared, it was the first time that he had heard of such a life form. He looked at Tess ands aid, “Patriarch, did you say that their bodies are all made of ice?”

Tess nodded and said, “Right, their entire bodies are comprised of ice, we’re sure of it because their bodies were somewhat transparent. When they are killed, they would immediately turn into water. They don’t look like a lifeform, but their fighting strength wasn’t very weak.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows, this was the first time that he had heard of this detail about the Northern Icefield. It was indeed worthy of being called one of the Five Forbidden Areas.

Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, has come at a tricky time. I estimate that in the coming days, those ice beings would attack. At that time, I think mister would understand after seeing them with your own eyes.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. I have also been travelling for a long time, I really need a good rest. I apologize to the Patriarch for disturbing your city.”

Tess smiled and said, “Mister is too polite. You’re our first visitor for more that 5000 years. Naturally, we would need to entertain you well.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at Tess and said, “Patriarch, while on the way here, I’ve discovered a lot of Diamond Ape corpses. I have brought those corpses with me, how would you want those to be processed?”

Tess stared, then he stood up as his expression changed, “Did Mister really bring those corpses?”

Zhao Hai also stood up as he nodded, “I did. To be honest, I’m very astonished by it. There were about 700 thousand corpses in total. If I didn’t have a Space equipment, then I simply couldn’t bring them with me. Patriarch, I really admire your tribe. For your tribe to still strive up to this point, I believe that you have already been redeemed.”

When Tess heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment before he suddenly cried and said, “Ancestors, can you hear this? Someone said that our crime has been redeemed, you can now rest in peace.” Tess’ wife, son, and daughter-in-law stood up as well.

Zhao Hai knew that the Beast God’s Spear was a huge thorn in the hearts of the Diamond Apes. He said that in order to somewhat appease their hearts. But him saying this was not without foundation. He truly thinks that the Diamond Apes have already paid enough for their crime.

After some time, Tess’ mood slowly calmed down, then he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, may I be able to see my ancestors’ remains?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he walked outside as Tess’ family immediately followed him behind. Upon arriving outside, Zhao Hai discovered that the place was full of Diamond Apes, they were all looking at him curiously. Zhao Hai smiled faintly, he felt like a monkey in a zoo, being gazed upon by onlookers.

Tess looked at the faces of these people and said, “Everyone, come to the city’s wall with me. Mister Zhao Hai just told me that he had brought the remains of our ancestors. Join me in bringing respects to them!”

Upon hearing Tess, the surrounding Diamond Apes turned silent for a moment before an uproar came about. They immediately passed the news around, and before long, every person in the city came to know about it.

Zhao Hai knew how the Beastmen regarded their ancestors. For Zhao Hai to bring their ancestors’ bodies with him was already a huge gesture of kindness towards the Diamond Apes.

Zhao Hai didn’t waste time. As he got on the wall with Tess, and then down again to the area outside, he immediately released the petrified corpses.

Tess looked at the corpses on the ground as tears came flowing out of his eyes. He gently walked towards on of the corpses, and then as he was sobbing he said, “This is indeed my ancestors’ remains. At that time, because they were afraid that the corpses would disintegrate in the harsh environment of the Icefield, they decided to place the bodies inside their companions. The skin of a diamond ape would slowly petrify as soon as it dies, allowing it to protect what was inside its body. Since they were hurrying along, they can only resort to this method of burial.”

Zhao Hai only released about a hundred corpses before he stopped. The area outside the wall was too small, it was impossible to release every single corpse. Therefore, he just released a hundred before turning to Tess and said, “Patriarch, the corpses are just too many. I cannot place them all down here, what do we do?”

Tess looked at the remains and sighed, “I’ll have to trouble mister to bring the remains down the mountain and then release them into the Icefield. After we give our respects, then we would be cremating them.”

Zhao Hai then asked, “Cremate? How come I couldn’t remember any ritual of cremation among the Beastmen?”

Tess nodded and said, “That’s true, there wasn’t a ceremony of cremation among the Beastmen. But our Diamond Ape clan decided to do it as a form of gratitude to the life that was given to use by this volcano. Since the time we settled here, we had changed our death ceremonies into cremation.”

Chapter 595: Cremation

Zhao Hai nodded, he can understand their decision. They thought that they were about to be eliminated and then suddenly a place like this appeared that can allow them to live. In this case, it wouldn’t be strange for them to grab the opportunity. Not wonder, even for the Beastmen to have not done cremation before, they decided to do so right now.

But Zhao Hai thought about it and decided to remind Tess, he opened his mouth and said, “Patriarch Tess, my Space is very big. If I can find the Beast God’s Spear, I can bring these remains back to the Prairie. How about burying them back there?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Tess couldn’t help but stare, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Is mister telling the truth? Is it possible for you to take these remains back to the Prairie?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’s true.”

Tess looked at the remains, and then he looked back at the mountain. He sighed lightly and then shook his head, “Forget it, we’ll go through with the cremation. My tribe would still look for the Beast God’s Spear. But I think we don’t have a place to return to anymore.”

Zhao Hai looked at Tess and said, “Patriarch, I came this time to seek the Beast God’s Spear, and I’m confident in being able to find it. If I retrieve the Divine Artifact, then can’t you return to the Prairie by then?”

Tess looked at Zhao Hai and then smiled bitterly, “Mister, to tell you the truth, what’s the point of our tribe returning to the Prairie? Our Diamond Ape tribe has a magnificent past, we were once the Royal Clan of the Beastman Race. But our entire tribe has been exiled here, and was now reduced to 100 thousand members. Even if we return to the Prairie, what can we obtain? Can our small tribe of 100 thousand people survive there? Won’t the present Royal Tribe see us as a threat? Mister, to be honest, we do long for the Prairie, but at the same time, we are also afraid to return.”

Zhao Hai was shaken, he didn’t think that Tess would have thought this far. Are they really the Beastman tribe that was known to be straightforward? This was a wise old man who had already seen the world.

Zhao Hai knew that what Tess said was true. The status of the Diamond Apes was too awkward. They were the previous Royal tribe, and was now reduced to a small tribe of 100 thousand members. Even if they have formidable fighting strength, what would they bring when they go back to the Prairie? The other Beastmen were already used to being under the rule of the Lion and Tiger races. If another Royal tribe returns, then things would get complicated.

Because one couldn’t exist along with the other, it was inevitable that a war would happen. Once their status was be placed on the line, the Lion and Tiger races wouldn’t give the Diamond Apes any opportunity, Therefore, being suppressed and eventually withering away was a possible outcome for them.

Zhao Hai sighed, he didn’t say anything more, he turned around and then stored the remains back into the Space. He then led the people of the Diamond Ape tribe down the mountain, When they reached the flat icefield, Zhao Hai immediately released all of the corpses before silently going off to the side.

Tess and the other members of the Diamond Ape tribe carried on with their rituals. Their ceremony was very simple, they killed some magic beasts and then made some rituals on bended knees. There weren’t a lot going on. However, the Diamond Apes wept upon seeing their people who have died. These were their ancestors.

After some time, Tess went to Zhao Hai as he bowed and said, “We thank mister Zhao Hai. We’ll have to ask mister to please take these remains to the summit.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then received the corpses again. Then together with Tess and the others, they began to walk towards the summit. The higher they went up, the higher the temperature became, but that didn’t matter. When Zhao Hai arrived at the summit, he saw a huge crater. It was round, and was spewing white gas into the air, one could even see faint signs of fire here and there.

Zhao Hai looked carefully and saw that under this crater was a magma pool. The magma inside was tumbling around, but it doesn’t look like it was about to erupt.[1]

Under the request of Tess, Zhao Hai dropped the bodies into the crater as the Diamond Apes resumed their ceremony Then they returned to the city, Zhao Hai was led by Tess back to his home.

When they arrived back home, Tess’ wife and daughter-in-law went to prepare for dinner while Tess, his son, and Zhao Hai sat on the living room. Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, can you tell us briefly about the current state of the Prairie?”

Zhao Hai didn’t decline, he nodded and then spoke up. He had a complete understanding of the Prairie at this point, so it wasn’t a problem for him to tell them.

Actually, even after 5000 years has passed by, there weren’t a lot of developments in the continent. Even the magic system remained virtually unchanged, the same was true for the Beastmen. The only thing fairly new was the fact that the Beastmen can now use the soul of their beasts in order to cultivate. They had also learned how to look for appropriate beast souls as well as appropriate mounts.

But one shouldn’t look down on this achievement, the Beastmen had done a lot of tests in order to achieve this point. In turn, it managed to increase their overall strength. Just imagine the difference between beastmen riding common bulls versus beastmen that were riding their exclusive mounts.

Five thousand years was quite a long time, even some of the Beastmen had changed their weapons in this period. But all of these 5000 years of change wasn’t recorded on the Diamond Ape tribe’s books.

Tess’ wife and daughter-in-law were already done making their meal, but Tess was still not willing to move. He was too deeply focused on Zhao Hai’s narration.

Only after his wife had called him several times did Tess woke up from his stupor, he looked at Zhao Hai embarrassingly and said, “I’ve been unfair to mister, let’s go have a meal first.”

Zhao Hai nodded with a smile, then he went along with Tess’ family to the dining room. The place wasn’t very big, and the inside only had ordinary wooden furniture. All of the things inside were either made of wood or made of stone. It was nearly impossible to see any ironware. If there were 1 or 2, those ironware were still heavily damaged due to prolonged use.

Zhao Hai didn’t laugh at them, after all, Beastmen weren’t good in handling iron. Moreover, from the looks of it, there weren’t any iron deposits that can be seen in the vicinity. And even ironware was already considered to be a miracle if the Diamond Apes were able to bring them along in the first place.

However, one couldn’t just devalue these people, they still had some sort of talent in them. From what Zhao Hai can see, the things in Tess’ house that used wood or stone were made very well. They were very smooth to the touch and even the stone knife looked very sharp.

They used a stone pot and a stone slab in order to cook the food. They didn’t have much of a flavor, but it still tasted very good. And most importantly, they also had their own wine here. When Zhao Hai asked, the wine was made from a fruit that can be found in the mountain. The fruit had a sweet taste, it was very good.

After having eaten their meal, the group returned to the living room. Then Zhao Hai resumed talking to them about the matters of the continent. The Beastmen, the Humans, all of those things were told to Tess.

Although Zhao Hai’s narration wasn’t comprehensive, he still finished talking deep into the night. Only after Zhao Hai was done did Tess and the others noted that it was already very late. They immediately prepared a room for Zhao Hai, asking him to rest.

After Zhao Hai entered his room, he immediately flashed to the Space. Even if it was late, Laura and the others were still not asleep, they were currently in the living room, chatting.

Seeing that Zhao Hai has arrived, Laura immediately smiled and said, “Brother Hai, you finally came back. You look very tired, Haha.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, he was far more than tired. He felt that his throat was about to emit smoke, moreover it was also very painful. If he didn’t treat it, then he might not be able to talk tomorrow.

Zhao Hai immediately drank a cup of Spatial Water. After feeling well, he turned to Laura and said, “I can’t help it. Tess is too enthusiastic. Why haven’t you gone to rest, did something happen?”

Zhao Hai already told Laura and the others that he had something to do outside, so they can just rest ahead of time. But it appeared to be useless, the women didn’t listen to him.

Laura smiled and said, “Something did came up. Brother Hai, you seem to have forgotten since you’ve been focused on the Icefield for one month. We think it should be time for the Buddha Empire to get the first batch of magic beasts.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he couldn’t help but smack his own head, “I forgot. Good, please arranged for it. Right, did the fleet from Golden Island arrive?”

Laura smiled and said, “They’re already on the coastlines of the Prairie. I’ll have them stop for a couple of days before going back. After all, 4000 beasts aren’t that much. If we make them stop there for too long, people might get suspicious.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll hand this matter off to you. It would be best if the beasts get as minimal contact with the Space as possible. If they get promoted inside, then it would be very troublesome.”

Laura and the others couldn’t help but chuckle. Others were afraid that their magic beasts wouldn’t be able to improve. Only their group were an exception, they were actually afraid of their magic beasts levelling up too quickly. If this was revealed to the outside world, people would kill them.

After some time, Lizzy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, does the Diamond Apes really not want to return to the Prairie?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he told them about the worries of Tess. After listening to Zhao Hai, Laura and the others couldn’t help but nod. They understood Tess’ worries. This matter was quite common, after all, no race wanted to give up their authority.

If it was the past Diamond Ape tribe, then it wouldn’t be a problem since they possess tyrannical strength. But now they were reduced into a small tribe, they don’t have the ability to rule anymore.

* * *

But I’m pretty sure dumping 700 thousand bodies in one go would cause a reaction xD

Chapter 596: Hiring Oneself

The political struggles of the Beastmen were much more worse than the Humans, and Laura and the others had experienced these things. Therefore, when they heard what Zhao Hai had said, they immediately knew what was going on.

Lizzy knit her brows for a moment before her eyes suddenly lit up, “Big Brother Hai, so you’re saying that it would be impossible for the Diamond Apes to return to the Prairie? If that’s so, then how about inviting them over to the Black Wasteland?”

Zhao Hai stared, he had not thought about it until Lizzy reminded him. If Tess and the others don’t want to return to the Prairie, then how about having them go to the Black Wasteland? The Black Wasteland was also very huge, he had also planted some grass on the still unoccupied lands. At this point those grasses should have healthily spread.

Wales was still in severe need of manpower right now, so the slaves still cannot be given to Zhao Hai. If the Diamond Apes were to settle in the Black Wasteland, then the current deficit would be solved.

Although they had lived for 5000 years on that mountain, Zhao Hai can see that the Diamond Apes haven’t given up in their tradition of herding. They were mainly focused on herding, there doesn’t seem to be much farming going on. Because of this, having them herd in the Black Wasteland would be quite feasible.

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai couldn’t bear but nod repeatedly and said, “That is a good idea. If we can invite them, then we would have an additional 100 thousand people that can help us. Moreover, the fighting strength of the Diamond Apes are strong. Having them with us will give the family another trump card.”

Megan nodded and said, “That would be very great. Moreover, Elder Brother Hai, I think Tess would ask you tomorrow about why you agreed to seek the Beast God’s Spear. You can use that opportunity to tell him about the matter with the Divine Realm. Then you can see if they would like to come with us. If they don’t want to, then that would not be a problem. But I think they would agree, after all, without our help, it would be impossible for them to go out of the Icefield.”

Laura smiled and said, “I also think that they would agree. They have lived in this volcano while in constant worry about it erupting. We can help them go live in a new environment, there’s no reason for them to oppose to it.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Who knows, maybe they have the ability to return, but they just chose not to. Alright, let’s go take a rest. Tomorrow, all of these matters would be settled.” Then he walked towards his room while pulling Laura. Laura’s face couldn’t help but turn red while Lizzy and the others were chuckling.

The next morning, Zhao Hai went out of Meg’s room (this is not a mistake, he also went there. Hahaha) Then he went out of the space and returned to the room that was given to him by Tess.[1]

Although one could say that Zhao Hai had practically zero rest, it didn’t affect him much since he was now a 9th rank expert. He didn’t feel any tiredness at all.

When Zhao Hai returned to his room, he arranged his clothes before going out. He didn’t see Tess anywhere, but he didn’t care about it. He went out quite early today, this was because he wanted to see get some unique beasts and plants from this volcano. Even if they cannot increase it’s level, it can still provide some experience.

Zhao Hai came out of the Tess’ house and saw that there were already quite a few people outside. These people had just woke up and were preparing for their work. Most of these people were elderly. Their jobs were quite simple, and it was to sweep the streets of the city. The fighting strength of older people had waned, so they weren’t suitable for defending the city. Therefore, the only thing that they could do was this.

Zhao Hai greeted these old people with a smile while the old people quickly returned the courtesy. They were very grateful to Zhao Hai because he brought the remains of their ancestors over, which was also one of their concerns.

After greeting the elderly people, Zhao Hai went to the wall. After seeing Zhao Hai, the guards immediately gave him a salute, of which Zhao Hai returned the gesture. After his salute, Zhao Hai informed them about his intentions before he summoned Alien and went out of the city.

He didn’t want to fly here, since it would make the Diamond Apes know about his strength. Therefore, he summoned Alien to be his transport.

Outside of the city was a forest, so Zhao Hai had alien patrol it for a while. Whenever he saw any unique plants and so on, he would immediately absorb them into the Space. Although the prompts kept coming, there was no notification regarding a level up. Zhao Hai already expected this, so he didn’t feel anything strange.

Alien was quick, and with the recent promotion of the Space, its might had also gone up. As long they weren’t 8th rank, Alien can forcefully catch them and store them into the Space. Because of this, Zhao Hai was comfortable and just sat inside as he left all the work for Alien.

It didn’t take a long time before Zhao Hai finished patrolling the mountain that the Diamond Apes were living in. The mountain did have some good plants and animals in it. It might be because it was a volcano, but most of them had the fire attribute. Although the Space didn’t level up, it’s fire attribute had been increase. This was a kind of success for Zhao Hai.

After touring the mountain, Zhao Hai felt that it was time, so he immediately headed towards the Diamond Apes’ city. He figured that it was about the time where most people would wake up.

As expected, when Alien arrived at the city, most people have already got up. Tess was in the wall and had been waiting for his return. Upon seeing Zhao Hai come back, Tess couldn’t help but feel relief.

After sharing a breakfast, Tess invited Zhao Hai to the living room. After sitting down, Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, yesterday I asked you about the matters of the continent and discovered that the present relationship between the Humans and Beastmen wasn’t very good. Moreover, they even had a recent war. I want to ask why did the Beast King trusted Mister with the task of retrieving the Beast God’s Spear?”

Zhao Hai already expected this question yesterday, so he had thought of an excuse. He told Tess his status in the Prairie as well as him being a Foreign Elder of the Dwarves. At the same time, he also presented a token, it seemed to be made out of beast bone and it had a carving of the word King(王) on it.”

Naturally, this wasn’t the Beast King’s command token, but instead, it was the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince token. The Beast King gave this token to Zhao Hai. In any case, if Zhao Hai can retrieve the Divine Artifact, he would become the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince. And if Zhao Hai failed, then it was probable that he would perish in the Icefield. Therefore, the Beast King giving this token in advance wasn’t much of a big deal.

When Zhao Hai showed the Foreign Prince token, Tess immediately believed him. This was because this Foreign Prince token was illustrated in their tribe records. Moreover, this token originated with the Diamond Apes. But they gave this token to a Dwarf Master Artisan instead of a Human.

Tess gave the token back to Zhao Hai and then said, “Mister, you said that something was about to happen in the continent. And the help of the Beast God’s Spear was required. May I ask what this matter is?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he narrated the prophecy of the Dwarf Race as well as Iron Hammer’s words. He told Tess about the latest movements of the Radiant Church. He didn’t hide anything from Tess since, just like Megan said, if the Diamond Apes doesn’t have his aid, then it would be impossible for them to leave the Icefield. And if Tess agreed to his help, then it would be similar to the Diamond Apes being his people, so there was no need to be on guard.

Although Zhao Hai admired the Diamond Apes, he couldn’t just have sympathy take the upper hand in this matter. If the Diamond Apes don’t agree to move to the Black Wasteland, then Zhao Hai wouldn’t reveal the existence of the Space to them. This was because it still wasn’t time to reveal the Space.

While listening to Zhao Hai, Tess’ brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. He didn’t think that while his tribe stayed in the Icefield for 5000 years, the events in the outside world had surprisingly developed to this point. Moreover, the Beast God’s Spear was now needed more than before.

Zhao Hai looked at Tess’ expression and decided to not disturb him. He just sat there quietly as he took a sip of water. Tess turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Is mister completely confident in retrieving the Beast God’s Spear?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Almost completely. It shouldn’t be a problem. You should know that since I was able to come here, I should have the ability to retrieve it.”

Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I heard from mister that you are a Human noble. So you should have your own fief. Mister, I need your help. I hope you can agree to it.”

When Zhao Hai heard Tess, he couldn’t help but gawk. This was because Tess’ statement was equal to him telling Zhao Hai that he wishes for the Diamond Apes to hire themselves to him on their own initiative.

Zhao Hai nodded immediately and said, “Yes, I’m a Marquis of the Rosen Empire. My territory is very big.”

Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “If my Diamond Ape tribe hires ourselves to mister, does mister have a way for us to exit the Icefield?”

Zhao Hao looked at Tess before he nodded and said, “I do, not only could I take you out of the Icefield, I can also provide you a place to herd on. I can make your children go to school, and also have your own tribe manage by yourselves. But after going to my fief, unless I give permission, you won’t be able to go out.”

Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Can I ask where Mister’s fief is?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Black Wasteland!”

Tess stared, he looked confused at Zhao Hai as he said, “Mister, did you just say Black Wasteland? That land has someone occupying it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’m the one occupying it. And nobody in the continent except people my family trusted knew that I was able to put it to good use. That’s why I said that you won’t be able to leave my land without my permission.”

Tess looked at Zhao Hai in shock, “Is mister really telling the truth? Are you really occupying the Black Wasteland? Right, can I ask mister how you’re planning to take us out of the Icefield?”

Zhao Hai looked at Tess, he smiled faintly and then said, “I ask Patriarch to relax your body. I’ll make you know in a moment. Regardless of what happens, Patriarch should not panic.” Then with an intention, he moved the two of them to Black Wasteland’s Iron Mountain Fort.

* * *

The parenthesis was the actual author putting in a comment

Chapter 597: Red Crystal

Zhao Hai didn’t bring Tess to the Space, he just directly teleported themselves to the Black Wasteland. The two appeared inside Iron Mountain Fort’s living area.

He’d rather make people aware that he has a Space Divergent Ability rather than revealing the existence of the Space. Although Space Divergent Abilities were rare, their existence were known in the continent. On the other hand, the Space was entirely unique, it was impossible for the continent to have such a thing.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was now very conscious of his conduct. Only those he trusted were able to know about the Space. For the others, the most they can know was him having some sort of Space Divergent Ability.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also didn’t want others to know about the current state of the Black Wasteland. He was afraid that the people would attribute the changes of the Black Wasteland to him.

In the past, he didn’t want the people to think that he had any skill in refining or alchemy. If people came to know that the Black Wasteland has been improved, he would have no way to justify it.

However, he wasn’t afraid of people asking about it right now. In the past he couldn’t find a reason. But now that he has the Processing Machine, as long as he provides the materials, it can make basically everything.

Zhao Hai thinks that being low key is good. After all, the area of the Black Wasteland was very big. If people came to know that it was now usable, greedy eyes would be staring at it.

Tess looked around him in shock. He didn’t think that he would instantly be transported into another place. He suddenly remembered something written in their tribe records about formidable Divergent Abilities in the continent.

One must know that the records of the Diamond Apes wasn’t broken even after they were exiled to the Icefield. They didn’t give up in their task of recording everything.

Because of this, the records of the Diamond Apes were as complete as it can be. Therefore, even when being exiled for 5000 years, Tess was still aware of the existence of Divergent Abilities as well as the existence of the most formidable one of them all, Space Divergent Abilities. In the past, even Beastmen were able to acquire such an ability, which explains why it had also appeared in their records.

Tess looked at Zhao Hai with shining eyes as he said, “Was that a Space Divergent Ability?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, it’s my Space Divergent Ability. Moreover, my ability is special, not only could I do teleportation, I can also make a Spatial Passage. It would allow people to pass through and immediately arrive here, in the Black Wasteland. This gave me the confidence to claim that I can bring you here.”

Tess was moved, he couldn’t help but say, “Good, fantastic. Thank you so much Mister.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Don’t worry about it. We still have to prepare the place where you’ll be settling in. Let’s head out and see the territory.”

Then Zhao Hai brought Tess to the fort’s exit. When the Giant Horned Bulls saw Tess, they couldn’t help but gawk. The expressions of the Giant Horned Bulls can be understood. After all, it has been 5000 years before a Diamond Ape was spotted in the continent.

The Giant Horned Bulls saw them but they didn’t know who Tess was. Although they knew that he was an ape Beastman, Tess was different from those that they had seen before. This made them very puzzled, explaining how they looked at Tess. Tess hurried towards one Giant Horned Bull, then he said, “Beastman Brother, what tribe are you?”

Tess question made the Giant Horned Bull gawk. Although they were tribes in the Prairie that cannot be classified at first glance, the Giant Horned Bulls were the most recognizable tribe among the Beastman. Their two large horns wasn’t something that people can just ignore.

The Giant Horned Bull rubbed the horn on his head, he thought that maybe his horns have shrunk. Otherwise, why would this Beastman ask about his tribe?

Zhao Hai saw the confused appearance of the Giant Horned Bull, so he smiled faintly and said, “Arpurt, don’t be surprised. It’s true that he cannot recognize you. This person is from the Diamond Ape tribe. They had lived in the Northern Icefield.”[1]

The Giant Horned Bull named Arpurt stared blankly, then he muttered, “Diamond Ape tribe, what tribe is the Diamond Ape tribe?” Then after a moment he was suddenly stunned, he looked at Tess with shining eyes as he asked, “The exiled Royal Tribe, the Diamond Apes? Some of you have survived? Oh my god!!”

When Tess heard Arpurt exclaim, he couldn’t help but be moved as he said, “I didn’t expect that people would still remember our tribe. I am indeed from the Diamond Ape tribe.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then said, “Patriarch Tess, these brothers are from the Giant Horned Bull tribe. Last year, they had come across a disaster in the Prairie, their tribe had been attacked. Therefore, we led them here. Now, they had settled in Iron Mountain Fort.”

Arpurt looked at Tess with an expression of disbelief, he looked very silly. In fact, who could act normal in such a situation. A race that had vanished for about 5000 years suddenly appearing in front of them, this was inconceivable.

When Tess heard Zhao Hai that Arpurt was from the Giant Horned Bull tribe, he immediately believed him judging by how huge Arpurt’s horns were. He immediately looked at Arpurt and said, “Beastman Brother, hello.” He didn’t know what to say. It seems like he wanted to say a lot, but he just didn’t know how to say it.

Arpurt recovered and then looked at Tess and said, “Are you really from the Diamond Ape tribe? Did you really go to the Northern Icefield? How did you manage to survive there?”

At this time, those working in Iron Mountain Fort who had noticed the commortion had already come over. When the people of the Giant Horned Bull tribe heard Arpurt, they couldn’t help but stare at Tess in disbelief.

After some time, Green and Merine had come and had the situation be under control. Then Green and Merine invited Tess to the living room while inviting Ares and Aria over. The two were now deemed to be the elders of the Giant Horned Bulls. It would be best if Tess talks to them.

ZHao Hai didn’t say anything and just had Ares and Aria bring Tess to explore Iron Mountain Fort. Zhao Hai believed that as they talk with each other, Tess would understand the life at the fort. Therefore, he didn’t have to worry.

Sure enough, Tess went out for a long time with Ares. And when he came back, Tess had a meal with Zhao Hai and the others. The face of Tess went red, it was quite clear that he had become drunk.

When Tess returned to the fort’s living room, Zhao Hai immediately looked at him and said, “Patriarch Tess, we should head back. If we’re gone for a long time, your people would start to get worried.”

Tess nodded, he had already asked Ares about the questions that was on his mind, so he was quite satisfied with today’s trip. It was already time for them to return.

Zhao Hai led Tess as their bodies flashed and returned to the Diamond Apes’ city. They didn’t flash inside their room instantly, but instead looked for a place where nobody was present.

Tess looked at the surroundings and knew instantly that they had come back. Then he walked towards his house along with Zhao Hai. Just shortly after they had returned, they had met a Diamond Ape, when the ape saw Tess he immediately said, “Patriarch, you’re here. Aunt has been looking for you.”

Tess nodded and said, “Thanks.” Then he went back to his house along with Zhao Hai. The family still hadn’t eaten yet, they were still waiting for the two to arrive.

Seeing the two come back, Tess’ wife couldn’t help but complain to him several times. She berated him about not coming back in time for meal. But when she saw that they had already eaten, she didn’t say anything.

While Tess had them eat their meal, he was sitting on the living room with Zhao Hai. After they had sat down, Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I still need to discuss this matter with the elders. I hope you can give me some time.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, you don’t have to worry. After all, the place and supplies for your tribe would have to be prepared. It’ll be fine if we go a bit later. But meanwhile, I’ll go head to the mountains and explore to see if there are any rare plants and animals present.”

Tess nodded and said, “Mister, do you need someone to guide you?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No need. I’m just casually strolling around. Do you think there are any beings in this mountain that can threaten my safety?”

Tess nodded and said, “There aren’t any formidable magic beasts in this mountain. But the third peak, fifth peak, and seventh peak must not be explored. Those mountains are quite unstable, they might randomly spew out high temperature fire. Mister should be careful, people aren’t able to come back after exploring those areas.”

Zhao Hai nodded before he stood up and gave Tess a salute. Then he turned around to walk outside. Seeing Zhao Hai leave, Tess immediately headed out and sent word to the various houses of the elders, calling them over for a meeting. They must reach a decision at the shortest possible time.

Zhao Hai didn’t really care about any of these. To be honest, he didn’t really place great importance to the decision that Tess and the others would make. After all, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to send them to the Prairie using his ability. The only place they can go to would be the Black Wasteland. Otherwise, Zhao Hai would stop caring about them and then going forth to continue his search. The Black Wasteland’s secrets cannot be revealed, so it would be careless for Zhao Hai to just have Tess reveal it.

Zhao Hai sat inside Alien as it walked into the forest and headed directly to the second peak. This mountain peak wasn’t as tall as the mountain that Tess’ tribe were living in. Moreover, it wasn’t very far from the third peak. Zhao Hai can clearly see what Tess just warned him, the third peak was actually a volcano that would erupt once in a while. This was the reason why Tess and the others decided to live on the first peak.

After leaving the first peak, Alien immediately slammed his tail on the ground as it directly flew towards the second peak. The distance between the two peaks wasn’t short. If Alien just walked, it would take them a lot of time.

Since Zhao Hai’s undead had become 9th ranks, it was natural that they were now able to fly on the air. Which made it even more convenient for Zhao Hai to travel.

The second peak didn’t have much things. From what Zhao Hai can tell, this second peak was just like an extinct volcano. It’s crater was black and had nothing in it. Zhao Hai stopped caring about it as his gaze turned towards the third peak.

The third peak was very different from the second peak. Zhao Hai can just feel how high the temperature was just from where he was standing. Even at the foot of the mountain, the temperature was still higher than back in the Diamond Apes’ city.

Plants were actually very rare in the third peak. The ones who populated the area were fire element magic beasts. Zhao Hai naturally wouldn’t let this opportunity go as he received the plants as well as the beasts into the Space. But although he had absorbed a lot, the Space still didn’t levelup.

While Zhao Hai was collecting, he proceeded further up the volcano. He was very curious and wanted to look at what’s present on top of the mountain.

Before long, he arrived at the summit where the temperature was very high. If one were to drop an egg on the ground, it would definitely turn into an omelette immediately. But this temperature didn’t affect Zhao Hai as well as Alien, so they proceeded to go take a closer look at the crater.

The crater looked like a giant stove that constantly spat out fire. Less than 50 meters away from the crater, magma can be seen tumbling about.

Zhao Hai looked at the magma with his eyes as he prepared to get down and observe it. However, he suddenly discovered something that made him stop.

It was a piece of red Crystal, it glittered and was translucent. It was very attractive, the crystal wasn’t very far from the crater. Moreover, it was a very big piece.

Zhao Hai curiously looked at the stone as he had a Spatial Rift appear and absorbed the red crystal.

When the crystal reached the Space, a prompt was then heard, “High energy crystal has been detected. Contains a huge amount of heat energy. The energy is stable and can be used. May produce energy equal to 100 thousand watts. This crystal can be reusable. Once it runs out of energy, it can just be placed on a source and reabsorb some energy.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This energy of this red crystal managed to move him. This thing can actually store a lot, and it can be recharged as well. He can now use it to provide energy in the future, this was a very good thing for the family.

Zhao Hai immediately opened the monitor and asked Cai’er to look at the other mountain peaks and search for other red crystals.

The Space’s ability to search was very good, it didn’t take too long before they had found more red crystals, whose sizes weren’t not small either. Zhao Hai immediately opened a rift and absorbed them into the Space before continuing on his search. But after searching around the three mountains, he wasn’t able to find any more crystals.

Zhao Hai then had the monitor look at the other ten mountains. To be honest, the other mountains weren’t as suitable for living as the second and first peaks. But on those two peaks, it was impossible to find red crystals easily. Among the crystals that Zhao Hai had already gotten, 60 percent of it was all produced by the third peak.

* * *

I always get confused by this. My mind always thought that Tess was present 5000 years ago. xD Basically the current generation of Diamond Apes haven’t seen other Beastmen before.

Chapter 598: Red Crystal Ore

Originally, Zhao Hai was searching these mountain peaks with the mindset of finding nothing. Since he had some free time, he might as well collect some things here. But now it wa different, after discovering the red crystal, he immediately thought about how great this thing would be in supplying energy.

The continent also had crystal stones, and Zhao Hai had gotten samples of these for the Space to absorb. But the Space’s evaluation of the crystal was that it was a low-energy consumable, without any way of recharging. This made Zhao Hai disappointed in the crystal.

However, this red crystal was different, after using up the energy inside this crystal, it can be recharged. Most importantly, the energy that the red crystal can store was vastly bigger than the ordinary ones. What can 100 thousand watts do? Zhao Hai didn’t calculate it, but he reckoned it would do a lot.

Between the first to third peaks, Zhao Hai had already gathered about 160 red crystals. Together, all of them can reach about 1 billion watts. What concept was this? Zhao Hai had some headache thinking about it before he became happy.

Energy, no matter what kind, was a good. It was something that anyone in the world was vying for. And this red crystal can store a lot. As long as Zhao Hai collects more of it, then he would have a lot of energy available for the future.

Zhao Hai sat inside Alien as it flew towards the fourth peak. The situation at this peak was better than the third peak since it wasn’t as hot as the third peak.

However, Zhao Hai was not paying attention to the temperature. He didn’t take any plants or beasts either, after all, he had already collected some back at the first three peaks. What Zhao Hai was on the look for at this time were those red crystals.

After scouring at fourth peak, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get disappointed. All in all, he had only discovered about more than 50 red crystals here. These crystals were small as well, about the size of a fist. Zhao Hai also expected these crystals to have differences in size and quality. For example, the first crystal that Zhao Hai had found was as big as a basketball, so it was natural that it can contain a large amount of energy. These fist sized crystals on the fourth peak can carry only about 5000 kilowatts of energy, it had a difference of about 20 times.

Zhao Hai sighed as he received the 50 crystals. Then he proceeded and flew towards the fifth peak, another dangerous place that Tess had told him. Zhao Hai hopes to gain good harvests there.

Before long, Zhao Hai had arrived at the fifth peak. This fifth peak was very similar to the third. Its heat was actually hotter than the third peak. Moreover, it also had more fire element magic beasts.

Zhao Hai didn’t pay attention to these magic beasts. His attention was fully in seeking the red crystals. However, the fifth peak seem to have special characteristics. The red crystals in this mountain was buried deep. If Zhao Hai wanted to obtain them, he would need to dig through the mountain.

Fortunately, the monitor can see underground, otherwise, Zhao Hai would take a long time before finding these crystals. Zhao Hai took his time collecting the crystals one by one. The quality of these crystals were higher than the fourth peak. Each of the crystals were about the size of a football. Zhao Hai has yet to see another basketball sized crystal.

The monitor’s sight wasn’t very deep, it can only penetrate through 500 meters of land. But after arriving at that 500 meters, Zhao Hai can see 500 meters further.

Zhao Hai was now a kilometer beneath the fifth peak. Such a distance wasn’t short, but this didn’t affect Zhao Hai. He already has magic as well as his earth Divergent Ability. So he wasn’t encumbered much at this depth. At this point, the only thing in his mind were those red crystals.

At this time, Cai’er appeared in front of Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, it looks like there’s a mineral lode underneath.”

Zhao Hai said, “Mineral lode? You say that there is a red crystal lode?”

Cai’er nodded and said, “Yes, there’s a red crystal lode not far under here.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he said, “Then let’s go there immediately, I want to take a look.”

Caier then said, “Young Master, that mineral lode is probably under a lake of magma. But from my analysis, the magma isn’t a huge threat to you. But the Young Master would have to keep your focus.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he knew how formidable the analysis of the Space was. What Cai’er said meant that the magma wouldn’t affect him too much, but he would still experience some troubles.

However, to obtain these red crystals, this small trouble was no big deal.  Zhao Hai slowly came out of Alien. Until now, he has been sitting inside its body and didn’t enter the Space. If he was in the Space, then he was afraid that Laura and the others wouldn’t allow him to go.

Moving forward, Zhao Hai was very focused and was paying attention to the monitor at the same time. He wanted to frequently know what was in front of him. Before long, he discovered that in a place 10 meters below him was magma. Zhao Hai then casted Earth magic on himself while also using his Earth Divergent Ability. He believed that in this way, he can penetrate the earth with the smoothest way possible. He was afraid of making a huge impact at this place since it might cause the volcano to erupt.

After reaching ten meters away from the magma, Zhao Hai stopped and inspected it carefully. After seeing that there wasn’t anything special inside, he immediately plunged into it along with Alien.

A dozen of meters away, Zhai Hai popped up and saw that he was in a rock chamber and a magma river. The magma flowed constantly, everything that Zhao Hai saw was red, like molten iron.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of this as he controlled his fired Divergent Ability and dispelled the heat from the magma before diving down again.

It was fortunate that the magma river wasn’t too deep. After Zhao Hai dived for a short time, he had finally reached the bottom of the river. He immediately merged with the earth underneath the magma river. These rockes weren’t red crystals, therefore Zhao Hai can use his Earth ability to merge into it, then he relaxed.

Although he can control fire, and the difference between controlling earth and fire was nonexistent, he still didn’t want to stay in the magma. The feeling of being immersed in hot rocks was different from being surrounded by earth. The pressure inside the magma was just too great.

After passing the magma river, Zhao Hai dove an additional ten meters before he arrived at the red crystal ores. This ore wasn’t very large, it had the thickness of about 100 meters. It also wasn’t made up entirely of red crystal, there were also rocks and soil here and there, only a few parts of it were red crystals. However, the crystal ores in this location was much higher than the mountains.

Zhao Hai proceeded to start collecting the crystals in this lode. It was worthy of being called a lode. The crystals were quickly collected with great speed. This lode was not long, probably only spanning a few of these volcanoes. After collecting all of the red crystals here, Zhao Hai had now over 10 thousand red crystals in his possession.

After Zhao Hai collected the final piece of crystal, he immediately went out and discovered that he was already in the tenth peak. But he didn’t care, at this time, there was a piece of red crystal in his hand. This red crystal was not like the other ones. The other red crystals can just be described as fiery crystals, but one could tell at a glance that they were crystal stones. If a person was not knowledgeable, they would just see it as a big gemstone.

But the crystal held by Zhao Hai was more red than the others. It also seemed to have some warmth in it, completely different to the others. The crystal looked just like a fireball.

Zhao Hai absorbed the crystal to the Space, the analysis of the crystal was that it was incomplete, it also has pure energy that would transform the surrounding rocks into red crystals. One could say that this thing was equal to pure iron. It was akin to being a source of red crystals. Zhao Hai buried the crystal underground and maybe it can produce some more red crystals in the future.

Zhao Hai inspected the crystal and couldn’t find anything else on it. This was the reason he just buried it in the Space. After all, he already had more red crystals than he could use at the moment.

And while Zhao Hai was flying towards the first peak, he discovered that the temperature on the 13 peaks seemed to have changed slightly. It seems like they weren’t as hot as before.

Zhao Hai gawked, and then thought that it might be possibly related to him taking out the red crystal ore. He had dug a lot of red crystals, so no wonder the magma wouldn’t be as hot as before.

But most importantly, he had unearthed the red crystal mother. This thing can produce red crystals. But unfortunately, it was incomplete, this somewhat disappointed Zhao Hai.

He was now afraid that the volcanoes would get extinguished, which was disadvantageous to his plan. Although Iron Mountain Fort already had enough equipment to support 100 thousand people moving over, it still needed a few days to prepare. If this volcano turned cold, then he would have to deliver the Diamond Apes ahead of time.

But after Zhao Hai saw that the magma on the seventh peak was still tumbling and didn’t have any looks of weakening, he immediately felt relief. Then he had Alien fly towards the first peak.

After Alien landed on the first peak, it slowly crawled towards the city. He was focused on collecting red crystals, so he didn’t know what Tess and the others had discussed. If they decided to move to Iron Mountain Fort, then they should be preparing by now.

Moreover, they also said that it would be possible for the ice beasts to attack them these days. Zhao Hai wanted to see these ice beasts, he wanted to see how these things managed to exist.

Just as Alien was about to reach the wall, Zhao Hai stared, he discovered that Tess was already on the wall waiting for him. At this time, Cai’er said, “Young Master, ice beings that Patriarch Tess have described has been spotted on the icefield. There are a lot of them.”

Chapter 599: Ice Beast

When Zhao Hai heard Cai’er, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. Then his expression changed. Alien felt Zhao Hai’s change in mood as it directly jumped towards the wall. Alien’s sudden movement scared the Diamond Apes.

Zhao Hai came out of Alien’s body before he directly went to Tess and said, “Patriarch, the ice beasts have come. There’s are a lot of them. Have the people prepare themselves.”

Tess couldn’t help but stare blankly at Zhao Hai, but he immediately knew that Zhao Hai was a Mage. Moreover, he also heard about Zhao Hai’s magical abilities from Ares. Therefore, he didn’t suspect Zhao Hai’s words. Tess immediately replied, “Alright, I’ll go transmit orders to everybody.”

Then Tess turned around and loudly said, “Everyone Prepare!”

These two words might be short, but it was already enough. After shouting, Tess turned his head and looked outside the city with a cold gaze.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was looking at the city. With Tess’ command, the city immediately exploded in activity. He saw a lot of people coming out of their houses, while some returned before coming out again in their leather armors. The able bodied immediately approached the walls as the old and women stayed behind. Only the children were hiding inside the houses.

From the time of Tess’ shout to this point, it only took 10 minutes. The efficiency of their movement was astonishing.

Zhao Hai looked shocked at these Diamond Apes. The continent had always strived to create an army as coordinated as these. What they thought was impossible was actually achieved by the Diamond Apes. It looks like they were very well practiced in this routine.

Then Zhao Hai turned to look at Tess. Tess was now like a towering colossus that was standing on the city wall. Although he wasn’t young, his imposing aura was still as massive as a mountain. One couldn’t help but admire his form.

At the same time, the resting beasts on the wall had begun to stand up. These giant apes were very huge, and all of them were currently wearing very fierce expressions.

Zhao Hai discovered that the temperament of the diamond ape beasts had completely changed. When they were lying down or sitting, they didn’t have any point of threat to them whatsoever. But now that they had stood up, Zhao Hai saw that they had turned into formidable soldiers.

Most importantly, Zhao Hai also discovered that when these diamond apes were with the Diamond Ape partners, their bodies seem to have formed a connection. At the same time, their strengths have been amplified, they were now at the level of 8th rank.

Although Zhao Hai had a lot of 9th ranks in his hand, he also knew that this due to the Space. But these Diamond Apes didn’t have a thing such as the Space, this was them completely relying on their abilities.

It was now that Zhao Hai truly understood how the Diamond Apes were able to rule the entire Beastman Prairie. It was because their innate skill was too frightening.

Even the Tigers would find it impossible to reach 8th rank even after growing up. On the other hand,  these young soldiers of the Diamond Ape tribe already had 8th rank in strength. Even the elderly and women on the back of the wall had a lot of 8th ranks among them. This sight was indeed too scary.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath. After experiencing the strength of the Diamond Ape tribe, Zhao Hai knew how they were able to survive at this place. Although they were left with 5000 people in the beginning, they still managed to penetrate this deep into the Northern Icefield.

Zhao Hai wasn’t idling when he arrived at the Icefield. After he arrived at the Diamond Ape’s city, he immediately had his Blood Ghost staff out and mapped the surrounding areas as well as the path that he had passed through before.

Because he wasn’t collecting corpses this time, the staff’s speed was increased completely. Actually, there wasn’t anything to see in the Icefield, its terrain had remained unchanged for more than then thousand years. Because of this, Zhao Hai just had Cai’er manage making the map and didn’t care about it again. Although he still hadn’t mapped the northern part of the Icefield, Zhao Hai was almost sure that this volcano is part of the Icefield’s inner area.

Because of this, he admired the Diamond Apes greatly. For them to arrive here was something unfathomable.

Since he hasn’t explored the area beyond the volcano, Zhao Hai didn’t know the situation there. But he believed that he would find a clue to the Beast God’s Spear in that place.

While he was thinking about this, Zhao Hai was suddenly startled awake. He knew that the Ice beasts that Tess had mentioned to him had come. He felt very curious to these beasts and wanted to see them with his own eyes.

On the forest under the city, while flashes started to be seen. Zhao Hai fixed his eyes and focused only to see an ice bull!

It was a bull made entirely of ice. It was about three meters high, had a huge pair of horns, and no matter what part of its body, it was all made of ice. Moreover, it was transparent ice, Zhao Hai can even see the tree behind the cow.

Zhao Hai stared blankly at this thing. He didn’t expect a piece of ice to walk. If he didn’t meet Tess, he might have thought that it was caused by someone who had an Ice Divergent Ability. Otherwise, such a phenomenon was impossible. If such an expert was present, then there would be more powerful attacks coming their way, and Tess would have met it. But Tess told him that there was no such thing. This only showed that these ice beasts weren’t controlled by anyone.

If it was not under control, then it must be made naturally. But can nature really make an ice beast? This idea made Zhao Hai surprised. What environment can allow the natural birth of ice beasts? This matter is too unreasonable.

Zhao Hai turned to Tess and said, “Patriarch Tess, why don’t you use long ranged attacks?”

Tess shook his head and said, “It’s useless. If you don’t destroy their heads, they won’t die. They can just retreat and recover.”

Zhao Hai gawked, but this wasn’t hard for him. He moved his hand as he released several stone golems outside the city. The bodies of these golems exceeded ten meters. Their bodies were red, they didn’t look like normal golems.

In the past, Zhao Hai’s golems were dark green. But since the Space had absorbed the God’s Blood and levelled up, the stone giants have turned blood red. Moreover, their strengths have been insanely increased. Each stone golem was very strong.

After the stone golems appeared, they immediately threw themselves towards the ice beasts. Zhao Hai discovered that the movements of these stone golems had gotten more flexible. Moreover, their speed had also been increased. Their strength must also be greater than before.

These stone golems initially made people feel that they are very bulky. But when Zhao Hai’s stone golems moved, they were smooth and powerful, they didn’t look very stupid.

The Diamond Apes in the city couldn’t help but stare. Although they knew about the existence of Mages, this was the first time that they had seen one fight. When they saw that the more than ten meter high stone golem can fight a Diamond Ape evenly, they couldn’t help but feel shock.

But when they saw the stone golems fighting, their hearts couldn’t help but feel a breeze of coldness. These stone giants had punches that can send people for a thousand miles. Each punch of these golems was able to break an ice bull. They also seem to know the weakness of these ice beasts since they were always aiming for their heads.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was completely focused on the ice beasts. From what he heard from Tess, as long as one doesn’t destroy these beasts’ heads, they would be able to regenerate. Zhao Hai saw an ice wolf blown to pieces by the stone golem without its head getting hit. When the ice wolf passed a puddle of water, the liquid flowed to the body of the ice wolf as it recovered quickly and reentered the fight.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit the brows of his head. He discovered how difficult these ice beasts were to deal with. Even if a stone golem can break one or two heads, it still wasn’t enough.

However, these ice beasts couldn’t do anything to the stone golems. Currently, the bodies of the golems were very hard. Most 8th ranks wouldn’t able to damage their bodies, not to way about these low level ice beasts. From what Zhao Hai has seen, mos of these ice beasts had about 6th rank strength. They didn’t have much of an attack strength.

Although their attacks weren’t a threat to the Diamond Apes, their numbers and regeneration abilities definitely were. This made the ice beasts very difficult to deal with.

Zhao Hai didn’t use fire magic. Although it would be very effective, the area of battle was a lush forest. If he uses fire to attack, then he might burn the entire mountain.

The stone golems were like an offensive wall outside the city. The ice beasts weren’t  able to go through for quite some time which made Tess very surprised. The stone golems were surprisingly very formidable.

Zhao Hai stood on the city wall, calmly looking at the battle below. After a while, he turned to Tess and said, “Patriarch Tess, how many ice beasts generally attack? And do they attack for a long time?”

Tess looked at the ice beasts before replying, “Each ice beast attack has about less than 100 thousand ice beasts. Moreover, if these beasts don’t die, they won’t retreat.”

This number made Zhao Hai surprised. He didn’t expect that the ice beasts would send so many, a hundred thousand. This wasn’t a small number, moreover, they needed to be killed off, which added to the difficulty.

Back on Earth, Zhao Hai saw people doing statistics about military battles. There was a certain percentage of losses before an army chooses to flee. If more than 20% died, then retreat was on the table. If 25% were gone, then people would accept defeat of even flee.

Chapter 600: Vassal

Naturally, Zhao Hai knew that this mentality wouldn’t apply to these ice beasts. These ice beasts didn’t have souls from what he had seen. It was possible that they were puppets that don’t fear anything, thus not knowing about retreat.

Zhao Hai was most proficient with Dark Magic, and Dark Mages had inseparable relationship with souls.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was sensitive about any movements of souls. Although there were already a lot of dead ice beasts, Zhao Hai still didn’t feel any soul in the vicinity. This proved Zhao Hai’s speculation that these ice beasts were puppets.

But what made Zhao Hai feel strange was that these puppets didn’t have anyone giving them command. They seem to have been moving independently. This explained why they didn’t have any attack formation and were attacking by instinct alone, causing their movements to be very disorderly.

These ice beasts weren’t weak, if they had some kind of command, their strength would have been increased by about three times. In this case, the Diamond Apes won’t be able to block them anymore.

The hundred thousand ice beasts were slowly overwhelming the mountain, they seem to be aiming for the Diamond Apes. The trees on the surrounding were virtually untouched, all of them were going straight to the Diamond Ape city.

The stone golems didn’t have any problems in dealing with them, but some ice beasts had started to spill out and headed to the mountain city. This made the Diamond Apes start to act against the ice beasts.

In fact, Zhao Hai had the power to eliminate all of these ice beasts, but he wanted to look at the fighting strength of the Diamond Apes.

It didn’t take too long for the Diamond Apes to show Zhao Hai their fighting ability. The bodies of the Diamond Apes suddenly lit up with a yellow light that resembled golden armor. This made the Diamond Apes and their partners become golden armored soldiers. The wooden clubs on their hands also had a layer of golden light on it.

At this time, the ice beast were already upon the city. Then a scene that Zhao Hai didn’t expect happened. The ice beasts gathered together and then a white light flashed. When the white light vanished, a huge ice beast was seen outside the city. This ice beast was much taller than the stone golem. Then it roared and rushed to the wall.

When it was a few meters away from the wall, it suddenly jumped. This one jump along propelled it towards the wall.

However, at this time, two Diamond Apes made their move. Two bangs were heard as four fists hit the head of the ice beast, causing its head to explode and the ice beast disintegrated after.

But that was not the end, the broken pieces of the ice beast suddenly became little ice beasts. Then those ice beasts rushed towards the other Diamond Apes.

The Diamond Apes seem to know about this property, so they didn’t go away after dealing with the giant ice beast. The Diamond Apes then started to clash with the ice beasts.

Zhao Hai discovered that these golden soldiers were extremely coordinated. The numbers of the ice beasts were simply useless in front of them.

Moreover, from what Zhao Hai had seen, the Diamond Apes seem to have developed a method to have their companion beasts work in total conjunction with their movements. There were no useless movements between the two of them, it was very flawless. This ability was very scary.

After seeing the Diamond Apes fight, Zhao Hai immediately casted a powerful fire element attack. Then an inferno appeared below the city wall. The ice beasts seemed to flinch. It seems like they fear fire.

When he saw this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. The weakness of the ice beasts were indeed fire element magic. However, Zhao Hai cannot use a larger attack magic than he had just used, otherwise, he would be burning the forest down.

While the Diamond Apes were focused on the fire, Zhao Hai immediately released a large number of undead in the forest and had them eliminate the ice beasts.

One of Zhao Hai’s undead can easily eradicate all of the ice beasts, but it would take some time, time which Zhao Hai didn’t have. He was currently thinking about how strange these ice beasts were. He had already mapped the entire southern area of the volcano and he couldn’t wait to unravel the mysteries of the northern part.

Moreover, Zhao Hai reckoned that Tess had already decided to follow him in leaving the icefield. Otherwise, he wouldn’t be waiting for him on the wall.

Because of the undead that Zhao Hai had released, no ice beasts were able to approach the wall and were eliminated in the forest. Because of this, the fight had reached a sudden conclusion. After a couple of moments, no ice beasts can be seen in sight.

This made Tess look strangely at the situation. There was no ice beasts present and Zhao Hai had also retrieved his stone golems. Aside from the traces of the fire magic, it was as though nothing had happened.

However, Tess felt puzzled, he remembered the number of ice beasts that has been killed and was sure that it was not enough. So why did the ice beasts stop coming? This was out of his expectations.

Tess had fought the ice beasts for the entirety of his life. So he was very familiar with the rate of each ice beast attack. Every single time these beasts attack, they would number no less than 100 thousand. When they fought with the ice beasts in the past, they would even need the support of the elderly and the women. So how could the current group of ice beasts be so little?

Zhao Hai looked at Tess expression as he faintly smiled and said, “Patriarch, no need to be worried, there are no ice beasts left.”

Upon hearing this, Tess couldn’t help but turn his head to stare at Zhao Hai. Then he immediately thought that since Zhao Hai was the first one to discover the ice beasts, then the reduction of ice beast numbers should be because of him.

Tess then sighed deeply as he nodded to Zhao Hai. Then he turned to his tribesmen and loudly said, “We’re good, everyone disperse!”

Although the Diamond Apes felt that it was strange, they still dispersed under Tess’ command. In the minds of a lot of people was the thought that this was the most relaxing fight they had been in their entire life.

Seeing that everyone has dispersed, Tess then arranged some people to guard the walls before he led Zhao Hai back to his house. After they had sat down, Tess looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, we have reached an agreement. The elders all agreed. Starting today, our Diamond Ape tribe will forever be your followers!”

Zhao Hai cannot help but get stunned after hearing this. One must know that this statement carried heavy implications for the beastmen. The Diamond Apes basically stated that they would become Zhao Hai’s vassals starting today. The meaning of vassals for the Beastmen and Humans are different. For the Humans, vassals would still have their own autonomy and independence. As long as they listen to their lord, then they would be fine by governing themselves. But Beastmen vassals are a different matter. Beastman vassals would forever respect and regard their master highly. Moreover, there weren’t much of an independence when it comes to their conditions. What they do and how they live would have to depend on what their lord wants. Therefore, when Tess expressed their decision, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk.

Zhao Hai looked at Tess and said, “Patriarch, you need to think about it. If you become a vassal to the Buda Clan, you would no longer have autonomy. I just need to remind you of this.”

Tess nodded and said, “We already considered it. I’ll be frank to Mister, these past few years, the 13 peaks had gotten more and more unstable. And we don’t know when they would erupt, but when they do, we would have nowhere to run to. Passing back through the icefield towards the Prairie wasn’t something that we are able to do. And even if we managed to return, what would be do then? Our tribe has vanished for 5000 years, when we come back, we won’t know what we’ll do.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he understood what Tess was saying. Seeing Zhao Hai nod, Tess continued, “When you brought me to Iron Mountain Fort, I asked Ares about their situation. You did not lie, you truly do treat beastmen very well. I believe that if we come with you, we wouldn’t suffer any loss.”

Zhao Hai looked at Tess and then faintly smiled, “Alright, I’ll accept the Patriarch’s words. Patriarch, have your clansmen prepare. In a few days, I would deliver you to Iron Mountain Fort.”

Tess nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “If Mister is worried about our living necessities, you don’t have to. Our Diamond Ape tribe can handle hardship. The continent would enter summer soon, it would be fine if we don’t have houses.”

Zhao Hai can feel their sense of urgency as he heard Tess’ words. He gave a smile and said, “Patriarch, just wait for a few days. Even if you don’t bring anything, you would still be fine.”

Zhao Hai didn’t lie to Tess, he had a lot of things in his hand. Ever since Wales promised him 100 thousand slaves, he had already amassed materials in order to accommodate them. Of all these things, Zhao Hai gave priority to the thing that Beastmen needed the most, tents.

Tess looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, from what he heard from Ares, Zhao Hai was a man of his word, he wouldn’t deceive them. “Alright, then we’ll trouble Mister. Also, isn’t Mister planning to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear as well?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I would look for it certainly. But rest assured, I’ll deliver you to the wasteland first so that you can avoid any more attacks from the ice beasts. After I send you to the wasteland, I can then take my time in looking for the Divine Artifact. I can just return to the continent whenever I want so you don’t need to worry about my safety.”

Tess already experienced Zhao Hai’s Space Divergent Ability, so he didn’t doubt Zhao Hai’s words. He shifted the topic and asked, “We still have magic beasts in here. How would we deal with those?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That depends in how you want to handle it. If you want to raise  magic beasts in the wasteland, then that won’t be a problem. But if you don’t want to raise this kind of magic beast, I can trade you some argali, bulls, or other beasts. We’ll decide on a fair price. What do you think?”

Tess thought for a moment and said, “We’re really not familiar with argali or bulls. We don’t have any knowledge on how to raise them. On the other hand, we’re quite used to raising these fire rabbits. Can we just raise them in the wasteland?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course, that’s not a problem. But fire rabbits don’t sell for much money. If you decide to raise argali, you can get some milk, wool, and skin for money. But since you don’t have any experience, I’ll give you some argali and bulls to practice on and try to raise them. If you decide to raise them and forgo the fire rabbits, you can approach me and we’ll do a fair trade.”

Tess felt very grateful to Zhao Hai as he said, “Mister, you’re really a good person. Our Diamond Ape tribe didn’t have prior relationship to you, but you still decided to greatly help us. Let me express my deepest thanks.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Patriarch doesn’t need to say anything. You joining my Buda Clan made our overall strength increase. It should be me who says thanks.”

Tess didn’t say anything. However, he knew that Zhao Hai was just saying this out of courtesy. Ares had told Tess about the Buda Clan’s present status in the continent. With the Buda Clan’s current strength, having the Diamond Ape tribe join them wouldn’t give them much of an improvement.

This fact made Tess more grateful to Zhao Hai. There was no doubt that Zhao Hai had helped them a lot but for little benefit to him. This fact made Tess feel very moved.

Seeing Zhao Hai like this, Tess felt that he had not followed the wrong person. It strengthened his determination even more. Zhao Hai looked at Tess’ expression and didn’t comment. It was just as Tess thought, with the current strength of the Buda Clan, he didn’t need the help of the Diamond Ape tribe.

Speaking of true fighting strength, Zhao Hai already had enough 9th ranks to overrun the entire continent. And to say about herding, he already had the Space to do it for him. The main reason why Zhao Hai helped the Diamond Apes were mainly because of sympathy and admiration.

He sympathizes with the situation of the Diamond Ape tribe, while he admired their resolve. After these many years, they still hadn’t given up in their quest to search for the Beast God’s Spear. To such a race, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look highly upon them.

Chapter 601: Settling In

The next day after Zhao Hai and Tess’ agreement, Tess announced to his tribesmen that they would be moving to a new place.

This fact made the other DIamond Apes feel somewhat at a loss. They don’t know what’s going on, why would they suddenly move to another place?”

Zhao Hai didn’t participate in this matter. This wasn’t something that needed his help, it was all left up to Tess and the others. The Diamond Ape tribe had already stayed in this place for more than 5000 years. And in these 5000 years, their lives had been calm. Aside from looking for the Divine Artifact as well as the ice beasts, they didn’t suffer any other trouble. It was a sort of mundane heaven, one which had beasts living in it.

And now they were suddenly leaving, this made the minds of the other Diamond Apes turn blank. But Tess told them about the situation of the volcano and compared it to the Black Wasteland. This managed to calm the people down.

Seeing the reactions of the Diamond Apes made Zhao Hai gawk. Then he immediately understood why. They had lived in seclusion for too long that they would find it strange seeing other strangers in their vicinity. If they suddenly come across an assortment of new people, then they might not be able to adapt.

But fortunately, the place where they would be going to was the Black Wasteland. This meant that they would just be moving from their mundane life into a less mundane place but somewhere without wild beasts. Perhaps this was the best result for them.

Tess’ influence in the tribe was very high that after he talked his tribemates through, they started to pack up and prepared to leave.

The things that they focused most was actually their magic beasts, which were the fire rabbits. These magic beasts were quite big, they weren’t much shorter than the argali. It can eat anything and it rarely get sick. It was a very good type of magic beast.

However, when one considers money, these rabbits were inferior to argali. Because of this, Zhao Hai wanted the Diamond Apes to raise argali, not these fire rabbits.

However, Tess words reminded Zhao Hai that the Diamond Apes haven’t raised argali for more than 5000 years. They simply didn’t have the knowledge to herd argali. If Zhao Hai immediately swaps their fire rabbits for argali, then they might find it hard to adapt.

Zhao Hai and Tess stood on the wall and observed the people preparing. After their talk, Zhao Hai told Tess that Iron Mountain Fort would be prepared after three days. Zhao Hai also sent some undead to Green in order to rush the preparations.

Tess and the others were still not finished preparing. They had lived in here for a long time that not even a stick was spared in their packing. Seeing this scene made Tess smile bitterly.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about it too much. These people were just unwilling to give their stuff up due to nostalgia, it wasn’t something strange. Tess sighed and looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister, I think it’ll take two days before they finish packing. If you are in a hurry, I can make them go faster.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and shook his head, “It’s fine. The Wasteland is already prepared. Being late for one or two days wouldn’t matter. Just have them take their time. There’s no need to worry.”

Tess said, “I’m just afraid that you might miss the chance to get the Beast God’s Spear.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Don’t worry, the Beast God’s Spear has already been here for 5000 years. If something did happen, one or two days wouldn’t make much of a difference.”

Tess nodded, then he said, “Mister, the Beast God’s Spear is a very important matter to our tribe. I have a request. If Mister finds the Beast God’s Spear, please bring it to our Diamond Ape tribe first. We’ve sought for this thing for 5000 years, the least we could do is see it with our own eyes.”

Zhao Hai nodded and, “Patriarch, rest assured. If I do retrieve the Beast God’s Spear, I’ll go back to this volcano and show it to you so you could perform a ritual.”

Tess nodded, he hadn’t requested Zhao Hai about doing a ceremony at the volcano because it was already too much to ask for. Therefore, the only thing he could ask was to see them Beast God’s Spear.

Zhao Hai understood Tess’ mood. This was their tribe’s obsession for 5000 years. If Tess doesn’t see it, then he might carry this regret for the rest of his life.

Sure enough, just as Tess had thought, the Diamond Apes took two days before they finished packing. After all of them had prepared, Zhao Hai immediately went out of the city and opened a huge spatial rift that allowed the people to get through it.

The people couldn’t help but get surprised upon seeing the spatial rift. But they still obediently walked through it. What made them surprised was the fact that Tess was not present. But fortunately, the other elders were there to guide them.

It didn’t take a long time for the people to pass through the spatial rift. And when they emerged, they immediately saw Tess. As it turns out, Tess was the first one that passed through the rift.

Along with Tess, there were also some slaves as well as Giant Horned Bulls on the other side. These people would help the Diamond Apes get settled in.

The Diamond Apes looked curiously at the Giant Horned Bulls. The Giant Horned Bulls were very enthusiastic. Almost all of the Beastmen knew about the exiled Royal tribe, now they had finally seen what they looked like.

However, the Giant Horned Bulls also knew the importance of the current matter. Therefore, they didn’t say a lot of words to the Diamond Apes. They just led the Diamond Apes to the place that was prepared for them. The place where they’ll go to was very close to the Giant Horned Bulls. This was because the Bulls would be the people who would teach the Diamond Apes about the life in the Black Wasteland.

The Diamond Apes received their tents according to their families. It was great that Beastman tents were very tall and spacious, which allowed the Diamond Apes to stay in it.

The Diamond Apes looked curiously at their new home. They had discovered that everything that they would need was already provided. There were even some ironware that they hadn’t seen before, this made them feel very excited.

Soon, the 100 thousand people had arrived at the camp. Tess and the elders also helped them settle in quickly. Green and Merine came as well along with a lot of slaves. The most important thing for these Diamond Apes was to get used to meeting new people. These were people that they would have to come in contact frequently in the future.

Zhao Hai had also started to improve the Wasteland this year. And now that Cai’er has levelled up, she had extended her branches slowly. In the end, she had surrounded the Iron Mountain as well as the middle part of the Black Wasteland. In this way, it won’t be very cold here even in the winter. This also allowed plants to grow normally, increasing the yearly yield of the land.

Cai’er didn’t have anything to say about this. She was a plant type magic beast. And all of the plant types can do this when they reach a high enough level. And now that she has been upgraded further, this matter was not even a problem for her. Now, one could see a beautiful ring of flowers around the Iron Mountains. These branches belong to Cai’er. She can use this to absorb energy from the land. Not only would it affect her cultivation, it would also provide more nutrition for her, which was one of her most important ability in order to survive as a magic beast.

This was also Zhao Hai’s consideration for Tess’ tribe. Although they can survive in the current Black Wasteland, on shouldn’t forget that they had been living in a volcano for 5000 years. They weren’t used to having seasons. If winter suddenly arrives, then it would be troublesome for the Diamond Apes.

Regarding the arrival of the Diamond Apes, Robert and Evan couldn’t help but get surprised. There were once Great Patriarchs who governed land with a border with the Beastmen. Because of that, they also collected a lot of materials regarding the history of the Prairie. The matter of the Diamond Apes wasn’t a huge secret among the Beastmen. They were basically a royal tribe that was exiled to the Northern Icefield. When they went to the Icefield, nobody was expecting them to survive. But who would’ve thought that Zhao Hai would bring them here.

Evan and Robert didn’t know about the true reason why the Diamond Apes were sent to exile. In fact, most Beastmen didn’t know either. However, they were now more surprised about Zhao Hai’s abilities.

Settling 100 thousand people was no small matter. But since Green and the others had already done it for more than one time, they knew what to do. Because of their experience, there weren’t any mistakes in the process. And adding on to the fact that they had prepared, the Diamond Apes were settled quickly.

100 thousand people might sound many, but when one divides them into households, the unit number would be reduced to 30 thousand. Settling them up was much easier than they thought.

Zhao Hai also lended a hand in settling the Diamond Apes. Whatever the Diamond Apes needed, Zhao Hai would fulfill it immediately. He already had a lot of things in his Space, common necessities wouldn’t be a problem.

When the curtain of night fell down, the Diamond Apes were finally settled in nicely. Zhao Hai and the others also relaxed. However, Zhao Hai knew that settling down was not this easy. These Diamond Apes might be unable to adapt to their new life and would take a long time before they get familiar with the place. It was just like when the Giant Horned Bulls had come here for the first time.

However, this time was also not the same. Now, there were Giant Horned Bulls present in order to teach the Diamond Apes. Compared to when the Giant Horned Bulls’ arrival, the current situation was much better.

It took three days before the Diamond Apes had finally reached their new home. Zhao Hai also sent some argali and bulls. With the help of the Giant Horned Bulls, the Diamond Apes would slowly learn how to herd them.

At this time, Zhao Hai returned to the Northern Icefield. It was time to unearth the place’s secrets!

Chapter 602: Ice Pillar

Going back to the volcano and seeing the already deserted city, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile a little. Maybe the volcano would be just like the Northern Icefield. Once it’s secret is discovered, maybe it would be like this mountain city, just a piece of history.

Zhao Hai’s figure slowly flew up the mountain and went to the place beyond it. He then looked at the white icefield as well as the thirteen peaks. He couldn’t help but feel a sense of excitement welling up in his chest. He wanted to conquer this area, he must unearth the secrets that nobody had found out before!

After thinking up to this point, Zhao Hai cannot help but face the skies and issued a long and loud cry. Then his figure moved and quickly flew towards the northern part of the icefield!

While Zhao Hai helped Tess and the others settle down, he also wasn’t idling about. He also made Cai’er control the Blood Ghost Staff and map the entire Northern Icefield.

The Northern Icefield was indeed very big, comparing it to the Beastman Prairie would not be an understatement. It might even be bigger. Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t know that the Northern Icefield wasn’t like this big before. The Icefield was just expanding at a very slow speed. It was because of this discovery that the Patriarch of the Diamond Apes decided to do an expedition to see what caused the expansion. They wanted to know why it continued to expand all this time, but who would’ve thought that they wouldn’t be able to survive their trip.

The White Tigers, Polar Bears, and the Ice Hawks decided to guard the Icefield for the same reason. They wanted to prevent the Icefield’s expansion as much as possible.

Since Zhao Hai didn’t know about this, so he only knew that the place was very big. Since the time Tess had decided to move, Cai’er was already controlling the Blood Ghost Staff to fly and map the Icefield. But even if the Space had already mapped a huge chunk and its speed of mapping was not slow, they still hadn’t found a single clue regarding the Beast God’s Spear.

But Zhao Hai also didn’t worry about it. He was aware that in such a place, wanting to find ten thousand people was not an easy matter.

In other places, ten thousand people might be a considerable number of people. But in this icy wilderness, that number had become insignificant. Moreover, there were countless roads that one can make in a place like this. So it was useless to find a direction. When one goes forward, it was difficult to know where one was heading. In such a place, who knows which direction the ten thousand Diamond Apes went.

Because of this, Zhao Hai moved slowly forward and scanned the place carefully. He was afraid of missing a single thing.

This kind of search was very boring. Zhao Hai couldn’t understand what the Patriarch of the Diamond Ape tribe was thinking. Did he think that looking for the core of the Northern Icefield was very easy?

Zhao Hai didn’t think about it too much since he still needed to constantly go forward day by day. As long as he discovered an anomaly, he would immediately stop and see even if it was just a half buried stone. Zhao Hai didn’t want to miss a single thing.

For ten days, Zhao Hai discovered practically nothing. This made him feel more pressure, the feeling in his heart had gone worse and worse.

Laura and the others also discovered Zhao Hai’s bad mood. They kept using methods to make him happy every day. Although their methods were useful, they knew that unless Zhao Hai finds the Beast God’s Spear, these methods would just be temporary.

As time and days pass by, Zhao Hai was also getting more and more agitated. But he had very good control of himself, so it was only his words that got fewer and fewer as well as the wrinkle in his brows getting tighter and tighter. When Laura and the others looked at this, their hearts couldn’t help but ache. Even if they want to help, there wasn’t anything that they can do.

Zhao Hai wasn’t in the Space most of the time anymore. He was currently on a small ship that he had made. His eyes were virtually stuck to the monitor.

It has been 13 days since Tess and the others had settled down. But even after that time, no clue has been spotted. Zhao Hai slightly shut his eye, he was feeling very tired.

He opened his eyes after some time, then he turned the monitor off. He knew that even if he didn’t look at it, Cai’er would inform him if something special had come up.

Zhao Hai looked outside through the pale red color of the airship. The outside world was pure white, but who would’ve thought that behind this white facade was actually endless murder. It won’t kill you from the beginning, but it will slowly suck you in and dissolve you into this white landscape, making you part of it forever.

While Zhao Hai was thinking about this, a white light suddenly flashed from a distance. Although he has the Staff’s wall protecting him, Zhao Hai still couldn’t help but shut his eyes.

Zhao Hai cannot help but get surprised, he was not familiar with the Icefield. And one could hardly see any other colors inside. There was no change, everything is white, even the sunshine was white. Zhao Hai wanted to know where this glare that blinded him came from.

After some time, Zhao Hai opened his eyes and proceeded to inspect the place carefully. It didn’t take a long time for him to discover that there was a sparkling thing in the distance. Not only was it dazzling, it also emitted seven types of color, it was very beautiful.

Zhao Hai looked at the object and couldn’t help but think about the toy prism that he had in his childhood life. The prism would take in light and disperse seven colors just like a rainbow.

Zhao Hai then saw that the object at the distance was a huge ice pillar, no wonder it can disperse seven colors. Zhao Hai stopped his thinking as he immediately urged the staff to fly towards it. He didn’t care about any other place at this point. He now wants to see what was going on in front of him.

Before long, Zhao Hai was already getting closer and closer to the bright light to the point that the monitor can now pick it up. He immediately inspected the thing on the monitor and couldn’t help but get shocked. This was because what he just saw was an incredibly huge ice pillar!

The thick ice pillar was just like Sun Wukong’s enlarged staff that was stabbed into the earth. It stood there as though it was connecting the sky and the ground.

Zhao Hai stared at this ice pillar, it looks like this pillar just appeared out of nowhere. There was nothing else all around it. It was as peculiar as seeing a huge tree in the Prairie.

After some time, Zhao Hai recovered. Then he called over Laura and the others and had them look at this marvelous sight.

After Laura and the others had come out, they were immediately attracted to the seven colored light in the distance. It took quite some time before they expressed their surprise. Then they shifted their gazes to the monitor to be shocked once more. This was the first time that they had seen such a thing.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what is that strange thing?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I don’t know, I just discovered it right now.” Then he enlarged the image on the monitor. He wanted to have a closer look to see if the ice pillar had anything.

Then he noticed that there were several mounds below the ice pillar. These mounds were quite big, they were 10 meters tall and had about 30 meters in diameter.

Below the pillar were about 12 mounds. Zhao Hai looked at the mounds carefully, he didn’t know the purpose of these things.

At this time, brilliant rays suddenly went out of one of the mounds. An ice beast then appeared to be digging itself out. Right, it was an ice beast. The same ice beasts that attacked the Diamond Ape tribe.

Zhao Hai had also been looking for clues about the ice beasts in the past few days, but he had not succeeded. He didn’t expect to find traces of them in this place.

Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but change since he had always felt that the ice beasts may have something to do with the Beast God’s Spear. If this was the case, then does the ice pillar have any clues about it?’

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately quickened his speed, he wanted to inspect the ice pillar as soon as possible. It didn’t take too long for the monitor to be able to penetrate inside the ice pillar. Zhao Hai stared intently at the screen, his heart was already beating loudly.

The layers of ice looked just as hard as a copper wall. But Zhao Hai didn’t worry about it, he just calmly watched the monitor. He now noticed that the monitor’s distance to the ice was now closer compared to the ground.

At this time, the ice suddenly vanished from his sight. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get surprised at this development. He immediately stopped and looked around. Unexpectedly there was a space inside the ice pillar.

Zhao Hai stared blankly before he immediately had the Blood Ghost Staff move forward. He didn’t expect the pillar to have a hollow space inside.

Zhao Hai then discovered that the ice pillar was very thick, and the space inside it was also very enormous. Although the pillar can only be hardly seen in the icefield, one would discover how grand it was the closer one approaches it.

The entire ice pillar was about 10 thousand meters in diameter, but its altitude would reach about 100 thousand. Such height was incredibly astonishing.

The pillar’s wall was about several hundred meters thick and the space inside was very huge. This was the grandest place that Zhao Hai has ever been in.

The more the staff advanced the more shocked ZHao Hai was at this incomparably huge ice pillar. Just as he was shocked, he suddenly found some black spots that had appeared on the monitor.

Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but turn sharp as he saw these black spots. With a pure environment such as this, these black spots were peculiarities that attracted his attention.

One of these black spots was a Diamond Ape that was carrying a spear. Moreover, he also had his beast relative towering right behind him!

Chapter 603: Perverted Bubble

This ape has been frozen in ice that has not been melted in about thousands of years. The Beastman and the beast now looked like an ice sculpture.

Zhao Hai stopped in mid air and stared at the frozen ape, Laura and the others did so as well. The Diamond Ape looked very peculiar. He wore a very simple sleeveless leather armor, there was no way to keep his arm from getting cold. Apart from the leather armor, the ape also wore a beastkin cloak. And on his hand was an iron spear.

At the same time, the ape that was behind the Diamond Ape was much larger than the giant apes of the Diamond Ape tribe. It also appeared much sturdier. The ape has the eyes and expression of someone that was anticipating an attack. The two of the were like soldiers that were preparing for battle.

Zhao Hai looked blankly at this scene, he took a good long time in silence. Although the beast and person was already sealed for thousands of years, their imposing aura still remained. It was for certain that they were formidable soldiers when they were alive. Only elit warriors had this kind of fire in their expressions. They had an aura of someone who had gone through a mountain of corpses and a sea of blood. Their single step was enough to frighten a child.

Laura and the others looked at the frozen person and beast with not so good expressions. Their faces had paled, noticeable frightened by the Diamond Ape and his beast.

Before long, Zhao Hai recovered, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “I guessed correctly! Thes ice beasts did indeed have something to do with the Beast God’s Spear! Hahaha. It seems like the Divine Artifact is in this ice pillar.”

“Brother Hai, I’m a little scared.” While Zhao Hai was drowning in happiness, Laura’s shivering voice sounded out. Zhao Hai turned to Laura and saw that their faces were a bit pale, they were indeed quite frightened.

Zhao Hai immediately understood the matter and then said, “Alight, you go back to the Space first. I’ll go to the ice pillar myself and look for the Beast God’s Spear.”

Laura and the others complied as Zhao Hai transferred them back to the Space. Zhao Hai didn’t expect that Laura and the others would be frightened by this.

However, his thought changed as he understood the feelings of Laura and the others. Although they had experienced a lot of matters, they weren’t very familiar with a genuine battlefield. Most of the time, they were looking at the scene from the monitor, just like how someone looks at a movie in a television. But now, they were looking at an enlarged version of an image which was almost the same as the actual person. The aura of the beast and beastman was too overwhelming that it was not a mystery why Laura and the others were frightened.

Zhao Hai gently shook his head, he didn’t care about this matter. After all, he didn’t want Laura and the others to go through this path in the future. They weren’t necessary in the battlefield, Zhao Hai was already enough.

After Laura and the others entered the Space, Zhao Hai immediately flew forward. The more he went forward, the more Diamond Apes he had managed to come across. All of these Diamond Apes were the same as the first one. All the them had the same expression, leather armor, cloak, as well as iron spear. With their companion beast at their back, and their mouth roaring, they looked like an army that had declared their presence in the battlefield.

Zhao Hai slowly went forward. Although he couldn’t wait to get the Beast God’s Spear, he wasn’t worried much about that anymore. He knew that the pillar certainly had clues regarding the Beast God’s Spear. With the expressions of these people as well as the ice beasts, Zhao Hai knew that he had reached the core part of the icefield. Therefore, the more he proceeded forward, the more calm he became.

After flying for quite some time, Zhao Hai found out that there were no more Diamond Apes in front of him, so he stopped again. He immediately narrowed the monitor to see that there was a neat square formation in front of him, composed of frozen Diamond Apes. And in front of the square stands one Diamond Ape.

Zhao Hai immediately focused the monitor on this man. He was very tall for a Diamond Ape, towering at about 3 meters. The ape that stood behind him was much more astonishing at a height of 15 meters. He was holding a spear in his hand, but it wasn’t pulled back. The iron spear was stabbed at something in the front.

Zhao Hai quickly discovered that the spear that was stabbed was quite unique. Zhao Hai reckoned that the Diamond Ape that wielded it must have been the Patriarch of the Diamond Ape tribe.

But when Zhao Hai saw what was being stabbed, his eyes couldn’t help but narrow. It was not an animal, nor was it an ice beasts, it was actually a small pool!

A small pool! Not a big pool. It’s diameter was about five meters, and seemed to be as deep as it was wide. The water in the pool was dark blue, much bluer than the sky. It’s color seems like it could penetrate into a person’s soul.

Zhao Hai looked at the poll in a daze. Suddenly, the water in the pool started shaking, and Zhao Hai also noticed that the Beast God’s Spear was similarly shaking. Following that, an ice beast suddenly jumped out of the pool. The ice beast seemed to be afraid of the Beast God’s Spear. When it saw the spear, it immediately ran away.

Zhao Hai stared at all of it as it happened. Until now, he was still unsure of the spear, but now he was certain that it was the Beast God’s Spear. It was because inside this place, except for the ice beasts as well as the pool, everything was frozen. Only the spear was not frozen in ice.

Zhao Hai understood that the pool must have been the true core of the entire Northern Icefield, and that the Beast God’s Spear has been suppressing it. But in fact, it didn’t manage to fully seal it, which explains the appearance of the ice beasts. The ice beasts didn’t know what to do, so they decided to just attack Tess and the others.

Zhao Hai saw it as a very interesting turn of events. The Patriarch of the Diamond Ape tribe suppressed the pool with the Beast God’s Spear which in turn causing it to spawn the ice beasts that were attacking the Diamond Ape tribe.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath as he smiled faintly. Then his figure moved as his actual body appeared inside the ice pullar.

Zhao Hai was now standing right by the Diamond Apes and its Patriarch. He calmly looked at the spear that the Diamond Ape Patriarch was holding. It looked just like any ordinary spear, black, and had a ribbon wrapped around its shaft. Its tip was as red as blood.

Then Zhao Hai felt the intense fighting intent of the spear, it was very frightening as it caused Zhao Hai to take deep breaths. Just as he was about to deal with the pool, he suddenly noticed the ice walls around him started to move.

Zhao Hai thought that it was just an ice beast. But when he looked at it, he suddenly froze. This wasn’t an ice beast, it was a person!

No, it wasn’t exactly like a person, but an ice person, someone made entirely out of ice. These ice people were all in the forms of women. They wore court lady dresses and had fluttering dark blue belts. They looked like dancers with their attire and belt, it was very beautiful.

The faces of these ice people were beautiful as well, but it didn’t show any expression. Their hairs were fashioned into an attractive swirl, something Zhao Hai had not seen before, but was still very beautiful.

From what Zhao Hai can see, there were 12 women who appeared on the ice wall. All of their appearances were the same. Zhao Hai thought that they looked like the beautiful ancient ladies on television back on Earth. Their clothes and their expressions were very pure.

At this time, the hands of the 12 women started to move towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before his figure moved and disappeared from his location. Then he appeared right next to an ice man as he opened a spatial rift and absorbed her into the Space.

When the iceman entered the Space, the Space immediately issued a prompt, “An Ice Fairy has been detected, detected to be hostile to the Space. Changing its internal programming. Change completed.”

When Zhao Hai heard the prompt, he immediately understood. This ice people were actually just like the stone golems. They can technically be called ice golems, but they weren’t as big.

Zhao Hai became serious and before long, he had absorbed the 12 ice people into the Space. After absorbing the icemen, Zhao Hai looked around in order to see if there are any other danger. When he didn’t discover anything else, he then went to the pool.

The water in the pool fiercely moved, but the Beast God’s Spear kept stopping it completely.

Zhao Hai looked at this scene and didn’t dare to be careless. He opened a spatial rift and then absorbed the entire violent pool into the Space. In a blink of an eye, the pool became completely empty.

When the pool entered the Space, a prompt was then heard, “Massive amounts of water element energy detected. The energy is very hostile to the Space. Changing its program, change completed.”

When the prompt finished, Zhao Hai’s body immediately flashed into the Space. Then he discovered that the Profound Ice pool that was already in the Space has become the pool in the ice pillar. Just as Zhao Hai had become curious, a bubble suddenly separated itself from the pool and then floated towards Zhao Hai. Then the bubble suddenly said, “This one has seen the Lord!”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that a bubble would be able to speak. At this time Cai’er arrived and said, “Young Master, I feel like this bubble is just the same as me.”

Zhao Hai looked at Cai’er, he knew that Cai’er was a spirit that was born from the seven-colored flower. Was this bubble also a spirit that was born from the pool?

Zhao Hai turned to the bubble and then said, “Don’t call me Lord, just call me Young Master. Are you the spirit of this pool?”

The bubble replied, “I am indeed, Young Master. I’m the spirit of this pool. If the Young Master doesn’t want to call me spirit, I’m also called the Myriad Water.”

Zhao Hai affirmed his speculation, then he referred to the 12 iceman and said, “Are these 12 icemen your creations?”

The bubble replied, “Yes, Young Master. I don’t know when I appeared here, but when I awoke, I was already in that place. Then some people came and suppressed me. I couldn’t do anything and struggled. I was afraid and thought that those things might help. So I made those 12 people.”

Zhao Hai knew that the people that the bubble was referring to was the Beastmen. But he felt strange. The bubble didn’t know about the Beastmen, but yet he was able to make ice beasts. This was a bit too weird, so Zhao Hai immediately asked, “So you made those ice people? And what about those ice beasts?”

Bubble replied, “I also don’t know. In any case, when I awoke, the figures of those ice people and ice beasts were already inside my mind. So I chose to make them. Young Master, don’t you think that those ice people are very beautiful?”

Zhao Hai stared, then his head felt very dizzy. Was this really the spirit of the Myriad Water? Why does it sound like a wretched old man? The words of bubble completely destroyed the image that Zhao Hai had of him in his mind.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head as he asked once more, “So you really don’t know anything? Where you come from? Then how did you know that you are the spirit of the Myriad Water?”

The bubble replied, “I just knew that I am the spirit of the Myriad Water just as I woke up. That, and the images of the ice beasts and the ice people.”

Zhao Hai went silent, he didn’t know how to proceed. This fellow does seem to have severe amnesia. He waved his hand and then said, “These ice men, can you receive them?”

The bubble nodded and then said, “Naturally. After all, these things are made by me.” Then the 12 ice fairies turned into blue waters and then flowed into the pool, completely vanishing from sight.

Zhao Hai then turned his head to the bubble and said, “Starting today, you are called Bubble. Come with me, we’ll be heading out.” Then Zhao Hai took Bubble along with him out of the Space.

When Bubble disappeared, the Beast God’s Spear seemed to look back to normal, Its intense fighting aura had disappeared, it had returned to its base state.

Then with an intention, Zhao Hai received the Beast God’s Spear along with the Diamond Ape Patriarch and his giant ape. At this moment, a prompt was heard from the Space, “Item with weak spirit detected, strengthening the item’s spirit. Updating it’s program, update complete.”

Zhao Hai looked at the spear and knew that it indeed had an Artifact Spirit. This was because the prompt that was just heard was the same as when Iron Hammer was sent to the Space. Zhao Hai was now thinking about what kind of Artifact Spirit this Beastman Divine Artifact had.

Chapter 604: Bloody War

A group of blood suddenly flowed out of the Beast God’s Spear and slowly formed into a large drop. This drop had a huge stench of blood. Then the drop wobbled as it reshaped itself into something like person’s figure that was as tall as someone’s arm. The figure slowly changed before it grew an ape head, four arms, and two feet.

The head of this ape looks like the Diamond Ape tribe, but Zhao Hai hasn’t seen a race with four arms before. The figure wore full body armor while each of its four arms held something, a shield, a spear, a blade, and a morningstar. The belt on its waist had the head of a fierce tiger.

Before long, the Artifact Spirit had finished forming itself.

Zhao Hai was somewhat surprised at this Artifact Spirit. He had seen Artifact Spirits before like Mu’er and Iron Hammer. But Mu’er looked like a child, one which didn’t look like a threat. Iron Hammer looked just like a proper Dwarf. On the other hand, this Artifact Spirit looked like someone born for slaughter. His body was filled with the smell of blood, one that only an experienced War General would have.

A Wargod, this was the first word that came into Zhao Hai’s mind after seeing this Artifact Spirit. And extremely aggressive Wargod, one that lived of for blood and battle.

While Zhao Hai was surprised at the Artifact Spirit, the Spirit turned to look at Zhao Hai as it gave salute with its four arms and said, “Bloody War has seen the Master.”

“Bloody War!” Zhao Hai repeated the two words in a low tone. This name might sound careless, but Zhao Hai had an idea of the implications of this name. This was because from the ancient times to the present, the actions of the Beastmen had always been in line of these two words. Bloody War.

Beastmen wouldn’t flinch in front of adversity. As long as they were issued an order, they would immediately execute it. Bloody War, fight to the last person, nobody was allowed to retreat. This was the meaning of these two words.

Zhao Hai recovered and looked at Bloody War and said, “Just call me Young Master. Bloody War, Iron Hammer already told me about the matters in the Ark Continent. Do you have anything to add to it?”

Bloody War shook his head and said, “I don’t. Young Master, Iron Hammer and me descended from the Divine Realm at the same time. The experiences that we had are similar as well. What Iron Hammer knew was also what I knew.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “Alright, then that’s that. I’ll go hand you over to the Beastmen. Do your best to protect them, understood?”

Bloody War immediately replied, “I shall, Young Master!” Zhao Hai nodded, but when he was about to exit, Bloody War said, “Young Master, please help this Diamond Ape.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then he turned to look at the frozen Diamond Ape Patriarch. He was confused as he looked at Bloody War and said, “They’re already dead, how can I help him? Moreover, their bodies have been petrified, my Dark Magic is useless.”

Bloody War shook his head, “No, no, Young Master. They are indeed dead, but their bodies are not petrified. You can use Dark Magic in order to turn them into undead. The Patriarch of the Diamond Apes has a very special talent called War Flag. This ability acts just like a War Flag on the battlefield. Every single soldier under his command would get improved, increasing the combat effectiveness of his army. That year, he relied on this ability to take his expedition deep into the Northern Icefield.”

Zhao Hai was surprised, this was the first time that he heard of such an ability. But this was indeed something great. If he had these Diamond Apes and turned them into undead, their fighting strength would certainly be formidable.

Zhao Hai nodded as he had a black fog appear and penetrate into the bodies of the Diamond Ape Patriarch and his giant ape partner.

The black gas permeated into their bodies very quickly, Zhao Hai also felt a connection to the two. But at this time, the corpses still remained unmoved.

Zhao Hai stared, the Space had already transformed them into undead, 9th rank undead. How could these 9th ranks still get stuck in ice? Is this a joke?

Zhao Hai face suddenly changed as he said, “Bubble, come over here, what’s wrong with them?”

Bubbles appeared in front of Zhao Hai and looked at the Diamond Ape Patriarch as well as the giant ape. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, they’ve been frozen in Myriad Ice. This ice is frighteningly cold, one would be frozen into almost indestructible solid. Anything frozen by Myriad Water would find it near impossible to recover.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he asked, “Can you melt this ice?”

Bubbles seemed to look strangely at Zhao hai, “Young Master, this ice is essentially me, so I can definitely control it. If Young Master wanted to take the ice away, you can already do so anytime. You’ve gained the same ability as me.”

When Zhao Hai heard Bubble, he immediately tried to melt the ice with his mind. The ice surrounding the Diamond Ape Patriarch and the giant ape immediately became water and flowed into the pool.

When Zhao Hai saw this happen, he couldn’t help but feel relief. Then he looked at Bubble and then turned his hand before a red crystal appeared. He held the crystal in front of bubble and said, “Bubble, in the place that you’ve stayed, were there things that are like this?”

Bubble looked at the crystal and then nodded and said, “There’s plenty, but they are colored white, some of its energy also came from me.”

Zhao Hai became happy, the myriad ice and the red crystals were very good things. Zhao Hai turned his head to Bubble and said, “Is the entire Icefield really covered in myriad ice? Are there any special things inside?”

Bubble shook his head and said, “Young Master, those are just ice that were there for thousands of years. Only those infused with my energy can be said to be real myriad ice. The ice pillars as well as the ice in a radius around it can be considered to be myriad ice. At the same time, the snow on a certain radius around me has also been infused by my energy. I named them myriad snow. Although they aren’t as good as the myriad ice, they can still prove very useful.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then his body flashed as he went outside, Bubble was also right beside him. Then Zhao Hai said, “Take the snow and the ice away. Then we’ll find that white stones that you said and bring them to the Space.

Bubble complied as he started to rotate. And along with his rotation, all of the ice in the surroundings started to change into water as it slowly got absorbed into his body. Before long, the giant ice pillar as well as the surrounding ice had returned to Bubbles’ body. At the same time, the snow all around had also started to get absorbed by Bubble. When everything stopped, what was left was a giant pit. The giant pit originally contained the  myriad ice. Also, there were no more snow present on a radius outside the pit.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Bubble and then saw that there were no changes to its size. Zhao Hai looked confused at Bubble as he asked, “You just absorbed a lot, why haven’t you grown up?”

Bubbles looked at Zhao Hai’s eyes as if he was confused at Zhao Hai’s question, “Young Master, I am an origin of water. Even if you load my body with all of the water in this world, I still won’t get big. Actually, after these things enter my body, they just exist in a much smaller form. If Young Master doesn’t believe it, you can see it for yourself.” Then Bubble came closer to Zhao Hai’s eyes.

Zhao Hai looked into Bubbles’ body. Bubble wasn’t big, he was only the size of a football. He looked dark blue but he was still quite transparent. When Zhao Hai looked carefully inside Bubble, he can faintly see some very small bubbles. In one of the bubbles, Zhao Hai can see the ice pillar, there were also a lot of ice inside as well as the snow. The bubbles were so small that if Bubble hadn’t informed Zhao Hai, he couldn’t even see these things.

Zhao Hai became shocked, he didn’t expect this. He looked at Bubble and said, “Can you store anything in your body?”

Bubble shook its head and said, “No, I can only store things that are related to my nature, like water, ice, snow, fog, and so on.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he also wasn’t disappointed. His Space’s Warehouse was very big and was able to store all kinds of things. So there was no need for Bubble to have the ability to do the same.

Zhao Hai then turned to Bubble and said, “What if I want to use those things? Do I still need you to get them?”

Bubble nodded, “Right, they’re in my body. If Young Master wants them, you’ll have to ask me for permission.”

Zhao Hai’s face seemed to turn black, he looked at Bubble and then said, “After going back to the Space, go give those things to Cai’er. Have her store it to the Warehouse. Then go back to the pool and don’t come out if I don’t call you.”

Bubble snorted, but Zhao Hai still looked at the Icefield and said, “Are there any other good things here?”

Bubbles nodded and said, “There is. If you walk towards the north, you would see a ball of wind. Because of that ball of wind, my life in the icefield has become miserable. Every single year, it blows air towards me, it’s very annoying.”

When Zhao Hai heard Bubble, his eyes couldn’t help but shine. This ball of wind might actually be another good thing.

Chapter 605: Wind Bead

Although he knew that the wind ball that Bubble just told him about was a good thing, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately go out and get it. He calmed his emotions as he started to looked at the white crystals that Bubble described.

The white crystals weren’t hard to find, there were 12 lodes on the previous mounds that Bubble just hollowed out. Zhao Hai didn’t think that those 12 lodes would be on the 12 mounds around the ice pillar. It seems like these lodes did have a  big relationship with Bubble.

After he thought about it, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel happy. He understood that as long as he has Bubble, he would have a lot of crystals to use. This was really fantastic.

Although he was pondering about these, Zhao Hai’s movement didn’t slow down. He quickly received the white crystals into the Space to see what properties they had.

When the crystal was absorbed into the Space, a prompt was heard, “Item that contained cold energy has been detected. Contains stable cold energy equivalent to 100 thousand watts. The crystal can be charged after it has been used up.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel relieved after hearing this. But he also discovered the difference between this white crystal and the red one. The white crystal contained cold energy while the red crystal contained hot energy.

Zhao Hai thought about it and decided to appropriately name the red one Fire Crystal and the white one Ice Crystal. This was because the red crystal was found in a volcano while the white crystal was grown in the Icefield.

Zhao Hai quickly received the 12 mineral lodes. The amount of white crystal that Zhao Hai just got wasn’t as small as the red crystals. After all, the red crystals were only sourced by an incomplete mother ore while the white crystals had 12 complete ones.

From what Zhao Hai can count, he had collected 500 thousand ice crystals altogether. This wasn’t a small number. One must know that the quality of these white crystals are vastly better than the fire crystals.

After receiving the crystals, Zhao Hai then returned to the Space. Laura and the others were currently gathering around a spinning Bubble. Bubble looked very comfortable; he was blue, he was soft to hold and wasn’t cold at all.

However, when Zhao Hai saw Laura and the others gathering before Bubble, looking like they were enjoying themselves, he couldn’t help but feel irritated. For such a perverted Bubble to get this much attention was very unreasonable.

Zhao Hai grabbed Bubble who was held by Laura, he stretched the blue ball out before asking, “Bubble, where did you say that wind ball was again?”

Although Bubble was stretched out by Zhao Hai many times, he seemed to not care at all. So when Zhao Hai asked him, he immediately replied, “When Young Master heads to the north, you would be able to see it for yourself.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he returned Bubble to Laura’s arms before he immediately had the staff fly straight to the North. He wanted to see what this wind ball actually was.

Zhao Hai didn’t explore around this time, he didn’t slow down as he headed in a completely straight line heading north. Because of this, the staff’s speed was extremely quick.

In the evening, Zhao Hai had found out that the wind has gotten much stronger. Zhao Hai immediately took Bubble out of the Space and went inside the staff.

Zhao Hai looked outside and said, “Bubble, is it this place?”

Bubble turned and circled before saying, “Yes, Young Master. We’ll arrive there soon.”

Then Zhao Hai turned to Bubble and said, “Bubble, how did you know that there is a wind ball here? And what is that wind ball?”

Bubble replied, “Young Master, I’ve been here for a long time, even before the Beastmen started exploring the area. At that time, I had the ice beasts explore the entire icefield and saw that ball of wind. That ball of wind is just like me, it is the origin of myriad wind. But it probably hasn’t reached the same level as me. When I found it, it still hasn’t awakened.”

Zhao Hai was shocked, he didn’t think that the ball of wind would actually be like Bubble. So in other words, the ball of wind might have its own spirit as well?

Zhao Hai was now much more careful, he personally controlled the Blood Ghost Staff. At the same time he asked, “Bubble, this isn’t the wrong direction, right?”

Bubble shook its head and said, “It shouldn’t be. Don’t worry, Young Master. Compared to the past, my present ability is much better. As long as there is water element in the area, I would be able to monitor it. The place should not be far away from here.”

Hearing Bubble’s words, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get startled. He looked at Bubble and said, “So you’re saying that you can monitor things through water?”

Bubble’s round body shook up and down, as if nodding, then said, “Young Master, I am the source of myriad water. As long as it has something to do with water, it will submit to my will.”

Zhao Hai looked at this small bubble, he didn’t think that this little thing would have such an ability. It seems like he shouldn’t look down on it.

At this time, Bubble suddenly said, “Young Master, we’ve arrived.” Zhao Hai immediately turned his head and looked out only to see a small whirlwind in front of him that was constantly turning around. This whirlwind seem to be supporting a small green bead. This bead was at the very least at the size of a walnut. It couldn’t be called a ball at all.

Zhao Hai looked at the green bead and said, “Is this the ball of wind that you said? Can it really control the wind? Why does it look so underwhelming?”

Bubble replied, “Young Master, this ball might seem to be behaved, but if it gets angry, it’s very terrifying.”

Zhao Hai looked at the green bead, he really couldn’t imagine how this bead could be so frightening. But to be sure, Zhao Hai and Bubble returned to the Space. Laura and the others were already inside the Space, looking at the situation through the monitor.

When the group saw Zhao Hai came in, Laura immediately ran over and hugged Bubble. Then she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, would you really take that thing? Can it really control the wind?”

Zhao Hai looked at the snuggled Bubble in Laura’s bosom and couldn’t help but get irritated, he poked Bubble repeatedly before Laura swept his hand away while staring at him with fierce eyes.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly and said, “Perhaps. In any case, it was what Bubble said so I don’t really know. I’ll go try and capture it.” Then Zhao Hai sat on the sofa and gave an order to the staff.

The halted Blood Ghost Staff immediately flew towards the bead while Zhao Hai and the others looked at it through the screen. Zhao Hai wanted to see how the bead would react.

Sensing that the staff was about to hit it, the bead immediately acted like a hedgehog. It spun quickly and as it turned it collected more and more wind. Before long the wind had gotten bigger that it had turned into a tornado. The ice below couldn’t handle the strong winds and got dug up, causing a pit to form on the ground.

The Blood Ghost Staff was actually affected by the wind, making it unable to go any further. Zhao Hai was shocked before he took the staff back to the Space. Laura and the others couldn’t help but be surprised at the small bead. They didn’t think that it would be this powerful.

After some time, the wind stopped as the tornado became small. Then it seemed to rock back and forth as if it was looking for something.

Zhao Hai cannot help but wipe away his sweat. This little thing was really a trickster. Zhao Hai didn’t become polite, with an intention, a spatial crack suddenly appeared right beside the bead. Then a big hand stretched out from the Space and pulled the bead inside.

When the bead entered the Space, a prompt was then issued, “Wind Spirit has been detected. Lifeform is hostile to the Space. Suppressing the lifeform. Lifeform suppressed.”

Then Zhao Hai had the bead appear inside the room. The bead still looked green and was somewhat transparent. However, this bead was still spinning since one could see a faint tornado appearing around it.

Zhao Hai looked at the bead and said, “Can you speak?”

A faint infantile voice sounded out, “I’ve seen the Master, I can speak.”

Upon hearing the voice, Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “Good, from now on, you shall be called Breeze. Bubble, Breeze, remember, you must always listen to Cai’er’s words. Cai’er, look after these two children.”

The young lady Cai’er smiled tenderly and said, “Young Master, rest assured, I will certainly take care of them.” Zhao Hai nodded, he knew that although Cai’er is very strange, she also knew that Zhao Hai didn’t like to joke, so she appeared quite proper. But still, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but recall the time when Cai’er was riding on the back of Zhao Wen. She really looked childish back then.

Laura and the others didn’t oppose to Zhao Hai’s decision. Although Laura liked Bubble very much, she also had a lot of matters to attend to. It would be impossible for her to accompany Bubble daily. Making Cai’er play with Bubble was also a good idea.

In fact, Laura and the others had always regarded Mu’er and Cai’er as children. Although their abilities were formidable, Laura couldn’t help but treat them as kids because of their image. When there was nothing to do in the Space, they would often play with Mu’er and Cai’er. That was one of their happy times.

Zhao Hai also likes to accompany Cai’er and play around for a while. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s feeling towards the Space was bigger than Laura and the others. This was because the Space represented Zhao Hai’s only connection to Earth.

Since arriving at the Ark Continent, Zhao Hai has found himself to be more and more like a native. But he doesn’t want to be like this, but there was no other way. If he wanted to survive, then he would have to adapt. His only escape is the time where he was inside the Space where he always felt like he was back on Earth, playing his farm simulation games. He would feel just like his ordinary self back on Earth, and that all of this was just a dream.

Chapter 606: Fighting Intent

However, Zhao Hai also didn’t want to return to Earth. If he returned, he would just go back to being an ordinary nerd. In here, he was Zhao Hai Buda of the Buda Clan. He also had several wives that loved him. His situation here was leagues better than back on Earth.

The reason why he thought of Earth was because he didn’t want to forget where he came from. In the universe, there is a planet called earth, of which there was a country called China. There, people with yellow skin and dark eyes were present, they were his true people.

Although Zhao Hai was now the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, had gotten married, and also had his own life in the Ark Continent, his Chinese heart was still burning inside him. He always thought of himself as Chinese, a descendant of dragons.  To him, being married and getting a career in the Ark Continent was just like how someone was living and working abroad and also had gotten married.

The only thing different in his situation was that people who worked overseas can just return to their homeland while Zhao Hai cannot.

Now that the matters in the Northern Icefield had been taken care of, Zhao Hai finally relax. Then he immediately returned to the volcano in order to fulfill his promise to Tess. He must bring the Beast God’s Spear to this place so that the Diamond Apes can do a ceremony.

Zhao Hai took Bloody War to the Space and then to the volcano. The moment Zhao Hai came out, Bloody War also materialized. He looked at the direction of the volcano and said, “Young Master, what is this place? Why do I feel a strong Beastman fighting intent from here?”

Then Zhao Hai narrated to Bloody War about the matters of the Diamond Apes. For the entirety of the story, Bloody War was carefully listening to Zhao Hai. After Zhao Hai had finished, Bloody War took a deep breath before he said, “Good, good, worthy to be called the children of the Beast God. They did great!”

Then just as Bloody War’s voice fell, a red light suddenly erupted from the volcano as it pierced the heavens. Zhao Hai thought that the volcano had exploded but it didn’t look like it. Although the red light was from the crater, it didn’t have any degree of heat to it. Insted, the light held a cold killing intent, one that dared to fight the skies.

Fighting Intent! This should be the fighting intent that Bloody War had described! Zhao Hai felt felt the pressure from it and confirmed his thoughts. But he didn’t understand why he hadn’t felt it before. Instead, only after Bloody War said a few words did the fighting intent explode.

At this time, the red light from the crater slowly solidified and turned into a blood red spear that shot up to the sky. The spear was very huge, it was about a dozen feet high and about a meter thick. It looked extraordinary and imposing.

When the spear started to form, Bloody War immediately said, “Young Master, let me loose. This fighting intent would be good for me.” Zhao Hai immediately let go of Bloody War.

Just as Zhao Hai’s hands let go, Bloody War immediately flew towards the crater and penetrated the giant red spear. Then Zhao Hai saw that the giant spear had started to shrink as it integrated itself with Bloody War. After that, Bloody War flew back.

But now, Zhao Hai discovered that the originally black shaft of the spear already had a shade of red in it. Moreover, Bloody War’s imposing aura had been strengthened.

At this time, Bloody War materialized again, but this time, he was much bigger than before. Zhao Hai looked at Bloody War and said, “What happened? That thing is useful to you? How did you absorb it?”

Bloody War shook his head and said, “Young Master, that fighting intent is a unique Beastman’s Blood Oath fighting intent. This thing has huge benefits to me. This fighting intent is only produced by those who underwent a Blood Oath and is formed through generations. One couldn’t see this kind of thing during normal times. Since I am a weapon, I always feel it in battlefields, it also causes me to get stronger and stronger. Young Master doesn’t need to worry about me. I’ve already reached the same state as my peak.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good. I’ll go let you see the current Patriarch of the Diamond Apes. They badly wanted to see you. At the same time, tell them that you had me turn their previous Patriarch into an Undead. I don’t want them to misunderstand me.”

Bloody War nodded then said, “Young Master, rest assured, Bloody War understands.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he brought Bloody War to the Space and then to Iron Mountain Fort.

The lives of Tess and the others had been blissful these past few days. Beastmen were inherently good at herding. So although they hadn’t herded in 5000 years, they quickly learned it with the help of the Giant Horned Bulls. Moreover, their living conditions have improved by tenfold. Normally, they would need the help of their giant apes in order to go anywhere, but now they didn’t need to. This made Tess and the others unusually happy.

However, Tess still couldn’t help but worry about the Northern Icefield. Zhao Hai had already been there for many days but there seems to be no information.

He was afraid that Zhao Hai had suffered an accident, or that Zhao Hai couldn’t find the Beast God’s Spear. Because of this, Tess has been losing sleep for the past few days. One could even see him visibly getting skinnier. Compared to the other Diamond Apes, his appearance looked very exhausted.

Today, Tess was herding some argali. Then suddenly, a person appeared in front of him. Tess was initially startled, but then he thought that the only person who can appear in his vicinity without alerting his beast partner was Zhao Hai.

Tess turned to look at Zhao Hai and saw that the other party was smiling while holding a spear in his hand. This spear was obviously not something that was used by Humans. Its shaft was very thick and it was very long. It was evident that this spear can only be used by Beastmen.

Tess looked at the spear in Zhao Hai’s hand and couldn’t help but recall the records of their tribe. There, a spear with a specific length and thickness was carefully drawn. It was impossible for Tess to not recognize that the spear in Zhao Hai’s hand was indeed the Beast God’s Spear.

Tess took slow steps towards Zhao Hai before he knelt and extended both of his shivering hands in order to receive the spear in Zhao Hai’s hand. Tears was constantly flowing out of his eyes.

Zhao Hai placed the spear on Tess’s hands as Tess inspected the spear. Before long, Tess gave a loud howl as he wept, alarming the other Diamond Apes. The others immediately went to see what was going on. When they saw the Beast God’s spear on Tess’ hands, they gawked before they all knelt to the ground and cried non stop.

The Diamond Apes entered the Northern Icefield in order to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear. They were educated by their elders about their mission from their younger years. Therefore, they immediately recognized the spear at first glance.

Adding Tess’ reaction, they didn’t doubt it at all. 5000 years, their 5000-year obsession had finally been solved!

Zhao Hai stood silently at the side. He can somewhat understand Tess’ emotion. 5000 years, how long was that? In those 5000 years, how much have they suffered, how many did they lose? A tribe of nearly 800 thousand has been reduced to 100 thousand. Who can understand such bitterness.

After some time, Tess started to calm down. Zhao Hai then turned to Tess and said, “Patriarch Tess, I’ve also cured the Beast God’s Spear’s Artifact Spirit. He can come out and tell you a few words. I won’t be listening to your conversations. I’ll come back here after a minute.”

Tess nodded, then Zhao Hai returned to Iron Mountain Fort’s living room. Seeing Zhao Hai come back, Green immediately asked, “Young Master, did you manage to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled and said, “I did, it’s currently in Tess’ hand. Rest assured, everything is fine. After Tess and the others do their ritual, I’ll immediately head to the Beastman Prairie and hand it over to the Beast King. After that, I’ll be a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen, hehe.”

Green laughed, “Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince, Dwarf Race’s Foreign Elder, the Rosen Empire’s son-in-law. Hahaha. Our Buda Clan hadn’t seen this much status since its beginning. Fantastic!”

Zhao Hai chuckled as well before saying, “After taking care of the matters in the Prairie, I’ll go and return to see the Dwarves. I want to meet Patriarch Billy and see if he had any communication with the Elves. I want to go visit the Elves. Once we unite, only then can we resist the Divine Realm.”

Green retracted his smiling expression as he turned serious and said, “Indeed. Young Master, I have thought that since we cannot just simply sell the grain that we had grown in the Wasteland, it would be better for it to be stored in the Space in preparation for the war. After all, during battles, food is one thing that must never run out.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Grandpa Green, you don’t need to worry about that. The Space already has ten backgrounds. Those backgrounds are still not used. If we plant some crops there, then we would certainly have a lot.”

Green tapped his head and said, “Ah, I forgot about those. Alright, there’s no need to save. But Young Master, how would we know the time of the Divine Race’s attack?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “We won’t. But as long as we prepare, we’re fine. But even if they don’t begin, I will still make a move. I don’t want to be too passive.”

Green stared, then he looked at Zhao Hai with bright eyes as he said, “Alright, good. It’s just as Young Master says, being too defensive is no good. Our Buda Clan had always been known for our Wild Dragon Flag. Attack has always been our forte. Offense is always good.”

Green was now very confident in Zhao Hai. One must know that the Buda Clan not only had the God ranked Cai’er, they also had more than 1 million 9th ranks. Green believed that such strength can, at the very least, contend with the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about Green’s thoughts, but he knew that he wasn’t the type of person that waits to be beaten. He knew that the other party wanted to deal with him. But they would only begin after they had made the proper preparations, explaining why they still haven’t begun.

After he heard Green, Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “After so many years of development, I don’t know what the Divine Race has right now. And there are still the Demons on the sidelines. The future of the Ark Continent wouldn’t be very good. Unfortunately, not many people knew about this. Forget it, let’s stop talking about this. Grandpa Green, no need to welcome me back. I’ll be going to Tess and see if they wanted to return to the Northern Icefield in order to do a ceremony. I’ll be leaving this place to you once again. By the way, how are Tess and the others doing? Have they become familiar with the place?”

Green smiled and said, “They have become familiar with the customs here. At this point, they basically didn’t need the guidance of the Giant Horned Bulls. Young Master can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. Then I’ll take my leave.” He said as his body flashed and vanished. Green looked at where Zhao Hai vanished and couldn’t help but mutter, “Old Master, have you ever thought that the Buda Clan would have such a day? The Young Master had grown up, he will certainly be a pride of the Buda Clan!”

This was Green’s dream, and it had been completely realized. Green knew more than Zhao Hai. At this point, everybody in the continent was aware of the Buda Clan’s strength. Green knew that even if the Buda Clan revealed the current state of the Black Wasteland, nobody would still dare to make a move on them.

Adding on to the fact that Zhao Hai would become the Beastman’s Foreign Prince, and was also a Foreign Elder of the Dwarves, his status was something that no country would dare to offend. One could even consider the current strength of the Buda Clan to be like a calamity.

Zhao Hai was unaware of Green’s thoughts. He just followed his own plan and went forward step by step. He wouldn’t care about any other things.

When Zhao Hai reappeared in front of Tess, Bloody War had already returned to the spear. After seeing Zhao Hai appear, Tess and the others immediately knelt in front of him.

Upon seeing them, Zhao Hai quickly said, “Patriarch Tess, please get up. I’m unable to receive a big ceremony like this.”

But Tess still kowtowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Patriarch, you are a huge benefactor to my Diamond Ape tribe. Not only did you take us out of the Northern icefield, you also arranged a good place for us to live as well as some cattle and argali to keep. Most importantly, you have retrieved the Beast God’s Spear for us. You’re not only a benefactor to the Diamond Ape tribe, you are a benefactor to the entire Beastman Race. So please accept our gratitude.” Then Tess knocked his head to the ground.

The other Diamond Apes also kowtowed simultaneously with Tess. This time, Zhao Hai didn’t dare to stop them. After receiving their kowtow, he said, “Alright, all of you, get up. You’re now people of the Buda Clan. You won’t need to do such a thing in the future. Just remember, no matter what you do, always consider the Buda Clan in your hearts.”

Tess and the others roared in one voice before they stood up. Zhao Hai then looked at Tess and said, “I can take you and the Beast God’s Spear back to the volcano. Do you still want to do your ceremony?’”

Tess shook his head and said, “There’s no need, Patriarch. Sir Artifact Spirit told us that he had already received the sentiment of our ancestors. So there’s no need to go back there anymore.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll be delivering the Beast God’s Spear back to the Prairie. You go continue on with your matters.” Then he took the Beast God’s Spear before vanishing in front of the group.

Chapter 607: Excitement

These past few days, the Beast King has been paying close attention to news about the Northern Icefield. From the moment Zhao Hai entered the Icefield, two months had already passed by. But until now, no new information had arrived.

He had ordered the White Tigers, Polar Bears, and the Ice Hawks to have open ears towards the Icefield. As long as something happened, they must give action. They must support Zhao Hai at all costs.

Because of this, the Ice Hawk tribe had been doing constant rounds every day. As long as they discover a trace of Zhao Hai, they would immediately go and offer him aid.

But unfortunately for them, they didn’t know that Zhao Hai had the Space. Because of this, their efforts had been in vain.

But one couldn’t blame the Beast King for being so careful, being careless would have been a much worse offense. As the matter stands, the Beast God’s Spear has apparently become very important. The Beast King had nothing else to do but be alert.

These past days, the Beast Kind didn’t have any good sleep. Nearly two months had passed, and there wasn’t any information about Zhao Hai. The Beast Kind was near to believing that Zhao Hai had failed.

While sitting in his office, the Beast King couldn’t help but give a deep sigh. He felt pity for Zhao Hai since he knew the reason why Zhao Hai wanted to look for the Divine Artifact. The Beast King always believed Zhao Hai to be a very great person that could unite the entire continent, and he wasn’t afraid of taking risks. The Beast King really hoped that Zhao Hai would succeed. But it seems like the chances had grown smaller and smaller.

But it was good that the business with the Buda Clan had remained stable. The business still stayed the same, and for the Beastmen, this was a very good thing.

Although there was that, the Beast King still couldn’t help but sigh. He was also worried about the entire Ark Continent. If Zhao Hai cannot find the Beast God’s Spear, then they would definitely be in good danger. If Zhao Hai didn’t come back in one month, then he can only task several 9th rank experts to explore the Icefield. Retrieving the Beast God’s Spear was not only a must for the Beastmen, it was important for the entire Ark Continent as well.

At this time, the Beast King’s guard suddenly walked in. With an excited face he gave his report to the Beast King, “Your Majesty, Mister Zhao Hai seeks an audience. He is outside!”

The Beast King gawked, for a while he was frozen as he stared at his guard. It took some time before he recovered, then he immediately said, “Invite him in quickly! No. I’ll go personally greet him.” Then he didn’t delay in going out.

Before long, he arrived at the tent for reception. It was obvious that the people there didn’t expect the Beast King to come personally, but they still immediately said, “We’ve seen His Majesty!”

The Beast King waved his hand and said, “Where’s Mister Zhao Hai?”

A Tiger Beastman immediately replied, “Your Majesty, he’s at the registration tent outside the palace.” The Beast King didn’t wait for him to finish before he dashed out of the palace.

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the registration tent while chatting with the Beastmen inside. The fact that he went to the Northern Icefield was a secret, there were only few Beastmen who knew about it. However, although the people in the tent were clueless, they were already familiar with Zhao Hai’s status. They knew that seeking audience with the Beast King at any time can only be done by people of revered status. Those kinds of people weren’t someone they can afford to offend.

Additionally, these Beastmen were also very grateful to Zhao Hai. As long as one was a Beastman, it was inevitable that they would make milk wine. And because of Zhao Hai’s business, their families were able to make good profit. At the same time, Zhao Hai’s Magic Lily shop was very honest in doing business. Whenever they do business, the Beastmen would never feel that they were cheated. At this point, even if Zhao Hai didn’t display his friendship flags, his name alone would gain respect from the other Beastmen.

The war had long been finished, so Human merchants had also started to come and do business. But after those people arrived, they had discovered that their business had shrunk. Even if they had traded with a tribe before, they still weren’t the tribe’s first choice. Instead, the Beastmen seem to first look to Magic Lily shop for business.

However, these Merchants can’t do anything to the shop. They simply cannot offend Magic Lily shop. First, because it was backed by the powerful Buda Clan, and second, because the Beastmen would deal with anyone that dared to take action against the shop.

At the same moment, Zhao Hai’s business alliance had also been organized. Now. the biggest business in the Prairie was Zhao Hai’s alliance. If other people wanted to do business in the Prairie, then they would have to do their best to not offend the alliance.

Naturally, Zhao Hai won’t provoke others on his own initiative. Zhao Hai knew that the Beastman Prairie was very big, it was impossible for them to swallow it’s entire market. So as long as people play fairly, Zhao Hai would not make a move. After all, Zhao Hai was never afraid of competition.

At this time, sounds of footsteps can be heard outside the tent. Zhao Hai knew that it must be the Tiger beastman that he had sent to notify the Beast King. What made him feel strange was the fact that there was one more set of footsteps that can be heard.

While Zhao Hai was thinking, the tent’s curtain was suddenly opened as a person walked from outside. Zhao Hai looked at the person and couldn’t help but stare, it was because it was the Beast King. Zhao Hai hastily got up and gave a bow, “I’ve seen His Majesty.”

The Beast King excitedly walked forward and helped Zhao Hai up. He looked at Zhao Hai and was at a loss for words because of his excitement. Zhao Hai saw the Beast King’s expression and immediately knew what he came here for. So Zhao Hai gave a gentle nod.

The Beast King’s face exploded with even more excitement, he immediately pulled Zhao Hai’s hand and said, “Mister, come with me immediately. Let’s talk somewhere else.” After that, regardless of the expressions of the other people present, Zhao Hai went with the Beast King to head towards the palace. After they were gone, the other people couldn’t help but look at each other. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this big of a position inside the Beast King’s heart. He could actually make the Beast King meet him personally.

The Beast King brought Zhao Hai to his office and had the guard protect the door. After that, the Beast King immediately said, “Mister, did you really retrieve the Beast God’s Spear?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as the Beast God Spear appeared in his hand. Zhao Hai held the spear in both hands as he carefully handed it over to the Beast King.

The Beast King’s hand couldn’t help but shake upon receiving the spear. Tears went down uncontrollably out of his eyes. He held the Beast God’s Spear gently and after a short while let out a long breath. His tears vanished as he respectfully placed the spear at an appropriate place and turned to Zhao Hai, “My deepest gratitude goes to Mister. Let me offer our gratitude in behalf of the entire Beastman race for retrieving our Divine Artifact.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty doesn’t need to be too polite. The Beast God’s Spear’s Artifact Spirit has also been restored to its original state. He can now materialize. If Your Majesty has any questions, you can just ask Sir Artifact Spirit.”

The Beast King gawked, then his two eyes turned to the Beast God’s Spear as he bowed and said, “I ask to see Sir Artifact Spirit.”

As soon as his voice ended, Bloody War immediately appeared on the spear’s shaft. He looked at Beast King and said, “You’re the current Beast King?”

When the Beast King saw Bloody War, he enthusiastically gave a bow and said, “Wei Jian has seen Sir Artifact Spirit. I am indeed the current Beast King.”

Bloody War nodded and then said, “Good, Mister Zhao Hai has already asked me to look after the Beastmen. He also asked me to confirm what the Dwarves have said. I want to tell you that everything is true. The Gods, the Divine Realm, everything. I have no other thing to say that you don’t already know.” Then his figure went back to the spear.

The Beast King gave another bow to the Beast God’s Spear. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, thank you.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Your Majesty is too polite. Sir Artifact Spirits restoration is also beneficial to the Human race. When I told him about the situation of the Beastmen and the Gods, i didn’t expect him to know about it. His words also coincided with the Dwarves’ Artifact Spirit.”

The Beast King nodded and then sighed, “It looks like mister’s speculations are real. It’s possible for the Radiant Church to be connected to the Divine Realm. But no matter what, we cannot let them off. Mister can rest assured, tomorrow, I shall announce your appointment as the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “There’s no need to rush. What His Majesty needs to do now is to prepare the Beastman race. I shall head back to the Dwarves as soon as possible. I want to see if Patriarch Billy was able to get into contact with the Elves. I don’t know about their current situation, so I wanted to take a look.”

The Beast King nodded, “Then I’ll to trouble mister with this matter. Mister can rest assured, your appointment as our Foreign Prince has already been discussed and approved by the major tribes in the Prairie. They agreed that as long as mister comes back then you would immediately receive your position. So there’s no need for a lengthy process, mister can just do his own matters immediately.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll have to thank his Majesty. Also, the Beastmen needs to save their strength at this time. In the past, the Beastmen lacked ironware, but now, with the Dwarves’ support, I think your development would be much more quicker. I also think that since the Beastmen needed to preserve their strength, wars should be minimized as much as possible. Otherwise, with the newly acquired ironware, the casualties would be too big.”

The Beast King agreed, “Mister can feel relieved. I would certainly act on it. However, the Prairie still needed grain, we’ll have to depend on mister on this matter.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Majesty doesn’t need to worry about this. Whether it be bamboo rice or bread fruit, I have tons of them. I can provide you with as many as you want at a fair price.”

The Beast King nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright. Also, I’ll need to ask mister to stay here for a meal. Otherwise, i would feel uneasy.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then I would be polite. But I think it would be better if the retrieval of the Beast God’s Spear would be held in secrecy. This could become one of our ace against the Divine Race. I’m sure that the Radiant Church is aware of the Divine Artifacts’ disappearance. Let’s have them continue that thought.”

Chapter 608: Cooperation

“Zhao Hai Buda has become a Foreign Prince of the Beastman Race!”

These words had rippled through every street and alley in the continent. Everyone knew about it, and there was no doubt that this was bomb. Everyone was stunned.

It had been less than a year after the war between the Beastmen and the Humans. But at this time, this news had suddenly spread out. A Human becoming a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen was something that was extremely startling.

Zhao Hai, who had gone quiet for two months, suddenly had his name mentioned in the continent once again. People started to discover the talent of this Patriarch of the Buda Clan. It was known that he had helped the Beastmen greatly, but nobody knew the specifics, even most Beastmen. Because of this, people started to make all kinds of speculation.

At this time, Zhao Hai was actually looking for Randolph in Dark Solder Fort. Zhao Hai told Randolph about the Divine Realm as well as what happened in the Northern Icefield. Compared to the Emperor, Zhao Hai was much more trusting towards Randolph. Zhao Hai believed that Randolph wouldn’t tell this matter to anyone else.

After listening to Zhao Hai, Randolph’s expression couldn’t help but go heavy. And after Zhao Hai left, he immediately adjusted the future plans of the Calci Family. This made people confused about what just happened.

Then Zhao Hai went to the Crook Family, however, he didn’t tell Jesse about the matters of the Divine Realm, as well as the Beast God’s Spear. He just told Jesse to adjust the future strategy of the Crook Family.

Although Jesse didn’t understand Zhao Hai’s motive, he believed that their eternal ally wouldn’t harm them. Therefore, the Crook Family started to make adjustments as well.

Naturally, these adjustments weren’t obvious. Even if it were known to outsiders, they would only think that this was just an ordinary shift, nothing else.

And although Zhao Hai visited the Imperial Palace to see the Emperor, he didn’t say anything to him. He just chatted with the Emperor for a while. And seeing that the Dead Minister didn’t leave, Zhao Hai affirmed his stance of not telling the Emperor.

After handling his matters at the Rosen Empire, Zhao Hai then went to the Buddha Empire. The bulls that was sent to the Buddha Empire had already arrived some time ago and was given to the Buddha Emperor. This made the Emperor very satisfied with Zhao Hai.

The beasts that Zhao Hai sent over were special beasts of the Herculean Bulls, therefore, their levels weren’t very low. For the Buddha Empire, this was a very crucial shipment.

Zhao Hai travelled by ship towards the Buddha Empire’s Iron Knight City. Zhao Hai went to the capital in order to discuss to the Emperor about the horse magic beasts.

Wales had sent information to Zhao Hai about the horse magic beasts. The Horse Beastmen were also willing to trade some ironware for some 4th or 5th rank horse magic beasts with Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai came this time to discuss this matter with the Emperor.

Just as Zhao Hai entered the harbor, he had discovered the Ironwood was already there. But Ironwood wasn’t wearing this full armor this time but instead just an ordinary warrior’s clothes. However, his stance still remained imposing.

When Zhao Hai disembarked from his ship, Ironwood immediately went to welcome him. Ironwood smiled and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, His Majesty is already waiting for you.”

Zhao Hai gave a bow and said, “I’ve made Vice Admiral Ironwood wait, I hope you’ll forgive me.”

Ironwood laughed and said, “Mister is always polite, that’s no good. Mister, come with me to see His Majesty.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright” Then they sat down at a carriage and rode towards the city. And since this carriage was of the Royal Palace, it was given the highest priority of way.

After they got in, Ironwood boiled a pot of tea and offered it to Zhao Hai before saying, “The bull magic beasts that mister had sent last time made His Majesty very satisfied. Ever since then, His Majesty had always wanted to express his gratitude to mister. Because of that, when His Majesty came to know that you would be arriving today, he immediately sent me over to welcome you.”

Zhao Hai immediately replied, “His Majesty is too polite. I’m only a Merchant, doing business is our great pleasure. Since I accepted his Majesty’s request, then it was natural that I would need to deliver on that promise.”

Ironwood laughed and said, “Mister is certainly not an ordinary merchant. To be honest, this one admires mister. I didn’t expect you to become a Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince. That’s too great of an achievement. In the past millenium, you are the first person to become a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s really not that special. I just helped the Beastmen slightly. And because of his gratitude, the Beast King decided to confer me with this title. Actually, I don’t have any authority on the Beastmen.”

Ironwood smiled and said, “Mister doesn’t need to be so modest. I heard that to be a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen, it would more than their gratitude for them to agree. Mister must have helped them a great deal.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I did. But to be honest, they can also do what I just did. It’s just that I’m much more suitable for the job. Hehe.”

When Ironwood heard Zhao Hai, he knew that there was no chance of him knowing what that thing was. So he didn’t ask any questions about it. He just smiled and said, “Since Mister has become the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince, then wouldn’t it be much easier for you to acquire magic beasts?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s not that easy.  Beastmen’s temperament is not quite good, even the Beast King cannot fully command them, much less a Foreign Prince. The Prairie has a lot of unique magic beasts, but I can only send some bull magic beasts at this time. However, I had recently been in contact with the Horse Beastmen in order to trade for their magic beasts hopefully.”

Ironwood’s eyes turned bright, horse type magic beasts were the most compatible types for being a mount. If they could have a lot a horse magical beasts, the Buddha Empire’s cavalry would be elevated to another level.

It didn’t take long before the carriage arrived at the Imperial Palace. Then they were welcomed to a small hall where the Buddha Emperor was already waiting for them.

After exchanging greetings with the Emperor and being bestowed a seat, the Buddha Emperor smiled and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, we’ve troubled you a lot. My Buddha Empire is very thankful for mister’s efforts.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “This one doesn’t dare. Your Majesty is too polite, I was just doing what I needed to do.”

The Emperor looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Although there weren’t a lot of beasts last time, it still gave me hope for our future cooperation with mister.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “A long-term cooperation with Your Majesty would be good. It would give a lot of profits to me. Your Majesty, I came this time to tell you that I had managed to come in contact with the Horse tribe through the Cows. They also want to trade their horse magic beasts but on the condition that they would also be traded with ironware. What does Your Majesty think about this?”

When the Emperor heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but knit his brows. The ironware of the Buddha Empire were of very high quality, this was because the Buddha Empire’s ironware were mostly made by the Dwarves. It wasn’t a problem if the Buddha Empire were to sell them off, but the Buddha Emperor was afraid that the Beastmen would use the iron to attack the Human lands. When that time comes, he would be a criminal among the humans. Moreover, other nations would also seize that opportunity to deal with his Empire.

After thinking about it, the Emperor couldn’t help but turn to ZHao Hai and asked, “Mister, you’re a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen, can you tell me what the Beastmen intend to do with these ironware?”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he smiled and said, “I can understand your worries, Young Majesty. Although I don’t have much authority in the Prairie, I am still privy to inside information. Is Your Majesty worried that the Beastmen would invade the humans? I can tell Your Majesty that you can rest assured. I got information that the Beast King would soon be issuing a Sealed Blade Command!”

The Buddha Emperor couldn’t help but be shocked. He knew that the Beastman Race’s Sealed Black Command was an order for the Beastmen to rest and build up strength. As long as the Beast King announces this command, no Beastman Race would resort to any violence, whether it be exterior of interior. Only when their survival was threatened would the Beastmen be allowed to attack. In other words, as long as there is the Sealed Blade Command, wars between Beastmen and with Humans would not occur. Unless the Humans make the first move.

The Buddha Emperor couldn’t help but looked straight into Zhao Hai’s eyes and say, “Is mister telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I won’t dare to deceive Your Majesty. Rest assured, I’m quite sure that the Beastmen would issue a Sealed Blade Command.”

The Buddha Emperor nodded, he thought for a moment before saying, “If it is like this, then that would be good news. As soon as the Beast King announces the Sealed Blade Command, I would immediately agree to the Horse Tribe’s business.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, it would only take a few days before it’ll get announced. Just give word and leave the rest to me.”

The reason that Zhao Hai mentioned the Sealed Blade Command to the Buddha Emperor was to let the Buddha Emperor agree to his business with the Dwarves. Although he can get to the Dwarves without seeing the Emperor, he didn’t want any conflict between the Dwarf Race and the Buddha Empire. The Dwarves needed to rest and build up strength as well in order to prepare for the Divine Race and the future war. If any conflict occurs with the Buddha Empire, then the Dwarves wouldn’t have time to rest.

Zhao Hai believed that the Buddha Emperor would agree to his cooperation with the Dwarves. The reason why the Buddha Empire held tightly on to the Dwarf ironware was because the Empire didn’t want the others to use it to attack their country. Zhao Hai reckoned that selling to the Beastmen who were several nations away from them would be just fine.

The Buddha Empire’s agreement was also because of Zhao Hai’s performance. The last time that Zhao Hai went to the Dwarves, he told the Buddha Emperor that he wouldn’t sell the ironware to the Rosen Empire. Sure enough, Zhao Hai didn’t take the Dwarf Ironware to the Rosen Empire. This made the Buddha Emperor trust him more.

Chapter 609: Sea Race Incident

After a few days, the Beastmen did indeed issue an order announcing the Prairie’s Sealed Blade Command. But at this time, Zhao Hai had already arrived at Dwarf Iron Mountain.

Now that Zhao Hai was their Foreign Elder, Zhao Hai was immediately welcomed to Billy’s village after arriving at the mountain.

Billy personally welcomed Zhao Hai to his house. And after they had sat down, Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what happened? You suddenly became the Foreign Prince of the Beastmen, was that because you helped them restore their Artifact Spirit?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Not only that. The Beastmen had lost the Beast God’s Spear in the Northern Icefield 5000 years ago. Although they had been seeking for it the whole time, nobody was able to succeed. This time, I went to the Northern Icefield to help them retrieve their Beast God’s Spear. Because of that they gave me the position of Foreign Prince.”

Billy immediately replied, “Lost? How come? That’s their Divine Artifact.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then told Billy about the matter with the Diamond Apes. Billy nodded and said, “So it was like that. No wonder the Diamond Apes were sent into exile. When I read from our records that the Diamond Apes were sent to exile, I immediately became confused. After all, they were the Royal Tribe. So it was actually because of the Beast God’s Spear.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Beast God’s Spear has now been returned to the Beastmen. Moreover, its artifact spirit has been restored. The Beastmen will also issue a Sealed Blade Command, having themselves rest and buildup their strength. The Dwarves should do it as well. My ironware business with the Dwarves has already been approved by the Buddha Emperor since he wanted me to buy some magic beasts from the Beastmen. As the matter stands, he would not say a word about our business in the future. I just had to ask him since I want to maintain the good relationship between the Dwarves and the Buddha Empire. Peace is very important to your race at this time.”

Billy nodded and then said, “You really do think far into the future. Then what do we do next?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Not much really, as long as our current plans go through, everything should be fine. I’ve also started to stockpile some grain and daily necessities to act as strategic resources in the future.”

Billy nodded, “You can rest assured about the situation with the Dwarves. Although we had sold a lot of weapons outside, we still have very ample amount of stock still left. Moreover, these are our best products, much better quality than those we sell outside. So you don’t need to worry about weapons.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Our transactions in the future would still continue, just keep storing the warehouse. Right, you told me that you’ll find some people who will settle on the Black Wasteland. Did you manage to find them?”

Billy nodded, “I’ve picked some. At this point, there are more than 100 Dwarves that are willing to settle down in Iron Mountain fort. So when do you plan on getting them there?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment before he said, “Let them wait here first, I still need to prepare their place. But when they arrive there, they might not be working on metals the whole time. I might need them for something else.”

Billy smiled, “Don’t worry, I’ve already told them about that.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright. Also, if you dig up any special things, please leave some of them for me. I’m quite curious about those types of stuff.”

Billy couldn’t help but laugh, “That’s not a problem, rest assured.”

Then Zhao Hai said, “So how about the Elves? Did they send a reply?”

Billy smiled bitterly and said, “The matter with the Elves are doing just fine. Those guys are just slow. They said that they must observe first before sending proper word to us. So you don’t need to worry about it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he didn’t know anything about the Elves. Since Billy said that there’s no need to worry, then he would just wait. In any case, the Radiant Church wouldn’t start their plan in a short time. However, it seems like Zhao Hai’s plan to level up in the Elven Forest would have to be moved to a later time.”

Zhao Hai stayed for a day with the Dwarves before he returned to Golden Island using the Space. He wanted to know the current status of the island.

Zhao Hai already received word that the Hurricane Family’s Kristen had already arrived at the island and had started to do business there. The business that they had was very simple and was similar to the Buda Clan, grain and other basic necessities. Zhao Hai had also heard that their business was doing good.

Zhao Hai has not gone to see Kristen because his attention was taken by another piece of news. Kun just told Zhao Hai that the business with the Sea Race has been very unstable. The Rock Shrimps had also been recently reducing their business.

This news was very important for Zhao Hai. His business with the Sea Race was one of his more important businesses. If this business were to be broken, then it would have a huge influence to the Buda Clan. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to check the Marine Races personally.

But before that, Zhao Hai had Green empty out some land in the Black Wasteland so that the Dwarves can have their own place. Zhao Hai invited the Dwarves not only because he wanted them to work on his metals, but also to teach the slaves their craftsmanship.

Although the Space was also producing some iron ore, it wasn’t a lot. On the other hand, among the slaves that Zhao Hai had bought, there were also several blacksmiths among them. However, the craftsmanship of these slaves weren’t very good. Because of that Zhao Hai decided to invite some Dwarves to settle in the wasteland.

Green was already used to these kinds of things. But this time, Green had no idea of Dwarf customs. After all, he hadn’t contacted any Dwarves in the past.

Zhao Hai also asked Billy and was told that there were no special requirements at all. So Zhao Hai can only ask Green to continue while he returned to Golden Island and rode a ship towards the reef where the Rock Shrimps were living in.

The route was already visited by Zhao Hai many times, so naturally he wouldn’t get lost. Moreover, the pirates at the sea were already aware of the Buda Clan ships that would head towards the deep seas to get some marine products.

The influence to the Buda Clan in the sea was very strong that the pirates would just go around their ships, so the route was very safe.

Five days later, Zhao Hai had officially entered the deep seas. But he felt strange since there weren’t any Sea people that came to see him. In the past, people would’ve already been alerted to his presence and were already meeting him.

Because of this, Zhao Hai opened his monitor and looked at the surroundings. Aside from small magic beasts, there was nothing in the vicinity, even Sea people.

Along with Zhao Hai were Laura and the others who were basking in the sun. They also felt strange so Laura said, “Brother Hai, wasn’t this the Sea Race’s domain? Where’s everybody? Did they go lazy?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “Not necessarily. For them to reduce their business only meant that there was an internal problem going on. This situation proved this point.”

Laura knit her eyebrows and said, “Problems? What problems would sea people have?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Who knows? Only after meeting them would this matter be clarified.” Then suddenly a Rock Shrimp tribesman appeared on the monitor.

Zhao Hai turned the monitor off as the Rock Shrimp appeared near Zhao Hai’s ship. The Rock Shrimp looked at the emblem on the ship and decided to not attack. Then he asked, “Is this the Buda Clan’s ship?”

Zhao Hai went to the ship’s bow and gave bow to the Rock Shrimp in the water and said, “Buda Clan’s Patriarch Zhao Hai has seen Brother Rock Shrimp.”

As soon as the Rock Shrimp heard Zhao Hai’s title, he couldn’t help but stare. But he almost immediately replied, “So it is Patriarch Zhao Hai. This one has been very disrespectful. Can I ask why Patriarch Zhao Hai has come?”

Then Zhao Hai replied, “I have a matter to discuss with the Rock Shrimp Tribe Patriarch. Can I go and see him?”

The Rock Shrimp looked at Zhao Hai and awkwardly said, “I’ll be unfair to Patriarch Zhao Hai, but our Rock Shrimp Tribe has gotten into some serious matter. I’m afraid that the Patriarch wouldn’t be able to have the time to see you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ll just ask brother to send word out for me. I really do have something to talk to the Patriarch.”

The Rock Shrimp couldn’t help but feel awkward at Zhao Hai’s answer. But he also knew that they couldn’t offend the Buda Clan. Their Rock Shrimp Tribe was just a very small tribe. Without Zhao Hai, they would have huge problems with their yearly tribute.

After thinking for a moment, the Rock Shrimp gave a bow and said, “Then I’ll go send word. I’ll have to ask Patriarch Zhao Hai to wait for a moment.” Then the Rock Shrimp dove back down into the sea and headed back to his tribe.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also had the undead lower the ship’s anchor as he waited for the Rock Shrimp to come back. However, Zhao Hai had confirmed that there was indeed some issues that happened within the Sea Race.

Zhao Hai’s original plan was to take care of the Elves first before he takes a look at the Sea Race. No matter what, the Sea Race also held a large population in this world. If the Gods did indeed want to rule this plane, then they certainly won’t ignore the people of the Sea. Therefore, Zhao Hai also wanted to make an alliance with them.

Now that the matter with the Elves was pushed back, the Sea Race unexpectedly developed an incident. This was good for Zhao Hai since he can take care of this matter instead.

Zhao Hai didn’t wait for a long time before the Rock Shrimp Patriarch appeared near the Haven. Then Zhao Hai gave a bow to the Rock Shrimp Patriarch before he said, “I’ve taken the liberty to disturb the Patriarch. I hope that you forgive me.”

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t expect Patriarch Zhao Hai to come here personally. May I know Patriarch Zhao Hai’s reason for the visit?” Although he was smiling, Zhao Hai can notice a subtle worry in the old Rock Shrimp’s face. It seems like his people had encountered something big this time.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The reason I came to Patriarch this time was to ask your help. I just want to have an audience with the Leader of the Sea Race.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the old Rock Shrimp couldn’t help but stare. When he recovered, he clarified Zhao Hai’s words, “Patriarch, you mean that you want to meet with the Sea King?”

Only at this moment did Zhao Hai know that the Sea Race’s Patriarch was called the Sea King. But nobody can blame his for this, contact between the Sea Race and the Humans was too few. Humans didn’t even know the races in the sea. They were only collectively known as the Sea Race, and that they had a ruler.

Upon hearing that the ruler of the Sea Race was named Sea King, Zhao Hai immediately responded, “i have an important matter to discuss with the Honorable Sea King. I’m asking Patriarch to help me send word. Can I ask you to do this?”

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Why would Patriarch want to see the Sea King? To be honest, my tribe doesn’t have the influence to even see the Sea King.”

Zhao Hai’s expression sank as he said, “Patriarch, this matter is extremely important. Tell the Sea King that aside from being the Patriarch of the Buda Clan and the son-in-law of the Rosen Emperor, I’m also a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen as well as a Foreign Elder of the Dwarves. Tell the Sea King that my visit involves a major event of the world. I ask the Patriarch to relay these words.”

Zhao Hai’s long string of titles made the Rock Shrimp Patriarch’s expression change. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be so influential. The Sea Race might not have any idea about the relationship between the Humans and the Dwarves, but they were extremely familiar with the Beastmen.

Races from the Ark Continent and the Sea Race didn’t have much contact, with the only exception being the Beastmen. This was because the Beastmen also had tribes that lived on water. These Beastmen might not be fully living in water, but their lifestyles were closely tied to it. Some of these Beastmen lived on beaches while some lived on islands. Because of this, when Zhao Hai revealed that he was a Foreign Prince of the Beastman Race, the Rock Shrimp Patriarch’s heart couldn’t help but jump.

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch immediately gave Zhao Hai a bow before saying, “I didn’t expect Patriarch to be a Foreign Prince of the Beastmen. This one has been disrespectful. However, this one didn’t lie. Our Rock Shrimp tribe is indeed too small to have an audience with the Honored Sea King. I’m afraid I won’t be able to help you much in this regard.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows and said, “I’ll ask the Patriarch to please find a way. I came this time not because of business. This matter shall affect all of the races in this world. I sincerely ask for Patriarch’s help.”

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai’s face and couldn’t help but be moved. They had been doing business with the Buda Clan for quite some time. The Buda Clan’s business conduct is extremely good and they give very fair prices. This gave the Rock Shrimp Patriarch a very good impression towards the Buda Clan. And now that he saw how sincere Zhao Hai was, he couldn’t help but believe in Zhao Hai’s words. It seems like there really was something big going on.

Chapter 610: Swordfish Tribe

If it was like what Zhao Hai thought that the Fishman was having an internal problem, then the previously unqualified Rock Shrimp tribe would become qualified to see the Sea King, given the special situation.

The reason why this was possible was the enormity of the population among the Fishman. There were some people who would want to challenge the authorities, and those people were no doubt strong, and they might even have strong allies as well. At this time, the Sea King would want to pull even the smallest power he can find. And the weak Rock Shrimp Tribe was one of those.

It was precisely because of this that the Rock Shrimp Patriarch was allowed an audience with the Sea King. And the reason why Zhao Hai approached the Rock Shrimp Patriarch and not going directly to the Sea King was because he wanted to make an impression on the old Rock Shrimp.

Since they did good business with them before, the Rock Shrimp Patriarch believed in Zhao Hai’s words.

However, it would still take some time before the Rock Shrimp Patriarch can prepare. So he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I can try and seek help from a larger tribe with regards to this matter. But before that, can mister show me proof of your status as the Foreign Prince of the Beastman Race?”

When Zhao Hai heard the old Rock Shrimp, he knew that he had succeeded. So he immediately said, “Of course, there’s no problem.” Then he took out the Beatman Command token and threw it over to the Rock Shrimp Patriarch.

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch received the token and looked at it. The Fishman also had their own records, and among their writings were magnificent stories about the outside world. Among them was the Prince’s Command Token of the Beastmen. This token was made with a kind of beast bone that was strong as steel and was as heavy as black iron. There was no way for this token to be replicated by other people.

When the Rock Shrimp Patriarch received the Prince’s Token, he immediately knew that it was the real thing. One must know that one of the heaviest metals in the Ark Continent was black iron. And it was impossible for other people to mistake it for something else. However, the Beastmen actually managed to replicate the weight of black iron with a beast bone. There was no records of what bone was able to do this.

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch looked at the Prince Command Token and then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please give me time, about a few days or so. I’ll do my best to find a way. Is that alright?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “There’s still time, so it won’t be a big deal. But this matter is also important and must be told to the honorable Sea King. I’ll have to trouble Patriarch for this.”

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch looked at Zhao Hai and then nodded, “Alright. Mister can rest assured. This one would certainly do everything that is possible.” Then he gave Zhao Hai a small bow before diving back down into the sea.

Shortly after the Rock Shrimps had gone down, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “It seems like the Fishman did have an incident. Otherwise the Rock Shrimps would be certain that they wouldn’t see the Sea King. The Patriarch wouldn’t have thought that there was indeed a way.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he also carefully used his words in order to probe for answers. If the Rock Shrimp Patriarch really didn’t have a way, then he wouldn’t even dare to promise him. After all, the Rock Shrimps really needed human commodities, so he wouldn’t risk himself offending Zhao Hai. But since the old Rock Shrimp agreed, then there might really be a possibility. This basically meant that some instability has happened within the Fishman.

Although Zhao Hai had no understanding about the matters of the Fishman, he can still speculate from the business between the Buda Clan and the Rock Shrimp Tribe. Since the Rock Shrimp tribe can’t buy up all of the Buda Clan’s supplies, then the Buda Clan already had a metric about the Rock Shrimp tribes’ size.

From what Zhao Hai can see, the Rock Shrimp Tribe had similar standing with the Giant Horned Bulls as well as the Black Bellied Pig Tribe that Zhao Hai had met when the first entered the Prairie. They were people placed at the bottom of the power pyramid. Therefore, how could such a tribe be able to have an audience with the Sea King?

The Rock Shrimp Tribe being able to promise an audience was indeed a very strange thing. It was due to this that Zhao Hai knew that the Fishman had a giant accident. Otherwise the Rock Shrimp Patriarch wouldn’t have been so sure.

Lizzy turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, what do you think happened in the Fishman?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I can’t possibly know. But from how the Rock Shrimp Patriarch has been acting, I’m afraid that the structure of the Fishman has become unstable. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have been able to see the Sea King. The Sea King might have been scrounging up people in order to gain enough strength to hold into power.”

Megan nodded and said, “That’s extremely possible. If this is really the case, then I’m afraid that it’s not the time for us to come here. I think that the Sea King wouldn’t have time to get to see us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Not really. Perhaps we came just in time. If we can help the Sea King solve this crisis, then we might have more leverage in discussing with the Fishman.”

Meg knit her brows as he said, “Young Master, but this is the sea. Compared to the Ark Continent, this place is much larger. It’s possible that there are innumerable experts here. Do we really need to take part in this conflict?”

Among his wives, only Meg kept calling him Young Master, even if they had already been married for so long. This made Zhao Hai feel strange, he had already told Meg about this many times, but Meg seems to not be willing to change it.

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Even if there are a lot of experts in the sea, don’t we have much more? This time, I want to talk about the Divine Realm with the Sea King. The Fishman has the most population in this world. If they can help us deal with the Divine Race and the Demons, then we would have a much easier time doing so.

Laura nodded, “If that’s true, then that would be good. But Brother Hai, I’m afraid this would be more difficult than we imagine. After all, the war in the seas among the Fishman is much different compared to other places.

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “I’ve already had Cai’er prepare for this. There are now 9th rank undeads in the Space, and some of them are creatures of the sea. They should be stronger in terms of undersea battles. With the help of those guys, I think we won’t have much of a problem.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but smile and said, “So Brother Hai had already thought of it. Then we might only have small troubles undersea. But unfortunately, we can’t go underwater.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Why couldn’t we? I’ve already asked Cai’er to transform a Blade Scale Whale into an undead like Alien. When the time comes, we can just ride the whale and then go underwater.”

Megan became happy after she heard Zhao Hai, “Fantastic. I really wanted to see what the bottom of the sea looks like. I didn’t expect Big Brother Hai to be already prepared. So when do we go?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Don’t worry. If we go now, the Rock Shrimps might get offended. It’s much better to wait for the Rock Shrimp Patriarch to come back with news. I don’t think it would take him long to come back. Let’s just wait for him for a few days.”

Megan pouted her mouth before she nodded. Zhao Hai smiled, he also wanted to go underwater but it was not yet the time. He still hasn’t gained the approval of the Sea King. If he were to enter the seas right now, he would get attacked by them.

Although he was on his ship, Zhao Hai’s contact with the continent remained unbroken. Neither his business with the Beastmen nor Dwarves were getting affected.

Seven days later, Zhao Hai, who had been paying attention for the Rock Shrimps, suddenly spotted the Rock Shrimps along with their Patriarch. Zhao Hai immediately went to the ship’s deck. And sure enough, as soon as he arrived on top of the deck, he heard a Rock Shrimp say, “We request to see Mister Zhao Hai.”

Then Zhao Hai led Laura and the others to the bow of the ship to see the Rock Shrimp Patriarch. Seeing the old Shrimp’s tired face, Zhao hai immediately gave a bow and said, “I’ve seen the Patriarch.”

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch returned the bow as he said, “The Sea King agreed to have an audience with mister. Please follow me.”

Zhao Hai quickly responded, “Thanks, Patriarch.” Then the Rock Shrimp Patriarch nodded and then rode the bow of the ship. Zhao Hai knew that this was for him to guide the ship. So Zhao Hai immediately had the undead raise the anchor while hoisting the sails as he followed the Rock Shrimps towards the deeper parts of the sea.

A lot of Rock Shrimps were swimming alongside Zhao Hai’s ship. Seeing the Rock Shrimp Patriarch and the others, Zhao Hai was not sure if this was an escort or surveillance.

Zhao Hai and the others sat in the ship while looking at the monitor to see the situation. The ocean was indeed very big that it seemed limitless. The Haven was considered to be quick for a merchant ship. But compared to the Rock Shrimps, it was having a hard time catching up.

Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that the route that they were taking was very safe. They were completely safe along the way. They didn’t encounter any attacks, nor did they encounter any reefs or unpredictable undercurrents.

At night, the Rock Shrimp Patriarch would lead his people to rest in the sea. Zhao Hai also stopped his ship and waited for the next day. This cycle was repeated for ten days.

In these ten days, Zhao Hai already saw a lot of Sea Tribes. There were Turtles as well as numerous Fishes. Because of their numbers, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to correctly identify each one of them.

And these tribes always came to the Rock Shrimp patriarch since they were encroaching on their domain, there were even some who were intending to rob them. However, when the Rock Shrimp Patriarch showed a token, the opposite party allowed them to pass. But although they were allowed passage, the Fishmen still looked at Zhao Hai with curiosity.

Zhao Hai also knew that this was because of the long time where there was no contact between Humans and the Fishmen. So when they saw him, it was natural that they would feel interested.

In these ten days, Zhao Hai was expecting that he would be led to the Sea King. But he didn’t expect the Rock Shrimp Patriarch to bring him to the Swordfish Tribe’s Domain.

The reason why Zhao Hai identified the other party was because of their very special mounts. Their mounts had a very long bone spike that can be used as a spear, it looked very hard. Moreover, the fish was very big, about ten meters in length. On its back were big fins, which seemed to express power and prestige.

Riding atop these swordfishes were people who had the same kind of fins on their heads, looking like a well combed hair. The person was holding a long bone spear and was about two meters in height. It’s black skin looked slippery with mucus while he wore armor made of shells and seaweeds. He looked like a very powerful warrior.

Chapter 611: Stone Column Island

Zhao Hai saw on the monitor that the Rock Shrimp Patriarch gave the Swordfish man a salute. Then after a bit of talking, he presented a token to the Swordfish tribesman.

The Swordfish tribesman received the token and after taking a look at it, he nodded. Then the Rock Shrimp Patriarch and the others returned to the sea’s surface.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation and understood that he wasn’t here to see the Sea King. The Rock Shrimp Patriarch can only escort him up to here.

After that, just as Zhao Hai closed the monitor, the Rock Shrimp Patriarch’s was heard outside, “I ask Mister Zhao Hai to please come out.” Then Zhao Hai and the others went on to the ship’s bow to see the Rock Shrimp Patriarch as well as the Swordfish tribesman. The Swordfish was still sitting on his mount, he came along with his men. All them looked at Zhao Hai with a hint of curiosity.

Zhao Hai gave a bow and said, “I’ve seen the Rock Shrimp Patriarch and brother Fishman. Why did Patriarch call for me?”

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch returned the bow and then said, “Mister, we can only take you up to here. This is the Junior Patriarch of the Swordfish tribe. The next step would be up to him.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “I thank the Patriarch for his efforts. The Patriarch doesn’t need to worry, I have already sent a letter back to the family, they will be sending you two shipments worth of supplies. That would be my gratitude for Patriarch’s help. The Patriarch would just need to wait in your place and the ships would arrive in a few days. Please don’t refuse this gift.”

The Rock Shrimp Patriarch’s face couldn’t help but burst in glee, “Then mister Zhao Hai has my deepest gratitude. Junior Patriarch, Mister Zhao Hai is a very good person. Please take care of him.”

The Junior Patriarch of the Swordfish tribe looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, “I will. Patriarch Libben can rest assured.” The Rock Shrimp Patriarch then nodded and gave a bow to Zhao Hai before he submerged back to the sea.

Zhao Hai turned to the Junior Patriarch of the Swordfish tribe, he gave a bow and said, “Zhao Hai has seen Junior Patriarch, I apologize for the trouble.”

The Junior Patriarch of the Swordfish tribe was polite to Zhao Hai as well. He returned Zhao Hai’s bow and said, “Mister is too polite. The Sea King had issued summons for mister, so naturally we wouldn’t dare to ignore it. Mister, please come with us.” Then the Junior Patriarch went to the front of the Haven. The other Knights looked at Zhao Hai before they went to the sides of the ship and escorted it.

Zhao Hai discovered that the Junior Patriarch of the Swordfish tribe seemed to dislike having in contact with him. However, this Junior Patriarch also seemed to be very strong. Zhao Hai estimated this Junior Patriarch to be equivalent to an 8th rank human expert.

Zhao Hai has no way to calculate a Fishman’s age, so he didn’t know how old this Junior Patriarch was. But what he definitely knew was that this Junior Patriarch was not old for his race. For him to be 8th rank was a proof of his extraordinary talent.

Moreover, Zhao Hai also discovered that this Junior Patriarch’s army was very unified. These Swordfish Knights under his command, although only about 500, were comprised of 6th to 7th rank experts. These people were very unified that even in motion they still kept their proper formation.

Zhao Hai also paid close attention to the Swordfish knights’ reaction towards the Junior Patriarch. They seem to have no hint of resistance to his command, some of them even carried expressions of worship. This showed that the commanding power of this Junior Patriarch was very great.

An army this sharp usually held great pride. Even if one’s status was high, if they don’t believe your strength, then they would find it hard to follow you and would only look down on you. However, this Junior Patriarch seemed to have completely conquered these people. There was no need to doubt his strength and skill in handling his army.

Zhao Hai wanted to talk to this Junior Patriarch, but it seems like this Junior Patriarch was unwilling to talk to him. Zhao Hai tribed to open up a conversation only to be turned down with short answers. In the end, Zhao Hai chose to give up.

Following Laura and the others in returning to the Space, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but chuckle, “Brother Hai, they actually chose to ignore you. I haven’t seen that before.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “It’s just his arrogance. Hehe, this is the first time I’ve seen someone do that to me.”

Meg suddenly got fired up, “His arrogance is useless. Compared to the Young Master, his strength is just nothing. He actually acted disrespectfully to Young Master, you should go and teach him a lesson.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Calm down, we’re still in their domain. In addition, this Junior Patriarch is still young. Being this young and already strong is commendable. After all, he didn’t have the help of the Space.”

Although Meg nodded, her face still couldn’t hide her indignation. In her heart, Zhao Hai was the best, he was the strongest of them all. She would get angry if anyone were to dare to be impolite to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai thought that he would be seeing the Sea King after only a few days. But he didn’t expect the ship to travel for 20 days. On the 20th day, Zhao Hai discovered that there was a rainbow like radiance in the distance.

Zhao Hai opened the monitor and immediately became shocked. The rainbow lights was not too far. But after seeing what it was, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare at the scenery, surprised.

What Zhao Hai saw was an island. But this island was peculiar, it wasn’t connected to the sea but was instead held up by 13 huge pillars on the water.

He didn’t know how these stone pillars were produced, but there were many holes on each pillar of which water kept flowing out. The water produced mist that would in turn make the rainbows.

Zhao Hai also saw that in those holes, Merpeople can be seen. These merpeople had the upper bodies of humans but had a lower body of a fish. They all had long golden hair and dark blue eyes. Their chests were covered by shells while the others parts were left exposed. They looked pure with a tint of temptation. Their appearance made people unable to look away.

Laura and the others were also dumbfounded upon seeing these people. They also didn’t think that there would be such a place. The mists kept coming as an endless amount of water kept pouring down the pillars. There were also the attractive mermaids. This made them feel like they were in a fairytale.

After some time, Laura and the others recovered. Their mouths couldn’t help but release a sound of wonder. Zhao Hai was also the same, this scenery was indeed too beautiful.

At this time, the Haven was already slowly approaching the place. After heading to the island for some time, they were immediately blocked by a gigantic Fishman. This man’s stature was very tall and big. He was even taller than the biggest Beastman. It had blue skin and was as tall as Zhao Hai’s stone golem and looked just as strong. He held a huge trident on one hand that was about 20 meters long, it looked quite heavy.

The bodies of these people don’t seem to be different from humans. The sole difference were some parts of their body as well as their enormous tail. The tail was very robust, Zhao Hai seemed to identify it as something that belonged to a whale.

These people had their mounts as well. Each one of them had huge blue whales that carried them on their backs. They looked extraordinarily formidable. After they blocked the Junior Patriarch of the Swordfish tribe, the Junior Patriarch immediately took the token that was handed over by the Rock Shrimp Patriarch and gave it to the opposite party. The huge fishman nodded before he waved his hand, sending the Junior Patriarch away.

Although the Junior Patriarch was arrogant, he still wouldn’t dare to pull rank against these Whale Fishmen. The Junior Patriarch bowed to the Whale fishman before he retreated. The Whales then started to slowly float towards the surface.

When the Whale fishman started to appear on the surface, Zhao Hai can immediately feel the pressure coming out of them. These Whale fishmen on top of the whale mounts looked just like the ancient giants from the legends. Their heights had surpassed the deck of the ship.

Before Zhao Hai could speak, one Whale fishman said, “You are Zhao Hai?” His voice rumbling, it was as deep as thunder.

Zhao Hai didn’t get frightened, he immediately gave a bow and said, “Brother Fishman, I am indeed Zhao Hai.”

The Whale fishman looked at Zhao Hai and said, “The Sea King has summoned you. Go retrieve your sails.” Zhao Hai complied as he had the undead take down the sails of the ship.

Just as the sails were taken down, two Whale fishmen arrived by his ship and extended their hands towards the Haven’s bow before pushing it towards the small island.

Zhao Hai looked at these Whale fishmen, he didn’t think that these soldiers would have this strength. They seem to push an Ironclad Five masted ship with absolutely no effort.

It didn’t take a long time for them to arrive at the vicinity of the small island. However, Zhao Hai cannot walk at this time. This was because surrounding the small island were all kinds of reefs. There was simply no way for the ship to continue.

Zhao Hai also saw some Mermaids on the reefs. These mermaids looked curiously at Zhao Hai. Once in a while they would whisper some words to their companions before bell-like laughters echoed out.

About one kilometer away from a column, the Haven stopped. The Whale fishman then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You come to my mount’s back. I’ll take you further.”

Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude before leading Laura and the others to the back of the whale. When they arrived on top of the whale, they discovered that they were only as tall as the Whale fishman’s feet. It seems like if the Whale fishman wants to, he could step on them.

The Whale fishman turned his head to Zhao Hai as he cracked a smile. Then he led his whale mount to swim towards the island. Before long, they had passed by the stone columns and reached the middle column of the island. Zhao Hai noted that the stone column seem to be several hundred meters high. The waters from the holes above also kept flowing down. On top of this stone column was a palace, something that Zhao Hai has not seen before.

Chapter 612: Queen

The Whales took Zhao Hai to the stone pillar. The holes on this pillar weren’t small, however, the Whales were still unable to go up.

The Whale fishman shouted towards the stone pillar, “Old Turtle, please come out.” Just as his voice fell, a person suddenly appeared from the bottom of the stone pillar. After seeing him come out, Zhao Hai found out that this man was a Turtle fishman. He wore trousers made of seaweed with an upper body of a turtle, with a carapace protecting his front and back.

The Turtle fishman looked at the Whale fishman and said, “You called me?”

The Whale looked at the Turtle and said, “This is mister Zhao Hai. He’s someone that the Sea King had summoned. I ask the old Turtle Fishman to help me bring him up.”

The Turtle fishman looked at Zhao Hai and then said, “You are Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I am Zhao Hai.” Then the Turtle nodded. He waved as several turtles appeared from the stone pillar. These turtles weren’t large, their shells were only about two meters in diameter.

The Turtle fishman turned his head to Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Stand on them, I’ll go take you to the top.” Zhao Hai nodded, and then stood on the back of a turtle before they were taken up the stone pillar.

Upon entering this pillar, Zhao Hai had found out that it actually was a maze. There were plenty of interconnected channels inside and each of them had their own water currents. In the end, the Turtle fishman had brought Zhao Hai to a steadily flowing part of the pillar.

This pillar was unexpectedly a water slide. Each pillar had rushing water cascading down. One could clearly see that the water was very deep.

Zhao Hai felt strange, he was surprised as to how the Fishmen were able to do this. How did they manage to place a large amount of water in such a place? It was really amazing.

However, the turtles seem to not care about it as they swam against the stream. All of them were steadily going upward with speed that couldn’t be described as slow.

Zhao Hai counted probably about half an hour before they reached the top of the pillar. The position that they were in now was actually a big pool. An in the middle of this pool was a palace.

The palace was constructed beautifully. It was made out of white stone with its top being a blue tent. On the walls were endless pearls and crystals. These pearls and crystals made for an attractive sight. They sparkled under the sunlight, and they seem to be intricately arranged that their reflections had illuminated the big pool. The illuminations on the pool showed different Fishman tribes, it was very beautiful.

Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but be in awe with such a scene. They didn’t expect that they would be able to see such a beautiful place. At this time, the Turtle fishman stopped at the pull. Then the old Turtle Fishman turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, please come ashore. Some people would be meeting you there.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he gave a bow to the old Turtle Fishman and said, “I thank Brother Fishman.” Then he took a step towards the shore along with Laura and the others.

After seeing that the group had come to shore, the old Turtle Fishman then turned around to leave along with the turtles. But at this time, a person walked out of the palace. This person was a blonde haired woman with blue eyes. In her hand was a crystal staff. She wore a green robe on her body. It was evident that her robe was made out of seaweed.

The woman went towards ZHao Hai and bowed. Then she smiled and said, “Are you the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince, and the Dwarves’ Foreign Elder, Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai recovered, then he bowed hastily and said, “I am indeed Zhao Hai. May I know who the young lady is?”

The woman smiled faintly and said, “I’m a person of the Sea King’s palace. My name is Lola, please come with me.”

Zhao Hai quickly said, “This one has seen officer Lola. If I may ask, what clan does officer Lola belong? Are you a Human?”

Lola smiled faintly and said, “There’s no need for mister to be too polite. I am not a Human, I’m a mermaid. We mermaids can change between tail and legs all year round. So it isn’t strange to see us walking like this.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “So that’s how it is. I didn’t think that the Royal Tribe of the Fishmen were actually the Mermaids. This is the first time that I’ve heard of this.”

Lola curiously looked at Zhao Hai, “This is the first time? How is that possible? In the past, there were several occasions where the Fishmen and Humans came in contact. The nearest one should be about several thousand years ago. Did the Humans not have this in their records?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he turned to look at Laura and the others and said, “Did you know about this?”

Laura and the others shook their heads. Then Laura replied, “I didn’t. I’ve read all of the history books that we have collected. And in the past ten thousand years, there has been no contact between the Fishmen and the Humans.”

Lola looked at Zhao Hai and then shook her head, “There’s nothing strange about that. Our initial relationship with the Humans was very good. But later on, the Radiant Church had started to pressure us, causing our contact with the humans to be cut off. Later on we heard that the people of the Radiant Church had taken charge in making the history books of the humans. So it was natural that they wouldn’t include us in.”

Zhao Hai stared, he wasn’t aware of any of these matters. No wonder there wasn’t even a word about the Fishmen in the ten thousand year history of the Humans. Moreover, these history books were unfairly aggressive towards the Beastmen. In the history books, the Beastmen were described as wild and aggressive while the Dwarves were violent and irritating. The Elves had it better, since they were written to have unparalleled beauty. But this was not a good thing. This made the humans covet the Elves. For a period of time, there were humans who were capturing Elves and made them into slaves. In the end, the Elves retreated from the Human lands and went to the Elven Forest, completely cutting their contact with the outside world.

After putting all of this together, Zhao Hai was able to understand what was going on. This must be one of the plans of the Radiant Church. They wanted the Fishmen to be forgotten, and the Beastmen and Dwarves to be hated. But since the Elves were too perfect, the Radiant Church were unable to find dirt on them. The Church can only use one method, and it was to make the Elves cut their ties with the Humans. In the end, their plan succeeded, making it very difficult for the races to come in contact with the humans.

At this time, Lola had already brought Zhao Hai and the others to the Great Hall. This Great Hall was very spacious. From what Zhao Hai can see, the Great Hall must have been about 20 meters high. The ceiling of the hall was made out of crystal, making it possible to see the outside directly. These crystals were also adjusted in order to be a beautiful piece of art.

The stone pillars of the Great Hall were also inlaid with pearls and crystals. There were mermaids standing on each pillar, but each of them had already turned into their Human form.

In the innermost part of the Great Hall was a special throne. It looked like a normal throne but with half of it underwater. A mermaid was sitting on this throne. She wore green robes along with a crystal crown on her head as well as a crystal scepter on her hand. However, she didn’t change into her human form, her lower body was tail of a fish.

Lola led ZHao Hai and the others to the beautiful mermaid up to about ten paces away. Then Lola bowed to the Mermaid and said, “Your Majesty, Mister Zhao Hai and his wives has arrived.”

The woman waved his hand, then Lola bowed again before going back. Then Zhao Hai and the others went forward and bowed, “Zhao Hai has see Her Majesty the Mermaid Queen.”

The Queen nodded, then he looked curiously at Zhao Hai, “Mister Zhao Hai, Miss Laura, Miss Megan, Miss Meg, Miss Lizzy, Miss Ni’er. I welcome you in behalf of all the Fishmen. May I know the reason why you’ve been anxious to see me?”

Zhao Hai and the others stared, they didn’t think that the Queen would get their names accurately.

Zhao Hai looked confused at the Queen but he still answered, “It’s an honor for Her Majesty to know our names. I came this time to tell Your Majesty of an important matter.”

The Queen smiled faintly and said, “Mister can tell me.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Queen and suddenly said, “Before I say it, I want to ask Your Majesty something. What is your view of the Radiant Church?”

The Queen gawked, she was confused at Zhao Hai’s question. Then she asked Zhao Hai, “What is the purpose of mister’s question? Is mister’s trip because of the Radiant Church? I heard that mister is enemies with the Radiant Church.”

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at the Queen and said, “Does Your Majesty know about this?”

The Queen smiled faintly and said, “Of course. Although there weren’t much contact between the Fishmen and the Humans, that doesn’t mean that we don’t hear any news at all. Especially my mermaid race.”

When Zhao Hai heard the Queen, he couldn’t help but get surprised, but he still answered, “Then it’s good that Your Majesty knows about the matters of the continent. I just want to know about how Your Majesty views the Radiant Church.”

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai and said, “The Radiant Church is an evil organization. They probably wanted to rule the entire world and enslave all the races, including us Fishmen.”

When he heard the Queen, Zhao Hai’s confidence went up. He looked at the Queen and said, “I don’t know if the Queen knew about the war tens of thousands of years ago. Where all of the major races of the Continent united. The matter about the war against the Divine Race?”

The Queen stared, then she thought for a moment before she said, “I do remember it. Our clan has it on our records. At that time, our Fishman Race also entered that war. But since most of the fighting happened on land, we weren’t much of a help. But there were still a lot of our Mermaid tribe’s elders that had died in that war.”

Zhao Hai was now fully assured, “I’ll tell Your Majesty about all I know. I suspect that the Radiant Church is a chess piece that the Divine Race had placed here in the Ark Continent. They were here in order to prepare for the Divine Race’s invasion.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Queen’s facial expression couldn’t help but change, “Mister, tell me all the details.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and then narrated how he helped the Dwarves to restore their artifact spirit. Then on about the time he went to the Northern Icefield in order to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear. He also expressed his numerous speculations.”

While the Queen listened to Zhao Hai, her face constantly changed. After Zhao Hai finished, the Queen sighed and said, “So that’s how it is. No wonder mister can become the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince. Also it seems like there’s nobody in the continent that knew about you becoming the Foreign Elder of the Dwarves. So Mister has been preparing for this matter. It seems like the people of the continent had heavily underestimated mister’s capabilities.”

Zhao Hai looked strangely at the Queen. From her words, it seems like she was updated on the matters of the continent. This made Zhao Hai confused, how could the Fishmen had such deep understanding about the continent?

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai and then smiled faintly, “Mister doesn’t need to get confused about why our Mermaid clan is aware of the matters of the continent. Does mister know about the Sea God’s Merchant Union?”

Upon hearing Sea God’s Merchant Union, the faces of Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but change. It was not because they didn’t hear about it, but it was because they were too familiar with the name.

Among the big Merchant unions of the continent, the Sea God’s Merchant Union was the most mysterious. The main business of this Merchant Union were their clothing and jewelry.

The Queen wouldn’t mention the Sea God’s Merchant Union for no reason at all. Just her mentioning this name meant that the merchant union is under the Mermaid Clan’s control! This was too shocking, people had always believed that the Fishmen were always in the sea. Because of this, nobody would suspect that they would openly make their own merchant union. And it was actually one of the most famous merchant unions in the continent.

Zhao Hai and Laura looked at each other and can see the shock in each other’s eyes. The Mermaids were too formidable. They can actually hide this for a long time, it was too amazing.

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and smiled, “Mister shouldn’t be too surprised. After all, we, the Fishmen, still needed Human products to live. But we cannot openly trade with the Humans. After all, most of the Fishman races didn’t have good impressions towards your race.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I understand. Since Your Majesty knows, what would your race do now? Will you help us in dealing with the Radiant Church and the Divine Race?”

The Queen thought for a moment before she nodded, “Naturally. The Radiant Church was the main culprit who drove us away from the continent. And they also wanted to enslave everyone. So why wouldn’t we agree? We shall help you to deal with the Radiant Church and the Divine Race.”

When he heard the Queen, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be glad, “I thank Your Majesty.”

The Queen smiled faintly and said, “Mister shouldn’t be too polite. Compared to what mister had done, my word is nothing. But mister, we’re in quite of a trouble right now. I’m afraid we won’t be able to provide help in the meantime.”

“I knew it!” Zhao Hai said inside. But he smiled and said, “If Your Majesty trusts this Zhao Hai. Then I could provide you with a helping hand.”

The Queen stared, then she shook her head and said, “No need. The Buda Clan might be strong on land, but this is the sea. I’m afraid Mister can’t provide much of a help.”

Chapter 613: Secret

When Zhao Hai heard the Queen, he couldn’t help but show a smile as he said, “Your Majesty, since you know about my Buda Clan, they you should also know about my ability. I might not have good cultivation, but my Dark Magic, especially undead magic, is unparalleled. If I say I’m second, nobody would dare claim that they are first.”

The Queen stared at Zhao Hai, then after thinking for a moment, she said, “So mister wants to help us using your Undead?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It depends on what troubles you have encountered.”

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai, and the after some time, she let out a long sigh and said, “Patriarch Zhao Hai’s undead summoning is indeed very famous in the continent. This Queen wouldn’t hide anything from mister, this time, we had really met some trouble. Someone wanted to challenge the throne.”

This answer was within Zhao Hai’s expectations. The Mermaid Race was the ruling clan of the Fishmen. If there wasn’t a revolt, they wouldn’t have established ties with the Rock Shrimp tribe. After all, the Rock Shrimp tribe was just too unqualified.

Zhao Hai looked at the Queen and said, “Since Your Majesty wanted to form an alliance with us, they we are now allies. If an ally is in trouble, then it would be impossible for me to just stand by. I ask Your Majesty to tell us the problem, this Zhao Hai would do his best to help.”

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai and somehow felt that he can be trusted. So she gave a sigh and said, “I’m afraid mister would laugh at us. Although we rule the sea, the waters are just too big. Our Mermaid Clan simply cannot manage every single place. Moreover, since our management is quite loose, many people held us in high regard. But we had recently discovered that some Fishmen tribes were having trouble. It was clear that something must have happened. So we sent some people to investigate and found out that a strong subordinate of ours, the Sea Dragon tribe, has been collecting massive amounts of tax under our name. However, these taxes weren’t handed over to us, but instead, they hoarded it for themselves and used it to pull other tribes over to their side. At the time of us finding out, those tribes had already established an alliance and had blatantly announced their revolt. Now, we had lost control of the east side of the seas. Moreover, the Sea Dragon Tribe has also amassed an army and are now inching towards us. Because our Mermaid Race has not fought for some time, our response had been slow. Now, we have our backs behind the wall.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then I would have to disturb Your Majesty for a few days. In those few days, I will use the time to manufacture a batch of high level undead marine beasts and make them into an army. When the time comes, I believe they would be able to help Your Majesty. What do you think?”

The Queen gawked at what Zhao Hai said, then her face expressed her glee as she said, “Then I would trouble mister Zhao Hai. Lola, arrange a room for mister Zhao Hai to rest in.”

Lola stepped forward and gave the Queen a bow, then she turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, come with me.” Zhao Hai then gave the Queen a bow before leaving with Lola.

When Zhao Hai left the Great Hall, a Mermaid entered the Great Hall from a small entrance at the side. The Mermaid then told the Queen, “Your Majesty, from what we’ve heard from mister Zhao Hai, it seems like the attack of the Sea Dragons are also related to the Divine Race.”

The Queen nodded and said, “In our clan’s records, the Dragon Race were the most faithful dogs of the Divine Race. The Sea Dragons are a branch family of the Dragons. Their sudden move this time might have some reason. Luo Luo, you go look at the records and see what the Sea Dragons did during the previous war against the Divine Race. I’m afraid I can’t remember if there are any records of it in the clan.”

The Mermaid Luo Luo complied, then she looked at the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, do you think mister Zhao Hai’s plan is feasible? Can the undead really deal with those Sea Dragons?”

The Queen smiled faintly and said, “The Buda Clan’s Patriarch is very mysterious. There are numerous people in the continent that went to investigate him only to find out nothing. But some people suspect that he has some sort of Space Divergent Ability. Moreover, all of his undead are very high levelled, their individual fighting strength is not weak. If we have his help, then we may reduce our casualties. You transmit my orders to get the Whales to catch a lot magic beasts and bring them over. We don’t know how many undead mister Zhao Hai might make. But I’m sure that when the war comes, those Sea Dragons would surely be in on a surprise.”

Luo Luo nodded, then she turned around to leave. Inside the Great Hall, the Queen gave a sigh before she muttered, “The Divine Race is finally returning? Hehe, that’s good. I’ve also waited to take revenge. Clowns of the Sea Dragon Race, do you really think that you can dethrone us? Keep dreaming.”

Zhao Hai and the others were lead by Lola to a side hall. This hall wasn’t very big, but it still had the beautiful aesthetics of the palace. The hall was divided into four regions. Upon entering, one would first enter the lobby, it was a living room that was floored with blue stone. Moreover, the stones underwent careful polishing, one could see reflections when one walks on them.

The second room was the dining room, inside were stone furniture This room had wooden tables and chairs in them. These tables and chairs were all made out of the finest wood. They didn’t use a single coating of paint, revealing the natural wood grains. It looked very simple and natural.

The third were the bed spaces, inside were a total of four rooms and a living room. The fourth part of the hall was the bathroom. The floor of the bathroom was made out out blue shells. In the middle of the bathroom was a large pool. There were several fish head sculptures on the edges of the pool with water spraying out of it. There was also a water outlet under the pool in order to stabilize its height. The water was crystal clear and wasn’t cold at all. Instead it felt warm and was very nice to take a bath in.

Lola asked Zhao Hai and the others to the living room and briefed them about the palace before she took her leave. She also told Zhao Hai that if he needs something, he can just pull on the rope inside the bedroom. The rope was linked to a metal bell, when the rope is pulled, the bell would then issue a ring which would alert nearby people.

After Lola left, Zhao Hai and the others went to the small living area in their bedroom. Then, Zhao Hai opened his monitor. Cai’er already recorded the conversation between Luo Luo and the Queen.

After Zhao Hai and the others listened to the video, the group became silent. After some time, Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, looking at the Queen’s expression, is she confident?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then after sighing he said, “She certainly is. The mermaids have been ruling the fishmen for a long time. So how could they possibly not have their trump cards. If they didn’t have any methods, then they would’ve already fallen to a revolt long time ago. And seeing from the Queen’s expression, it seems like she is reluctant to use their trump card. Otherwise, she wouldn’t need out help.”

Laura nodded, then Lizzy frowned and said, “Do we really need to help the Queen? They have ways to deal with these people. Aren’t we being used like tools this time?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That doesn’t matter. In any case, if we help them deal with the Sea Dragons, our relationship would get much closer. This is good for our future plans. I just didn’t think that the Dragons would be on the side of the Divine Realm. It seems like the Radiant Church was the Divine Race’s chess piece in the light while the Dragons are their piece in the shadows.”

Megan looked like she had a heavy heart, “Big Brother Hai, Dragons haven’t appeared on the continent for many years. It seems like they have been living in the Accra mountains. If the Dragons were indeed on the side of the Divine Race, then its likely that they have been controlling the magic beasts of the mountain. No wonder the Accra mountains had become one of the Five Forbidden Areas. The Dragons controlling the magic beasts for the Divine Race must be kept secret from the others. So they naturally would kill people who ventured deep into the Accra Mountain.”

The smile on Zhao Hai’s face disappeared, then he nodded and said, “That’s very possible. If there is really a Divine Race’s force in the Accra Mountains, then the Demonic Abyss would definitely be a den for the Demons. People already had some suspicions that the Demonic Abyss is related to the Demon Race, but nobody had any proof of it. I think the Demons used this deliberately in order to focus everyone’s attention to the Demonic Abyss while the Engraved Ark continues to accumulate power. The methods of the Demons and the Divine Race were actually similar, but are reversed.

Laura became serious as she said, “It seems like the Demons and the Divine Realm still hasn’t lost heart for the Ark Continent. Brother Hai, we’re quite lucky that we haven’t gone to the Accra Mountains yet and found out about the relationship between the Dragons and the Divine Race. If we went there and found out, then the Divine Race would surely be alerted that their secret was revealed. It might spur them into action.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Fortunately, we went to the Fishman Race first. Otherwise, we would’ve gone to Accra Mountains since the Elves were still unprepared. I’m planning on getting some magic beasts and plants to upgrade the Space. I’ve also been thinking of subduing the Dragons, after all, their fighting strength were incredibly known to the continent.”

Megan knit her brows as she said, “It’s really strange that nobody knew about the relationship between the Dragons and the Divine Race. It seems like this was also because of the Radiant Church’s machinations.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “It seems so. The Radiant Church had probably obtained the Divine Race’s decree earlier than we have imagined. “The Divine race is good, they were actually very patient.”

Chapter 614: Arrogant? I Have Strength!

Although they were in a hostile relationship, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but admire the Divine Race. For them to hide everything for such a long time was a testament to how patient they were.

However, this also made Zhao Hai pay much more attention to them. The Divine Race can completely turn the entire Ark Continent over along with the Radiant Church. Such a race was notable, and Zhao Hai couldn’t help but refrain from being careless.

Laura coldly snorted and said, “Brother Hai, then what do we do? When we extinguish the Sea Dragons, then would we be looking for trouble with the Dragons in Accra Mountains?” She was afraid that the continent would find out that Zhao Hai had the guts to offend the Dragons. In the continent, Dragons were the symbols of invincibility. Nobody dared to go and purposefully offend them.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Don’t worry. First, we deal with the Sea Dragons, and then we go to Flame Island and see what’s going on there. Maybe we can get some benefits along the way. After that, we’ll go deal with the dragons. But since there are quite strong, we need to get ready. Right Laura, you and the others are now 9th rank experts. But you don’t have your own mounts. Maybe we can get you some dragons to ride in Accra Mountains.”

Laura snorted, “I don’t want them. What do those stupid dragons do that a 9th rank Blood Hawk can’t? I’d rather use the Blood Hawks as a mount.”

Zhao Hai and the others laughed. If other people in the continent were to hear Laura, hey would certainly laugh. She actually denied the chance to have a dragon as a mount. That’s an absurd idea.

After some time, the group gradually calmed down. Then Megan turned her head towards Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, will you start making undead tomorrow? Your undeads are now 9th rank, what form do you want them to look like?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “This is truly tricky to deal with. We can just let those undead retain their forms when they fight, but we’ll have them deliberately get injured or play dead. Naturally, those are just make believe. Once they reach a certain amount of damage, we can receive them into the Space. We can use this method as a cover up. Also, the Queen was also aware of the strength of my undead, so she wouldn’t suspect too much upon seeing them fight.”

Lizzy nodded and said, “From what I can hear from the Queen, she seems to be sincere in her move to ally with us. In this case, it would be more advantageous for her if Brother Hai is stronger than she expected. I think she wouldn’t just betray you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “in fact, there’s really no need to be careful about the Fishmen. Although they had the Sea God’s Merchant Union and can contact with the continent, they have always been mysterious and can only be rarely be spotted. Their contact with the other powers can only be said to be miniscule. So I believe that they won’t say anything. The other Fishman tribes are also less likely to talk, after all, they don’t get in contact with the humans. Because of that I believe that what we do here won’t be revealed to the Humans back in the continent.”

Lizzy shook her head and said, “But we still need to be careful. Even if the Fishmen wouldn’t talk, what about the Sea Dragons? They might use the other Dragons to expose us.”

Laura also nodded and said, “Brother Hai, we do need to be much more careful.” Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t say anything more. Laura and the others didn’t say anything as well as they went back to the Space and started to prepare.

Although the Queen didn’t invite Zhao Hai over for a meal, she still had people send him a beautiful array of dishes. The variety seafoods present were more than what Zhao Hai had eaten before. This made Zhao Hai and the others satisfied with their meal.

The next morning, after Zhao Hai and the others ate the Breakfast that Lola had given them, Lola gave them word that the Queen was inviting them over. Then Zhao Hai and the others went with Lola to the Great Hall in order to meet with the Queen.

The Queen was sat in the same position as when Zhao Hai had met her yesterday. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, the Queen couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “Mister, come and take a seat.” Zhao Hai then noticed that there were several chairs in the Great Hall today. It seems like these were specially prepared for them.

After Zhao Hai and the others expressed their gratitude and sat on the chairs, the Queen said, “How many undead can mister summon? How many beasts do we need to acquire?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “As many beasts as you can find, the more the better. Right, Your Majesty, how many people had followed the Sea Dragons’ rebellion? How much people do they have?”

The Queen forced a smile and said, “There are a lot of tribes that decided to join the Sea Dragons, I don’t know how many they are. But there were a lot of small races that were absorbed into their army. I’m afraid that the current army of the Sea Dragons numbers at about more than ten million.”

Although he knew that the seas was big and there were a lot of beings in here, Zhao Hai still couldn’t help but breath some cold air upon hearing the number of the opposite party. Now he understood why the Sea Dragons decided to act against the Mermaids. If the Mermaids were dealt with, the Sea Dragons would have full hegemony of the seas. When the time comes, they can amass their army and coordinate with the Radiant Church. At that time, it wouldn’t be impossible to conquer the entire continent.

Moreover, the Fishmen also had an advantage. Although they can’t stay on land for too long, one shouldn’t forget that they can just retreat to the seas whenever they get defeated. The sea is their domain and no army of the continent was able to contend with them there. That would be equivalent to the Fishmen having bases right beside Human territories.

If this was really the case, then the Divine Race can definitely depend on them and fight a battle of attrition with the major races in the continent. At that time, even if they don’t send a God-ranked expert and just sent down an army of 9th ranks, they can still defeat the races of the continent. After all, the population of the continent was greatly fewer than the people of the sea. Moreover, they still had the Dragons in Accra Mountains as well as the Radiant Church.

Thinking about this made Zhao Hai coldly sweat. If he didn’t come to see the Fishmen at this time, then he would really be in trouble. It was good that he came just in time to deal with the Sea Dragons, solving the issue with the Fishmen.

The Queen saw that Zhao Hai’s face turned ugly and didn’t speak for quite a while. She thought that he was frightened by the army so she quickly said, “Mister doesn’t need to worry about our ability to resist them. We were just caught off guard this time, so we couldn’t respond appropriately. Mister can just summon as many as you can, that’s already enough of of a help.”

When Zhao Hai heard that the Queen seemed to misunderstand him, he immediately smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty misunderstands, I can summon as much undead as the number of copses that you can provide. I can only ask Your Majesty to grab as much corpses as possible, it would be great to get corpses from the enemies.”

The Queen nodded, “Alright, the mister doesn’t need to worry about the magic beasts. I already had my people prepare them. I just want to know how much mister can take.”

Zhao Hai knew what the Queen meant. After all, her clan had a lot of contact with the Humans, so it was natural that she was aware about Dark Mages. She knew that Dark Mages have their limit. If the Fishmen were to provide more than what Zhao Hai can summon, then he would be losing face.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your majesty doesn’t need to worry. Make them get as many as possible, the more the better. If Your Majesty can prepare 10 million magic ebasts, then Your Majesty would acquire a 10 million undead army. This one will have to excuse myself to rest. Once the corpses are ready, Your Majesty can just send some people over to get me.” Then he gave a bow before he left along with Laura and the others.

When Zhao Hai left, Luo Luo arrived at the Great Hall, completely fuming, “Your Majesty, this Zhao Hai is extremely arrogant. Your Majesty is only thinking about his well being, but instead he was being impolite.”

The Queen smiled faintly and then shook her head, “Silly thing, he’s not being extremely arrogant. He is just very strong. You might not know but he has a very terrifying reputation among the Humans. In just one night, he had turned an entire several hundred thousand Aksu Empire navy into his undead. If he can really turn 10 million corpses into undead, then that would be good for us. Go give the orders to get as much magic beasts as possible. As long as they are wild, then get them. Right, go bring corpses of Sea Dragons and their allies as well. I want to see what an undead Sea Dragon looks like.” While she spoke this, a killing aura appeared around the Queen.

The Mermaid Queen was very angry. The Mermaid Race had ruled the seas for many years, but they hadn’t encountered a rebellion of this scale. The Sea Dragons actually made the Mermaids lose control of the eastern seas. For the Mermaid Race, this was not a small attack.

The fighting strength of the eastern sea was much stronger than the west. This was because in the eastern waters, aside from the Sea Dragons, there were also the Sharks, Electric Eels, and various poisonous races. These collection of people were very strong. It was because of this that when the Sea Dragon announced their rebellion, the Mermaid Race was caught off guard.

However, the Mermaids weren’t people who could be trifled with as well. Not only do they have the loyal Whale tribe and Swordfish tribe, their own fighting strength was formidable as well. The Queen believed that as long as they have time, they would be able to amass an army that can extinguish the Sea Dragons in one swoop.

Luo Luo looked at the Queen and didn’t talk about Zhao Hai anymore. She then looked at the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, I also checked the records about the Sea Dragons yesterday and found out that the Sea Dragons didn’t exist during the fight with the Divine Race.”

When the Queen heard Luo Luo, she couldn’t help but reply, “There are no Sea Dragons? What does that mean?”

Luo Luo replied, “Your Majesty, during the major war against the Divine Race where our Mermaid Race had participated, the Dragons were there as well, but they were on the side of the Divine Race. When the God was defeated, the Dragons didn’t have anywhere else to go but retreat to the Accra Mountains. However, part of them decided to ran to the sea and requested refuge from us. The Sea King pitied them and allowed them to thrive here. Afterwards, those Dragons married some Fishmen and eventually spawned the Sea Dragon Race.”

Chapter 615: Curious Fishman Race

When the Queen heard Luo Luo, her expression couldn’t help but change, “So you’re saying that only after the war did the Sea Dragons came to existence? Did the Divine Race intended that in order to deal with us?”

Luo Luo shook her head and said, “You really can’t say that, after all, that was a long time ago. My speculations is that the Divine Race only got contact with the Sea Dragons recently, which prompted them to deal with us. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have waited for tens of thousands of years in order to revolt.”

The Queen nodded, “It would be impossible for the Sea Dragons to hold off on attacking us. However, we can still affirm that the Sea Dragons are a bunch of ungrateful bastards!”

Luo Luo also held anger in her expression. When she checked the records, she couldn’t help but get irritated the more she read on. These Sea Dragons were too shameless. The Mermaids had given them shelter but they still ended up rebelling.

Then the Queen coldly snorted and said, “Sea Dragon race, you just wait. Luo Luo, make sure that everything mister Zhao Hai needs gets fulfilled. Maybe he can change the flow of this war.”

Luo Luo nodded before turning around to leave. The Queen coldly snorted and then mumbled, “Sea Dragon Race, good, good. You actually think that you can rule the entire Ark Continent?”

When Zhao Hai and the others returned to their room, Laura looked at Zhao Hai in confusion and said, “Brother Hai, what just happened? Why did you suddenly became arrogant?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “In any business, expressing your power is the one of the most important things. Don’t forget that we had formed an alliance with the Mermaid clan. And since we are now allies, we need to see ourselves as equals. If we show our weakness, then they would lose confidence in us.” Then Zhao Hai opened the monitor and played the video of Luo Luo and the Queen’s meeting.

After listening to the Queen and Luo Luo, the face of Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but turn ugly. They didn’t think that the Sea Dragons would actually have such a history with the Fishmen. If they were indeed a chess piece of the Divine Race, then the Divine Race was too terrifying.

Laura looked at the monitor before turning to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, do you think that the Sea Dragons were intentionally placed there by the Divine Race?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t think so. If they were, then they wouldn’t have waited for so long. Then when the Radiant Church was its most formidable, they would’ve already cooperated and conquered the entire continent.”

Laura and the others nodded, then Zhao Hai sighed and said, “But no matter what, we must deal with the Sea Dragons. When the time comes, we can just interrogate the Sea Dragons, then we can uncover the truth.”

Laura and the others nodded again. Then Zhao Hai change the scene of the monitor, showing the preparations of the Fishmen.

At this time, the places nearby the small island had become very busy. People of the Whale tribe and the Swordfish tribe have been sent out to grab all of the wild magic beasts on the surrounding waters. Moreover, the Queen had also sent another command making all of the other Fishmen to go full scale in their capture of beasts and had all of them sent to the island.

Zhao Hai was very calm when he saw the strength of the Fishmen. In just one day, they had actually managed to have 100 thousand beasts sent to the island.

For them to only take one day to collect 100 thousand beasts and had them sent to the island was terrifying. There were already a lot of magic beasts that were captured. However, Zhao Hai didn’t appear, the Queen didn’t send word to him either.

The next morning, after having their breakfast, Lola arrived and invited Zhao Hao over to the Great Hall. Besides the Queen, Luo Luo was present as well. But Luo Luo looked just like an ordinary servant right now, with her head lowered in obedience. Besides Luo Luo, there were also a Turtle Fishman and Whale Fishman present.

Zhao Hai felt strange, how could this Whale Fishman able to appear in the Great Hall. With their bodies, it was impossible for them to go up using the stone pillars. They may have other ways to come in. Zhao Hao decided to ask Cai’er about this later.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai arrive, the Queen nodded and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, come. Let me introduce you to the captain of the island guards, the Whale Fishman Dashan and the guard commander, the Turtle Fishman Jintai.”

Zhao Hai looked at these two and identified them. The Whale was the one who escorted him to the island while the Turtle was the one who brought them up to the palace.

Zhao Hai bowed to the two and then said, “Nice to meet you. This Zhao Hai thanks the two of you for delivering me here.”

They also returned Zhao Hai’s courtesy, but didn’t dare to utter a word. Then they returned to stand by the Queen’s side. The Queen then turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, we’ve already collected 100 thousand magic beasts. Please have a look at them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll be heading there now. Your Majesty, please allow this one to excuse himself first.”

The Queen nodded as she waved her hand and said, “Then I’ll have to trouble mister. Dashan, Jintai, make sure to take care of mister Zhao Hai’s every single need.” Then the two issued their agreement before giving the Queen a bow and then leaving the Hall along with Zhao Hai.

When they got out, the turtles were already prepared for them. Zhao Hai and the others then stepped on top of the turtles before they jumped down from the pool and then disappeared.

Zhao Hai didn’t have time to pay attention to anything right now. When the turtles entered the mounds, Zhao Hai felt that he was riding on a roller coaster. And the speed was much much more than back on Earth.

This was the first time that Laura and the others had experience this, so they couldn’t help but scream. But since they were already 9th rank experts, it only took them a while before they calmed down.

Back when they were heading up, Zhao Hai reckoned that they had taken about an hour. But now that they were going down, it only took them a few minutes to do so. In a blink of an eye, they were already on the sea’s surface.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at Laura and the others. He wanted to see if they were frightened. But when he saw their expressions, Zhao Hai felt relief. Although Laura and the others had been scared, their current expressions revealed their enjoyment.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. He actually felt that women were strange beings, they were too full of contradictions. They liked delicious food, but they were also afraid to get fat. They think that roller coasters were scary, but only to end up enjoying the ride.

Zhao Hai shook his head as he forced a smile before he turned to Jintai and said, “Commander Jintai, please take me to see those magic beasts.”

Jintai turned his head and smiled faintly, “I’ll have to be unfair to mister Zhao Hai. I cannot stay in this place for too long because of my duties. However, Dashan will come here and lead you to the place.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at Jintai and said, “Thank you commander. But Commander Jintai, how would be be able to enter and exit this place?”

Jintai smiled and said, “Mister doesn’t need to worry. The Queen herself sent word that Mister and your wives are free to move in the Mermaid territory. Nobody will restrict your freedom.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright. Then I’ll have to thank Her Majesty. My wives are very curious about this place. Even I am compelled to look around.”

Jintai smiled, “Then Mister is very welcome here. The Mermaid domain is very beautiful. Moreover, the Royal tribe is very hospitable. I believe that they would quickly become friends with your wives.” Then after he said this, a huge bulge suddenly appeared on the sea’s surface. Then Dashan’s mountainous figure suddenly appeared.

After Dashan appeared, he immediately gave Zhao Hai a bow and said, “Mister, please come with me. I’ll go lead you to see the magic beasts.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he rode on Dashan’s whale mount. When Laura and the others were about to board, Zhao Hai smiled to them and said, “You go play in the meantime. I won’t be long.”

When they heard Zhao Hai, the women couldn’t help but stare before their eyes suddenly lit up. “Can we really play? Good, Fantastic!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then turned to Jintai and said, “Commander Jintai I will have to trouble you, I will certainly come back soon.”

Jintai smiled faintly and said, “Mister can rest assured” Then Zhao Hai gave Jintai a bow before he turned to Dashan and said, “Captain Dashan, let’s go.” Dashan nodded, then he commanded his mount to move towards an island.

Soon after Zhao Hai left the Mermaid island, he had arrived at a nearby island where a large number of Fishmen were present. These Fishmen had brought a lot of magic beasts. These beasts were all alive, some of them were wild while some were struggling.

When Zhao Hai saw this scene, he couldn’t help but stare. He turned his head to Dashan and said, “Captain Dashan, dead beasts are fine. Even if they are alive, they would still end up dead in my hands. I need them to be dead before I can turn them to undead.”

When Dashan heard Zhao Hai, he nodded and then said, “Alright, mister, please wait a bit.” Then Dashan turned his head to the Fishmen and said, “Kill those magic beasts, and then you can leave.”

The Fishmen gawked, but they still obeyed. They pulled out all kinds of weapons and killed all of the magic beasts that they’ve brought.[1]

However, after killing these magic beasts, the Fishmen didn’t leave. Every one of them looked curiously at Zhao Hai. Seeing their appearances, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. Then he changed his thinking and understood what was going on. These Fishmen might be aware of what he was about to do. They haven’t seen a Dark Mage make undead before, therefore, they were curious to see what it looked like.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. He looked at the 100 thousand magic beasts piled in front of him. Moreover, since some of these magic beasts were quite big, the pile looked just like a hill. Zhao Hai pulled out his Blood Ghost Staff before he muttered some fake incantations. Then he waved his staff as a black gas appeared and surrounded the pile of Magic Beasts. The Fishmen looked at the mass of black gas as it enveloped the pile of beasts.

Before long, the black gas had vanished. But what the Fishmen saw after was something that made them scream out in alarm!

* * *

PETA would like to have a word.

Chapter 616: Dangerous Character

The pile of dead magic beasts had now turned into a pile of bones. There was no blood nor flesh found, only bones were present.

This gave a very strong impact to those who were present. The Fishmen couldn’t help but feel a chill. And at this time, more shocking things happened, the pile of bones had started moving!

Under the gazes of the Fishmen, each bone of that pile started to move. The bones then started rolling into the sea before slowly forming up and lining themselves. The big ones were at the bottom while the small beasts were at the top.

Before long, a hundred thousand magic beasts had arrange themselves in a cube formation, filling the space of the surrounding sea. The Fishmen couldn’t help but retreat as their expression changed. They wanted to be as far from these undead as possible.

Seeing the Fishmen retreat, Zhao Hai moved slightly and with an intention, the Undead beasts suddenly vanished. The only ones left behind were two turtle type beasts.

Zhao Hai jumped on top of the undead turtle and then bowed to Dashan, “I thank captain Dashan. I shall be leaving first, I want to take a look at what my wives are doing. The captain doesn’t need to accompany me any longer.” The the turtle under Zhao Hai moved its four limbs as it slowly swam towards Mermaid island. But at this time, Dashan still hasn’t recovered.

Only when Zhao Hai was close to Mermaid Island did Dashan recover. His face couldn’t help but change as he turned his head to look at Zhao Hai. His eyes were full of dread, in his mind, Zhao Hai had become a very dangerous person. This fellow can actually carry hundreds of undead beasts with him. Such a person being in Mermaid Island was a very unsafe factor.

After thinking about this, Dashan immediately urged his mount as he followed along Zhao Hai towards Mermaid Island. While Zhao Hai was looking for his wives, Dashan went to look for Jintai. He thinks that monitoring Zhao Hai’s every move was imperative to their own safety.

Zhao Hai was not aware of what Dashan was thinking. He just stood on top of his undead turtle as he looked around Mermaid Island. Mermaid Island was very large and was surrounded by numerous reefs. Some Mermaids playing on the reefs could also be seen from time to time.

While Zhao Hai was intrigued, the Mermaids were curious about Zhao Hai as well. Sensing their gazes, Zhao Hai did his best to not meet their sight. He didn’t know the customs here, so he might get into trouble if he did look them in the eye.

But what made Zhao Hai feel strange was the fact that he hasn’t seen an old Mermaid. All he had seen looked like young beautiful women. Even inside the palace, Zhao Hai couldn’t spot an old Mermaid while using the monitor.

Before long, Zhao Hai had finally found Laura and the others. They were currently sitting in a reef while chatting with some Mermaids. The group looked very jolly.

Meg had sharp eyes, so when she saw Zhao Hai, she immediately waved towards him. Zhao Hai directed the turtle to go forward before he looked at them and said, “You go and play some more. I’ll go and discuss some matters with Her Majesty. Right, I’ll also be leaving some turtles here to save Commander Jintai the trouble.” Then he withdrew some turtle type undead magic beasts. Then he nodded towards Laura and the others before heading back to the middle stone pillar.

When he reached the stone pillar, Zhao Hai had found that Dashan and Jintai were already there. When he went close, he discovered that their expression had changed.

Zhao Hao carefully looked into their eyes and found that there was a hint of fear on Dashan’s eyes. However, although there was still fear in Jintai’s eyes, there was also a hint of excitement mixed in as well.

Zhao Hai didn’t think too much about it. He came here to cooperate with the Mermaids and not to make enemies out of them. So as long as the Mermaids treat him as an ally, then Zhao Hai believed that they won’t attack him.

When Zhao Hai came forward, Jintai and Dashan immediately gave him a salute. Zhao Hai can feel that the greeting this time was more sincere than before..

Zhao Hai immediately returned the gesture before he turned to Jintai and said, “Commander, I’ve already given Laura and the others some turtles. You don’t need to send people to fetch them. Right, can I go see the Queen right now?”

Jintai nodded and said, “Come with me.” Then he used his mount as they swam against the stone pillar’s current. Zhao Hai gave Dashan a nod before following Jintai up.

When Dashan looked at Zhao Hai’s departing back, he couldn’t help but let out a long sigh. Ever since he saw Zhao Hai turn those magic beasts into undead, he had started to feel immense pressure when seeing Zhai Hai. But now that he had left, Dashan felt relief.

Dashan looked at the pillar and then said, “It seems like the Sea Dragons have terrifying bad luck.” Then he shook his head as he submerged into the water.

Zhao Hai, along with Jintai, had returned to the big pool. After reaching the shore, Zhao Hai immediately stored his undead magic beast into the Space. Then he gave Jintai a salute before heading towards the Great Hall.

But before Zhao Hai reached the Great Hall, Lola came to greet him. When Lola saw Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but gawk slightly. Then she immediately said, “Mister Zhao Hai, Her Majesty is already waiting for you inside.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Then Lola turned around and led Zhao Hai to walk towards the Great Hall. Upon arriving inside, Zhao Hai saw that Luo Luo was sitting right beside the Queen as if telling her something. The Queen was also listening as she nodded from time to time.

After Zhao Hai and Lola greeted the Queen, the Queen nodded and said, “I didn’t expect mister to come back so soon. Did mister’s summoning go smoothly?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Very smooth.  Your Majesty doesn’t need to worry about it. I can go to the battlefield anytime you want. You should know that a Dark Mage’s power is at its peak on the battlefield.”

The Queen nodded and said, “I ask mister to wait for two days. In two days, the Whales, Swordfishes, and Turtles would send an army towards the frontlines. Mister can then go along with them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then I’ll go with Your Majesty’s arrangement. If it’s possible, I’d like to ask Your Majesty to give me some information about the Sea Dragons and their army. Is that alright?”

The Queen nodded, “That’s not a problem. Mister can rest assured, those materials would get to you as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then bowed to the Queen, “Then this Zhao Hai would like to be excused. If there are more magic beasts, please send someone to inform me.”

The Queen nodded, “Alright, if Mister has something he wants, then don’t hesitate to send word.” Zhao Hai nodded, and then expressed his gratitude before bowing to the Queen and then leaving.

When Zhao Hai left, Luo Luo immediately turned to the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, this Zhao Hai is too dangerous. He just waved and turned a hundred thousand magic beasts into undead. Moreover, he can actually store them somewhere. Such a person living in this place is very dangerous.”

The Queen smiled faintly and said, “No need to be worried about Zhao Hai. He is our ally, the stronger he is, the more advantages we’ll have. Rest assured, no bad thing will happen.”

Luo Luo replied, “Now that I saw what Dark Mages are, I can understand why the continent deemed them to be emissaries of evil. They are really frightening. In a blink of an eye, the hundred thousand magic beasts had turned into bone. It was too scary. I really don’t know how he got his wives. He didn’t just snatch them right?”

The Queen looked at Luo Luo and smiled, “Luo Luo, don’t judge a person by their outside appearance. The Radiant Church was incomparably sacred in the surface, but was actually the worst people. And although Mister Zhao Hai uses Dark Magic, he actually has not injured an innocent person. Luo Luo, remember this, strength doesn’t describe good or evil, it’s the person himself that decides to be good or evil. Understood?”

Luo Luo nodded, “I understand. Your Majesty, with the addition of Mister Zhao Hai, I’ve become much more confident in our chances to win this war. Also, Your Majesty, what did mister Zhao Hai mean when he said that a Dark Mage is most powerful in the battlefield?”

The Queen smiled and said, “What does the battlefield have the most? It’s dead people. A Dark Mage can turn those corpses into undead. Moreover, those undead can also lead the opposing party to lose morale. Think about it, you have comrades who you’ve shared happiness and fear together, then when those comrades dies, they suddenly stand up and start attacking you. At that time, would you have the guts to turn your weapons against your friends? Or will you turn around and flee?”

Upon hearing the Queen, Luo Luo’s face couldn’t help but get pale. Although she has not gone to the battlefield, she had participated in magic beast hunting groups. If what the Queen said happened to her, then she would collapse immediately! The scene described by the Queen had Luo Luo shivering in fear.

The Queen looked at Luo Luo and felt that she had scared her too much. So she patted Luo Luo’s shoulder and said, “It’s because of this that the Dark Mages have become the most powerful Mages before the arrival of the Radiant Church. But there were also Dark Mages that loved to slaughter civilians in order to turn them into undead. Such Dark Mages are meant to be destroyed.

Luo Luo nodded, then the Queen looked at Luo Luo and continued, “You don’t have to doubt Mister Zhao Hai’s morals as well. The status of each of his wives aren’t low.. Since you haven’t gone to the continent, they you didn’t know that the story of Mister Zhao Hai and his wives has spread to all Human nations. Mister Zhao Hai is a person who many people envy.”

Luo Luo looked at the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, is Mister Zhao Hai really famous in the continent? But he is a Dark Mage, does nobody fear him?”

The Queen shook her head and said, “Mister Zhao Hai’s reputation on the continent can only be considered to be normal. But when commoners mention his name, they couldn’t help but call him vicious and merciless. He had turned hundreds of thousands of Aksu Empire troops into undead in a single night. Hearing that, wouldn’t you also think that he was vicious and merciless?”

Chapter 617: The Army Departs

When Luo Luo heard the Queen, her face couldn’t help but change, “Your Majesty, is that true? Did Mister Zhao Hai really turn hundreds of thousands of Aksu Empire soldiers into undead in one night? Then isn’t he a bad person? Why would the people on the continent only call him vicious and merciless?”

The Queen forced a smile and said, “People in the continent don’t differ to much with the Fishmen, they also respect strength. Mister Zhao Hai is strong, so nobody dared to offend him. Besides, mister Zhao Hai didn’t kill the Aksu Empire soldiers with no reason at all. The Aksu Empire had sent those soldiers to Mister Zhao Hai’s territory, claiming that they owned the land. Because of that, Mister Zhao Hai had no choice but be impolite.”

Luo Luo frowned and said, “Even so, mister Zhao Hai is too cold hearted. Why does he have to kill those hundreds of thousands of people?”

The Queen smiled bitterly and said, “If mister Zhao Hai didn’t kill them, then he wouldn’t have reached his current height. You should have heard mister Zhao Hai’s purpose in coming here. The entire Ark Continent’s future is at risk, he even went to the Northern Icefields personally in order to retrieve the Beastmen’s Beast God’s Spear. Such a person cannot be said to be cold hearted. He’s someone who would not forgive his enemies while also be the one who would shelter his allies. His ideals are that simple.”

When she heard the Queen, Luo Luo couldn’t help but nod. It was not only the others, their Mermaid clan respects strength as well. Protecting allies and suppressing enemies was a very simple ideology in this world. Even in the Fishmen this idea is found every day. It wasn’t anything strange.

The Queen gave a sigh and said, “In fact, the Sea Dragons were doing this as well. The Sharks and Electric Eels had become their close allies while they suppressed those who wouldn’t side with them. It was just unfortunate that we were too loose with our surveillance. We weren’t able to discover their ambitions in time.”

Luo Luo also sighed, because their business dealings with the continent was short, their commodities had become scarce. Because of this, the Mermaids had decided to establish the Sea God’s Merchant Union and bought what they need from the Humans. Because the Mermaids were too focused on this matter, they were unable to see the moves done by the Sea Dragons. By the time they had found out, it was already too late.”

Because the Mermaids had concentrated on business, the Sea Dragons had used the opportunity to revolt, catching the Mermaids off guard. But it was fortunate that they now had a strong ally that was Zhao Hai. The Sea Dragons wouldn’t be living greatly this time.

The Queen turned to Luo Luo and said, “Luo Luo, in two days, Mister Zhao Hai will go along with the others to head towards the frontlines. You should go with them as well. Although mister Zhao Hai is strong, he is still unfamiliar with the Fishman Race. You must help him with this aspect. It would be best if we defeat the Sea Dragons in one fell swoop. But even if we cannot, at the very least, push them into a defensive position. Understand?”

Luo Luo nodded and said, “I understand, Your Majesty.”

The Queen nodded and said, “What are mister Zhao Hai’s wives doing now? Are they doing fine? Remember to make ties with those women. Mister Zhao Hai’s strength is formidable, and he is a famous merchant as well. It would be good for us to have a good relationship with him. Moreover, his wives also held great influence in the continent, don’t offend them.”

Luo Luo smiled and said, “Your Majesty, feel relieved. Mister Zhao Hai’s wives have been doing very well. They are very friendly and have also been very good friends with our sisters.”

The Queen smiled and then said, “Then that’s good. This matter might be our Fishman Race’s opportunity. If we can cooperate with Mister Zhao Hai, then perhaps we can openly do business with the Humans later on. After all, the Radiant Church’s influence had waned in the continent. Alright, go prepare yourself, Luo Luo. You still have to follow mister Zhao Hai in two days.” Luo Luo nodded and then bowed before turning around to leave.

Zhao Hai was currently inside the Space, looking at the monitor. The monitor had shown the conversation between the Queen and Luo Luo. The Queen’s words made Zhao Hai very surprised. He didn’t expect the Queen to have this much faith in him. But this was a good thing for Zhao Hai. Dealing with the Sea Dragons wasn’t a difficult matter. In fact, those hundred thousand marine beast undead were already enough to do it. After all, these undead are very high leveled.

After Luo Luo retreated, Zhao Hai changed the monitor to another place. Then, Zhao Hai sat quietly inside. This time, his trip to the Fishmen had brought him great profits. For the Mermaid Clan to be willing to be his allies was a good thing for Zhao Hai. At the same time, Zhao Hai had found out his assessment in the continent, Vicious and Ruthless!

“Vicious and Ruthless! Hehe, it seems like I embody those two words now.” Zhao Hai muttered in the living room.

Nothing happened for the rest of the day. However, there were still people who kept bringing all kinds of Magic Beasts to mermaid island. But this time, they had brought dead ones, not alive.

However, Zhao Hai was not very anxious in turning these into undead, at the same time, the Mermaids didn’t look for him. On the next day, Zhao Hai went down to turn those magic beasts into undead. Although there were still some Fishmen in the surroundings, their expressions weren’t curiosity anymore, but it was fear.

After staying for two days, the Fishman Army had finally been gathered. Although the Sea Dragons had 10 million troops, Zhao Hai was still shocked to see the reinforcements that was gathered by the Mermaid Clan. This was an army of no less than 2 million people!

Seeing these numbers made Zhao Hai numb. He became speechless about the population of the Fishmen. They had just casually recruited 2 million people. While a rebel can come up with hundreds upon thousands of troops.

Zhao Hai was somewhat happy. Fortunately, the Fishmen wouldn’t be able to survive on land for too long. Otherwise, the entire Continent might have already been seized by them.

This time, the Queen personally delivered Zhao Hai outside Mermaid Island. This made the other Fishmen shocked, they didn’t expect the Queen to have this high respect for Zhao Hai.

In fact those people had misunderstood the Queen this time. In addition to sending Zhao Hai out, she also wanted to gave an address to the troops. The one who would lead the troops this time was Dashan.

Dashan was Mermaid Island’s Guard Captain. But since the situation of the frontlines had become urgent, and in addition to Dashan having prior contact with Zhao Hai, the Queen decided to just send Dashan along with this army in order to cooperate with Zhao Hai much smoother.

The vowing ceremony of the Fishmen was the same as the Humans. The Queen told a few encouraging words before assigning Dashan as the commander of the army. But at this time, Zhao Hai was now inside the body of a Blade Scale Whale.

This whale was the one from Zhao Hai’s Space. He had turned this Blade Scale Whale into an undead that was the same as Alien. It’s build had given them the opportunity to make it into rooms. And since the Blade Scale Whale was bigger than Alien, its room inside was very big as well. Zhao Hai had a living room, bedroom, as well as a bath installed inside.

Naturally, these things were only there as decoration. Zhao Hai would spend most of his time inside the Space.

The Blade Scale Whale was completely preserved. The layer of skin outside has been preserved as well. However, its skin had been turned transparent. One could clearly see the outside while being inside the whale.

Most importantly, there was no water that can come into the whale, so there weren’t any seawater inside. At the same time, Zhao Hai can also use magic in order to ensure that they have ample amounts of air to breathe inside.

At this time, Zhao Hai was inside the whale along with Laura and the others. There was only one outsider inside, and it was the person who the Queen had sent in order to help Zhao Hai, the little mermaid Luo Luo.

The mermaids didn’t have their own unique mounts. However, they had a peculiar ability that nobody had. They can turn any marine beast into their own mount. Naturally, there were also some Mermaids who decided to raise their own beasts as their mounts, but those instances were rare.

The Queen told Zhao Hai that Luo Luo would be there to help him be familiar with the various Fishman races. But she wouldn’t interfere with Zhao Hai’s fight.

Actually, there was no need for the Queen to tell him since he already knew about Luo Luo. But he didn’t say anything and just politely invited Luo Luo inside the blade scale whale. He also prepared a room filled with sea water inside.

The reinforcement army slowly went towards the frontline. Although they had passed through some small tribes, these people were all under the rule of the Mermaids. Some small tribes even dispatched their members to aid the reinforcement army.

At the same time, there were also some Fishman tribes who would bring over some marine beast corpses. Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t become polite as he made them into undead on the spot. There were also some beasts that the army had taken along the way, so they were also handed over to Zhao Hai.

Dashan had calculated that the amount of undead that Zhao Hai had made these days had now reached over five hundred thousand. Such quantity was astonishing, it was now a fourth the amount of the reinforcing army.

At this point, the shock and fear that Dashan held towards Zhao Hai had gradually turned numb. Even if Zhao Hai managed to turn all of the beasts in the ocean into undead, he wouldn’t be surprised anymore.

Although their number is huge, their advancement wasn’t slow. This was the sea, not the land, so the army doesn’t need to worry about terrain, grass, nor food. This was the ocean where there were too many kinds of low level magic beasts. These people cannot even finish eating their food, much less worry about it.

Chapter 618: Defensive Line

It was already dark, and they were already deep in the sea and could only barely get some sunlight. However, there were still a lot of them to the point where many smaller Fishmen have been pushed near the surface, which made them the target for some aerial magic beasts. During their day trip they didn’t rest even for a bit, therefore, they needed to get some sleep in the evening.

Zhao Hai and the others were now inside the Blade Scale Whale’s living room. It had been a few days since they had gone out of Mermaid Island. However, they didn’t have much time for each other because Luo Luo was with them. And since Laura and the others had become close friends with her, they would oftentimes sleep with each other. Because of that, Zhao Hai had very small opportunities to talk with his wives.

Today, Luo Luo had finally rested on her own. So Zhao Hai and the others gained the opportunity to gather inside the Space. Zhao Hai looked at Laura and the others’ expression, they seemed like they hadn’t had a good sleep for a while. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “What’s wrong? You haven’t been resting in the Space lately, didn’t have a good sleep?’

Laura smiled bitterly and said, “I really don’t know why, but Mermaids are very cold. It would be strange if one can sleep comfortably with them .”

Lizzy nodded as well and said, “But I still envy the Mermaids. Surprisingly, they cannot look old. No matter how high their age is, they would still look like they are 20 years old.”

This was the first time that Zhao Hai had heard of this matter. He couldn’t help but look at Lizzy and said, “Oh, is that it? No wonder I can’t see any old mermaids during our stay in Mermaid Island. Also, why aren’t there any men in their clan? How do they reproduce?’

When Megan heard Zhao Hai, her face couldn’t help but turn red, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “The Mermaids have a secret ability. After a certain age, as long as they eat a special fruit from mermaid island, they would get pregnant and bear a child. There is also another way, once a Queen reaches 40 years old, she can use a special method to make an egg of which little mermaids would hatch from. But this method would harm the Queen’s vitality. Something that the fruit would not.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he muttered and said, “So it’s like that. No wonder I can’t see any men. Haha. So what have you been doing in Mermaid Island? Did you have fun? Also, did you manage to see the fruit?”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and couldn’t help but chuckle, “I already know which question you want answered. And yes, we did see it. The fruit only grows in Mermaid Island. The fruit is in the root itself, and it directly absorbs nutrients from the sea, it was very mysterious. We begged for half a day before they allowed us to get a section of the root. Cai’er has placed it in the warehouse.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Oh? I didn’t know about this. Cai’er, quickly show me the root.” Cai’er nodded and then took the root out.

After the root was taken out, a prompt immediately came from the Space, “Discovered a root that is full of vitality. The vitality of everything in the Space has been improved. If planted in the Space, the root’s vitality would get stronger and stronger. Space has levelled up to level 59. Looking forward to the Host’s further efforts.”

Zhao Hai stared before he became exhilarated with joy. He immediately had Cai’er pick a place to plant the root. In the end, the root was planted right beside the villa with Cai’er taking good care of it.

Megan and the others didn’t expect the root to upgrade the Space. After Zhao Hai planted the roots, he couldn’t help but turn to Laura and the others before laughing happily, “My wives, you really did great this time. Let this one give you a present. We’ll work hard in making the next generation!” Then he pulled Megan into the villa. Although Laura and the others were blushing, they still followed behind….

The army had travelled for 13 days by now, at this point, they were already in a place not too far away from the frontlines. They were currently preparing to take a rest so that they can reach the frontlines in one go.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t object to this. He also wasn’t idling in these past few days. In addition to turning Magic Beasts into undead, Zhao Hai had also been learning how to lead an underwater army from Dashan.

In the war between Humans and the Beastmen, Zhao Hai had managed to learn how the Humans and the Beastmen lead their troops. However, the methods used by the Fishmen were different. First, while the Beastmen and Humans needed to worry about logistics, the Fishmen did not, so Zhao Hai didn’t need to worry about that aspect anymore. And another was the fact that Fishmen Army can move in three dimensions while the Humans and Beastmen can only use the flat land. Leading and fighting in this three dimensional battlefield was a completely different world to Zhao Hai.

A Human and Beastman Race army’s advance was divided into the Vanguard, the Center Army, and the Rear Guard. Those three were the most common formation for any army in the continent. But the Fishmen had a different approach, compared to the continent, the formations of the Fishmen were much more complicated. If the continent’s army can be seen as three blocks, a Fishman army would be just like a Rubik’s Cube. Each face of the cube would have 9 armies while the most important officials of the army would be at the core of the cube.

This way of leading an army made Zhao Hai’s eyes blank. This kind can of formation can not only attack, it can also defend properly while at the same time, leaving enough room for retreat. There were a lot of possibilities with such a formation, it was really an eye-opener.

This arrangement of the Fishmen was naturally much more difficult to manage compared to Human armies. It was great that they didn’t need to worry about logistics. Otherwise, Zhao Hai reckoned that even those Fishman generals would have trouble in going to war.

Dashan is the captain of the Mermaid clan’s guards, so his ability was certainly not average. Although this army comprised of 2 million people, Dashan still managed to easily take command. Looking at him made Zhao Hai learn a lot.

In order to learn how Dashan was leading the army, Zhao Hai stayed close to him these past few days. He even had Cai’er record his movements. Before Zhao Hai went to take a rest at night, he would repeatedly look and review Dashan’s way of leading his troops.

Laura and the others had become curious as well, so they also joined Zhao Hai’s research. In the end, Zhao Hai had found out that he had no talent in leading an army. If he were to be a commander, he can only be a vice or someone who managed a small division. If they really had him lead, who knows what would happen?

What surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that Lizzy and Megan seemed to have talent in leading armies. If they were to lead an army, they would surely find it quite easy.

As for Laura, she was already a mighty force in commerce, so her skills in commanding an army was only on par with Zhao Hai. The two almost had the same talent.

Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai decided to stop studying and just had Megan and Lizzy learn it instead. In any case, they had nothing else to do. Generally, they would go and help Laura in managing the Buda Clan’s matters. But in fact, Laura alone was enough to do all those things. But it was good that they now had something else to do, this made them much happier with this development than Zhao Hai.

However, they still couldn’t be considered genuine commanders at this point. After all, the things that they had learned this time were only about Battle Formations. They still had very few knowledge about the battlefield itself.

Zhao Hai wasn’t under anyone’s command, so as soon as the battle against the Sea Dragons start, they would have a chance to lead an army. This would give the two some experience in combat.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others hurried on towards the frontlines. Zhao Hai also asked Luo Luo about the current situation there.

The frontline was in a very special terrain, on its left side was a trench. This trench was called the Devil Trench by the Fishmen because of the cold undercurrent present in its deeper parts. This undercurrent was invisible, and it doesn’t matter if it’s a beast or Fishman, once they get in contact with this undercurrent, they would immediately be frozen to death. And after getting washed away, they would immediately shatter into pieces. Most importantly, this place was also the domain of the devil octopuses.

The devil octopuses were top level magic beasts of the sea. Every grown devil octopus possessed nearly 9th rank strength. And they were the only beings that were able to survive in the trench. Fortunately, devil octopuses rarely went out of their territory. But even so, this area was still labelled as forbidden by the Fishman population.

On the right side of the frontline was also another restricted area, the Soul Sucking Reef! This reef was densely covered in corals. All of those who went inside it had never managed to come out. The Fishmen had already sent people to examine the place. They didn’t go too deep, but they understood that the situation inside was indeed very alarming.

In Soul Sucking Reef, as long as someone goes in, they would immediately lose all sense of direction. They would find themselves to be walking around in circles. This kind of trap works in all directions, not just in two dimensions. Additionally, there were also poisonous magic beasts inside. The threat that those magic beasts posed weren’t something to be scoffed at either. Once you are poisoned, you won’t be spared.

Because of these two places, the Mermaid Clan had decided to place their defensive line here. This place was the most appropriate place to establish their defense. The ocean was just too big, and since the Fishmen didn’t build any cities, it would be nearly impossible just to find a place to bunker up.

While depending on the terrain, the Mermaid Clan managed to establish a defensive line of about a thousand li(500km). Although the present army only comprised of 6 million troops, they were still able to block the attacks of the Sea Dragons for more than a month.

Zhao Hai’s army was only the first batch of reinforcements. There would still be a second and third batch that would be coming in the next few days. After those armies arrive, the true battle would start.

However, since Zhao Hai had joined, everything had suddenly changed. In the past few days, Zhao Hai had already amassed over 1 million marine undead beasts. Additionally, he can also turn any corpse into undead at any time.

Chapter 619: Azure Dragon Battle Snail

When Zhao Hai arrived at the frontline, he was stunned. He wasn’t expecting the frontline to be like this.

The way the Fishmen set-up their defensive line was completely different from the Humans. A Human’s defensive line would have to be a castle or some kind of wall or so on. But the Fishmen’s defensive line was a completely different thing. There were no structures present whatsoever. The place can only be described as extremely clean. It was a place that was unusually clean for a place where slaughter would happen constantly.

Zhao Hai looked around and sure enough, he couldn’t see an army on the left and right sides of the defensive line. Only in the middle, about a thousand miles away, was an army of Fishmen. They didn’t have any camps and were just arranged in a square matrix pattern. These squares would comprise of people of the same tribe. There were nearly a thousand squares in this area.

These squares were all three dimensional. Some were close to the surface while some were close to the bottom of the sea. There were cubes all around, it would make someone stare for a long time.

After Zhao Hai and the others arrived, they didn’t immediately join the defense army. Instead, they stopped at a distance before the defensive line. Zhao Hai knew that this was due to Dashan. If they joined the defense army, they might disrupt their present formation. And breaking a defensive formation was not something to joke about.

After the reinforcing army stopped, Dashan went towards Zhao Hai’s Blade Scale Whale. Zhao Hai was now aware of the benefits of being a Dark Mage. It was the fact that nobody dared to bother you. The more than 2 million troops, from the beginning until now, had stayed far away from Zhao Hai’s Blade Scale Whale. One could even clearly see that they would take an effort to circumvent the Blade Scale Whale whenever the fishmen passed by it.

Regarding this situation, Zhao Hai can only bitterly smile. There was no other way around this. The ways of a Dark Mage were really strange, too strange that it would inflict fear on those around them.

Seeing Dashan approaching him, Zhao Hai immediately went towards the mouth of the whale. When he reached the mouth, Zhao Hai used water magic to keep the water from coming in before he had the whale open its mouth.

After some time, Dashan had finally arrived and saw that Zhao Hai was already standing there. He immediately gave Zhao Hai a bow and said, “I’ve seen mister Zhao Hai. I ask mister Zhao Hai to join me in meeting General Luo Ying.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, please take the lead, Captain.” Dashan nodded and then turned his mount towards a large fishman formation.

Zhao Hai commanded the Blade Scale Whale to follow Dashan. There were nobody else beside Dashan, he was completely alone. Zhao Hai did the same as well, he only had the Blade Scale Whale appear while collecting all other undead. He didn’t want a large group of undead to unnecessarily swim all around the place.

Before long, the two of them entered the large formation. Upon entering, Zhao Hai had come across some Fishmen that he hasn’t seen before. And all of them had eyes curiously looking at Zhao Hai while Zhao Hai also looked at them curiously.

It didn’t take a long time before they reached the core of the entire formation. Most importantly, the core of the formation was also the place where the commander of the army was. While Zhao Hai was still far away, his gaze couldn’t help but freeze. In the middle of this large formation was something that made him gawk, it was very enormous conch!

The conch was very enormous, it was nearly 100 meters high, even city walls can only be 30 meters high. This conch was azure, And the patterns on its body looked just like a coiling dragon.

Upon seeing this conch, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gawk. This was because he knew what which being this conch belonged to. It was from the extremely famous Azure Dragon Snail!

Azure Dragon Snails weren’t only famous among the Fishmen, even the Humans were in awe of such a being. This snail had two points of importance, first was its defensive capability, and the other was its very formidable support Water Magic.

This Azure Dragon Snail doesn’t grow up easily either. It would grow by about 1 meter every ten years. For such an Azure Dragon Snail to reach this big, it should have been living for more than a millenium. If one places this in the continent, it would undoubtedly become an extremely priceless treasure. Even the Fishmen would see this Snail’s value as immeasurable.

Laura and the others were at Zhao Hai’s side, looking dumbfoundedly on this incomparably huge Azure Dragon Snail. They didn’t think that there would be an Azure Dragon Snail this big. One must know that even a young Azure Dragon Snail would be able to block a 9th rank experts attach, showing how strong their defensive capabilities were. And as long as you have an Azure Dragon Snail, your Water Magics would be improved by 300%. Naturally, this support magic was something extremely terrifying in battle.

Even more so with this thousand year old Azure Dragon Snail, its abilities should be endless at this point. This snail could maybe even resist the attacks of several 9th rank experts for quite a long time.

This Azure Dragon Snail was itself a 9th rank magic beast. But for this magic beast, its courage was extremely small. Even a hundred year old 9th rank Azure Dragon Snail would still be afraid of any 8th rank magic beast.

The food of Azure Dragon Snails were also very special. They can only eat one type of seaweed and it was a type of seaweed that was very scarce. Because of this, the population of Azure Dragon Snails was extremely small. In the entire ocean, there might only be one or two more Azure Dragon Snails of this size.

Luo Luo looked at their expressions and couldn’t help but feel a sense of pride, with a proud voice she said, “This is our Mermaid clan’s special Battle Snail. After generations of refining, this Azure Dragon Snail can block and counter the attacks of six 9th rank experts. For out counter attack against the Sea Dragons, Her Majesty has allowed General Luo Ying to use this Azure Dragon Snail.”

It was at this point that Zhao Hai and the others had recovered, the group couldn’t help but inhale cold air. This Azure Dragon Snail was unexpectedly very formidable, they didn’t expect it to be able to withstand the attacks of six 9th rank experts. One must know that it can’t only block, it can retaliate as well. This meant that the power of this snail was more or less equivalent to six 9th rank experts. It was really astonishing.

Most importantly, Luo Luo had mentioned something peculiar. The snail was actually refined by the Mermaids for generations. Does this mean that this Azure Dragon Snail was a product of refining? This information alone is worth the shock.

Fishmen lived their whole lives underwater, this meant that they had close to zero chances of using fire. But it was general knowledge that refinement involved fire of some sort. How could the Mermaid clan use fire to refine this Azure Dragon Snail? This was inconceivable.

After seeing the reactions of Zhao Hai and the others, Luo Luo couldn’t help but chuckle as she added, “Is mister surprised by the fact that our Mermaid clan was able to do refining? In fact, this was largely due to a great Queen from 3000 years ago. This Queen was a 9th rank expert herself, but she was much more interested in crafting. After years of experimentation, she finally invented a way to refine using water. It was a way of refining that uses fire, not water, in order to process the materials. This refining process was very effective as well. Our Mermaid clan’s goods might not be as good as the Dwarves, but we can claim that we aren’t much worse than those made by the Human Race.”

Zhao Hai and the others stared at Luo Luo, this was the first time that they had heard of such a thing. Can someone really use water to refine? That is incredible!

At the same time, Zhao Hai had developed full respect towards that great Queen. Zhao Hai knew that water refinement was completely different from using fire to refine. For that Great Queen to invent this method was a very great feat. If the continent was to learn this, the whole refining theory would be completely turned upside down.

Luo Luo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “We Fishmen can also find some metals underwater. Additionally, there are also beast bones as well as precious stones and special seaweeds. These things can all be refined into weapons of other things. The trident that Dashan uses was made from refining beast bones and precious stones. Not only is its hardness on par with metals, it is also quite tough. Most importantly, it also couldn’t be corroded easily. Those kinds of weapons are the most suitable for the Fishmen.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he couldn’t bear but sigh, “That Great Queen was really talented. Only a genius could come up with such a method.”

Luo Luo proudly nodded, but her expression turned gloomy as she said, “However, this water refining also has a lot of limitations. It’s output is quite limited since not all Fishman can use it. The ones who could use this method are only those who belong to my Mermaid Race. Because of that, the amount of people we had given good weapons only number in the few.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he thought that it was reasonable. If this water refining method had no limitations, then the strength of the whole Fishmen Race would certainly increase explosively. The sea was a whole mass of water. If all the Fishmen were to use this Water Refining method, then wouldn’t he ocean become a huge weapon processing factory?

Luo Luo then said, “Millenniums ago, our Mermaid Clan has obtained this Azure Dragon Snail. At that time, the Snail was already dead, only leaving this huge conch behind. After we brought the conch to Mermaid Island, the Queen immediately refined it along with numerous other Mermaids. And after refining this conch for several hundred years, it became like this. At this point, the strength of this Azure Dragon Snail had reached great heights.”

Zhao Hai sighed once again, he was truly amazed this time. Although the Buda Clan had become very strong, it still lacked so much history compared to thousand year old forces. This history had truly shown its might at this moment.

The Mermaid clan was able to make this powerful conch largely due to their hundreds of years of refining. This was something that the Buda Clan would never have, they didn’t have such a deep history.

At this time, Zhao Hai and Dashan were not in front of the battle snail. When they were close, they could see how extraordinary this snail was. The draconic image on the snail seems to be able to fly into the skies at any time. And if one looks closely, one would find that there was some metallic sheen to it. This showed how hard it was.

When Zhao Hai’s group got close to the snail, several Mermaids swam out of it and blocked them from proceeding.

Chapter 620: Cone Attack

When Zhao Hai saw the Mermaids, he couldn’t help but stare. The Mermaids that he saw before were either wearing shells or a long seaweed gown. He wasn’t able to see them wearing any other clothing. Laura and the others also asked the Mermaids about the reason why they don’t wear much clothing. The reason was because not wearing anything made them feel the water element much easier. For their cultivation, this was something very good.

But these Mermaids that just came out of the Azure Dragon Snail wore something that Zhao Hai had not seen before. They were all on full body armor, they also had a Magic Staff on their hands.

The armor of these Mermaids seem to be made out of shells and bones of magic beasts. It was dark blue and looked very beautiful. It also had a helmet that made the originally sweet and pretty Mermaids look very heroic.

The Magic Staff on their hands looked very special as well, it was probably made out of crystals. It was a translucent carving that glittered from time to time. At the same time, it also looked quite tough, it might be even possible to use it as a weapon.

Zhao Hai looked at these Mermaids and couldn’t help but smile bitterly. These Mermaids are really unique. Not only are they born with an innate affinity for water, they are also innately Water Mages. Moreover, they can also control marine beasts while also having very strong physical strength that was enough to be a threat. They were almost perfect beings.

After the Mermaids blocked Zhao Hai’s group, they inspected them first before they gave the two a bow and said, “The General is already waiting for Captain Dashan and Mister Zhao Hai. Please follow us.”

Zhao Hai and Dashan nodded, and then swam towards the Azure Dragon Snail. The space inside the snail was not small, however, Zhao Hai and Dashan’s mounts weren’t allowed to enter. It seems like it would be difficult for them to make a turn inside.

Zhao Hai turned to Luo Luo and the others and then said, “The space here is not so big, so I need to collect the Blade Scale Whale. Luo Luo, you can swim by yourself. You guys, come with me.”

Laura and the others nodded and then gathered to Zhao Hai’s side. Then Zhao Hai wielded his staff as a giant bubble surrounded them. After that, Zhao Hai collected the Blade Scale Whale.

Now that the Blade Scale Whale has been collected, the space inside the snail had gotten much bigger. Luo Luo swam towards the other Mermaids and gave them a salute before calling them sisters. The warrior Mermaids also returned Luo Luo’s gesture, none of them looked down on her.

Dashan also dismounted from his whale. After that, the group went towards the Azure Dragon Snail and then entered it. After a while, they came into a hall which was made out of animal bones and aquatic plants. The floor as well as some chairs and tables were made out of either bone or wood. All of it was arranged to look like a warrior’s hall.

But what made Zhao Hai surprised was the fact that there wasn’t a drop of water in this hall. On the innermost part of the hall was a couch, the couch looked like a small bed. And a Mermaid warrior was lying on this couch.

When Zhao Hai’s group entered the hall, Dashan and Luo Luo simultaneously bowed towards the Mermaid warrior, “This one has seen General Luo Ying.”

Luo Ying looked up to Luo Luo and the others before nodding. Zhao Hai also led Laura and the others and said, “Zhao Hai has seen General Luo Ying”

Luo Ying stood up and then returned Zhao Hai’s gesture, “Luo Ying has seen Mister Zhao Hai. Our Mermaid clan is deeply grateful for Mister Zhao Hai’s assistance.” Her voice sounded somewhat chilly. Although she had the same attractive features as the other mermaids, she seems quite different. The Queen had an aura of elegance and maturity, Luo Luo gave out an aura of energy, like a beauty under sunlight. But this General appeared somewhat chilly, she was like a beauty that also held a martial aura.

After exchanging greetings, Luo Ying asked Zhao Hai and the others to sit down. Then Luo Ying turned to Dashan and said, “You came just in time. The Sea Dragons have been increasing the intensity of their attacks these past few days. Moreover, they seemed to have a lot of experts that were helping them, causing us heavy losses. At this moment, the defense army has been reduced to four million troops. It’s fortunate that you came in order to supplement the losses.”

Dashan became shocked, “The Sea Dragons had help? Who?”

Luo Ying shook her head, then her brows wrinkled as she said, “I don’t know yet. But they don’t seem to be Fishmen. They have been using Dragon Beads in order to repel water.”

Zhao Hai looked puzzled at Luo Ying and said, “General, can you tell me what these water repelling Dragon Beads are? I’m quite curious about them.”

Luo Ying wasn’t planning on hiding anything from Zhao Hai. So she nodded and then pointed to two gems in front her her and said, “These are Dragon Beads. They are something made from the eyes of Sea Dragons. No matter how deep you are, once you have one of these in your body, a shield would surround you. This would repel the surrounding water while at the same time, allowing you to breath naturally. But since Sea Dragons get buried as soon as they die, these Dragon Beads weren’t very common.”

Zhao Hai turned his attention towards the two blue beads. These beads don’t look like eyes. They were as big as one’s fist and looked just like two ordinary gems.

Luo Ying looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and said, “After Sea Dragons die, their eyes would slowly contract before turning into this appearance. These Dragon Beads have been used by the Sea Dragon’s helpers in order to give up huge losses. All of them were very strong moreover, there seems to be a lot of them. I suspect that after Sea Dragons die,  their kinsmen would get their beads to use in times like these.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Luo Ying and said, “General, why haven’t they attacked today?”

Luo Ying shook her head and said, “They’ve already attacked once but then drew back. I believe they would attack again soon.” Then after she said that, a rumbling sound was then heard from outside.

Luo Ying’s face changed as she said, “They’re attacking!” Then she waved her hand as a water curtain appeared on the hall. The water curtain rippled before it showed the situation outside. But compared to Zhao Hai’s monitor, the curtain was somewhat unclear, it was quite blurry.

However, this was still enough to surprise Zhao Hai and the others. This was the first time that they had seen someone else use a kind of magic that was similar to the monitor. If they knew about this magic before, they might already have a reason to use the monitor outside.

Although they have been surprised, Zhao Hai still kept his focus on the image that was on the curtain. They were attracted to the the fight that was about to happen.

They saw an army approaching from the opposite side. But the formation of this army was very strange. It looked like a huge cone and was constantly rotating. The tip of this cone was a big Fishman. The person had white skin and was about 5 meters tall. He had a large bone spear on his hand while having two large fins on his side and a large one behind him. He had a big bald head and was opening his mouth, revealing a row of sharp teeth. He looked like a terrifying monster that would inflict fear on anyone.

At this time, Luo Ying opened her mouth and said, “They’re using the cone formation this time. The one top the lead is a shark, a famous warrior named Sha Meng. Although this person is only 8th rank, his innate talent in weapons is terrifying. Moreover, he has a strong resistance towards magic. He is very difficult to deal with. In the ten times that they had attacked, 6 of them has him in the lead.”

Then Zhao Hai saw that the defenders have also changed. Their formation had become similar to a swirling vortex. The center of the vortex was facing the tip of the cone. Once the cone stabbed into the vortex, the whole thing immediately released blood. The surrounding seas have been turned red.

At this moment, Dashan stood up, he bowed to Luo Ying and said, “General, let me join the fight. That Sha Meng has been quite fierce!” Dashan was also a famous warrior among the Whales. The Whales have always been stronger than the Sharks. So when he saw how that Sha Meng was being fierce, Dashan couldn’t help but get the itch to fight.

But Luo Ying shook her head and said, “Don’t worry, someone would be able to repel Sha Meng. You just arrived, so you needed rest. This time is just a probing attack, in a while, they would retreat.”

Dashan sat down, but his eyes still showed his stubbornness as he stared at the water curtain. Although the image on the water curtain was clouded by blood, Dashan still kept staring, as though Sha Meng might come out of it any second.

Sure enough, just as Luo Ying said, this was just a probing attack. Before long, the opposite party had started to draw back, with the rear guard personally led by Sha Meng. After the confrontation, Sha Meng didn’t look tired, in fact, he even had the look of excitement.

Seeing the opposite side retreat, Luo Ying took down the water curtain before she turned to Zhao Hai and Dashan before saying, “This attack happens every day for several times. Since this time is only a probe, the next one would be more violent.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “General, can I head out first while it is still convenient to refine those corpses?”

When Luo Ying heard this, she couldn’t help but look deeply at Zhao Hai. Then she nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go.” After that, she took the lead as she stood up and went out.

Upon exiting the Azure Dragon Snail, Zhao Hai immediately summoned his Blade Scale Whale. He tried to invite Luo Ying inside the whale but she snorted before she called a huge seahorse over from the snail. When the seahorse came over, Luo Ying immediately rode it and had it slowly swim towards Zhao Hai’s whale. At the same time, Dashan also rode his mount and went to the other side of Zhao Hai’s whale.

The other Mermaid warriors also called their mounts over and followed behind Luo Ying. Their mounts were also seahorses, and they were all well trained. These seahorses were green and had occasional blue spots on their bodies, their height exceeded five meters. Contrary to what Zhao Hai expected, these seahorses didn’t hop around. They moved stably when they move forward, moreover, they were also quite fast.

Chapter 621: Messenger Fish

Zhao Hai doesn’t know that this seahorse wasn’t an ordinary seahorse, nor was it just an oversized version of it. This seahorse was actually a variant beast.

Whether it be on the Ark Continent or the Sea, magic beasts were always present. And some of these beasts were likely to become different from their own race, people call them variant beasts.

Magic beasts were generally wild beasts that would be able to use magic. But variant beasts were those beasts that had their own Divergent Ability. These two things were different, and naturally, their strengths varied.

Magic beasts would discharge magic through the magic crystal inside their bodies, therefore, they were called magic beasts. But variant beasts are different, they can still use magic, but at the same time, they can also use their Divergent Ability. Divergent abilities, compared to magic was much more formidable. Because of this, one would rather provoke an advanced magic beast rather than a variant beast.

These seahorses that Luo Ying and the others rode on were variant beasts!

They might look like giant fishes and were slow. But in fact, they were experts in water magic while at the same time, being an ice-type variant beast.

Variant beasts were certainly magic beasts, but magic beasts aren’t necessarily variant beasts. This was something that everyone knew. And Luo Ying’s mount were these variant beasts. They were very famous in the entire sea, their name was Ice Seahorse.

Although the name ice seahorse seemed very ordinary, the ‘ice’ part of it held gerat significance. In addition to their ability to do water magic, these seahorses also had an Ice Divergent Ability.

Whether it be offense or defense, the water element has always been inferior to the ice element. And this ice seahorse was a variant beast that can use both. Although their water magics weren’t strong, once they use it, their speeds would be greatly improved to the point that most magic beasts wouldn’t be able to catch up to them. And on the other hand, their Ice element ability was on of a kind, it was the Ice Cone Spell!

Their water magic would act behind their bodies and act as their propeller, making their movements much faster. In addition to that, their ice cone spell would make an ice spear appear in front of them. Not only are they fast, their attacking prowess was also very strong. This gave the ice horses the nickname fiery ice cone beasts.

The name fiery ice cone beast didn’t mean that they can also use fire element magic. This just meant that whenever these seahorses use their maximum speed, it would seem like they were blazing their way through everything. These kinds of beasts would give any Fishman a headache.

Zhao Hai curiously looked at these huge ice seahorses. But he didn’t say anything as the blade scale whale headed towards the battlefield along with Dashan and Luo Ying’s group.

Before long, the group arrived at the battlefield. At the moment, there were a lot of floating corpses present, but these Fishmen didn’t do anything about them. One must know that water always flows, and it wouldn’t take a long time before these corpses would get swept away by the sea current. This was also why Zhao Hai chose to come at this time, he didn’t want to miss the chance of acquiring these corpses.

The Fishmen didn’t have the custom of burying their dead underground. On the contrary, their burials would most likely involve the sea itself. That meant that when a Fishman dies, their kin would use a large shell as a coffin and then just let the shell go and have it slowly drift away. But if they couldn’t find a big shell, they would just place the corpse out there and wait for it to be taken away by the current.

This didn’t mean that the Fishmen were disrespectful to the dead. In fact, it was the direct opposite. The Fishmen highly respected the dead, they just think that since they lived their lives at sea, then after they die, they must return to the sea once again. It was because of this philosophy that they used this way to bury their dead.

These Fishmen also knew that once they let their kinsmen go and drift away, they would certainly become food for the magic beasts. But they still allowed it because they believed that the magic beasts of the sea were beings that were given to them by the Sea God and thus, were part of the sea.

On the battlefield, the Fishmen were doing the same thing. In their view, dying in this battle was akin to being buried at the sea. So there was no need to collect the dead corpses.

Zhao Hai gazed at the floating corpses. Although the contact between the two sides wasn’t long, the casualties couldn’t be described as small. In that short skirmish, there were already about a thousand dead people.

Zhao Hai turned to Luo Ying and said, “General, the bodies of your soldiers, can I use them?”

Luo Ying looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, “Mister, if those soldiers that died knew that they had given us help and had reduced further deaths, then they would certainly be able to rest in peace.”

Zhao Hai looked deeply into Luo Ying. He discovered that Luo Ying was really a qualified general. She was a commander that had a soldier’s heart, only such a person was qualified to be a good general. Only such a person could make soldiers and officers sacrifice their own lives for the greater purpose.

Then Zhao Hai turned his head back to the corpses and waved his hand. A black gas surrounded those corpses before vanishing along with the dead bodies.

Zhao Hai thought that these Fishmen wouldn’t want to see undead at this time. He knew what expressions these Fishmen would give after seeing one. If he made these Fishmen see a pile of skeletons, then their morale would certainly suffer a huge hit. And at this point in the war, morale was extremely critical.

When Luo Ying saw that the corpses vanished, she looked at Zhao Hai, confused. Zhao Hai turned to Luo Ying and then smiled, “General, no need to worry. I have already stored the undead. I’m afraid that revealing those undead at this time will have a huge toll to the troops’ morale.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Luo Ying couldn’t help but nod. She was somewhat amazed at Zhao Hai. She didn’t expect that he would have such a consideration at this time.

Then Zhao Hai looked at the Fishmen and said, “General, if the enemy is coming back, then I might as well stay here. What do you think?”

Luo Ying gawked, she didn’t expect Zhao Hai to take the initiative and volunteer himself for combat. But she still shook her head and said, “Mister doesn’t need to worry. Wars will always be like this everyday, the enemy just wants to grind our numbers down. I want mister to observe for two days while collecting more undead. After that, we can defeat the other party in one fell swoop.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll listen to the general’s arrangement. If general has any need for me, then don’t hesitate to tell me.”

Luo Ying nodded, then he led Zhao Hai and the others back to the Azure Dragon Snail. After arriving inside the snail, Luo Ying immediately called her officers over as they began to disperse Dashan’s reinforcing army into different divisions.

Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to return to the blade scale whale and then go to the Space. But when he saw that Lizzy and Megan were intently looking at how Luo Ying was managing things, he decided to stay.

Before long, the army that Zhao Hai came with was already dispersed to various groups. At the same time, Luo Ying also gave a command to be in full defensive mode. She thought that since the other part already had attacked for a few times, then it was time for them to launch a huge attack. So it was better for them to be prepared.

Zhao Hai carefully observed how Luo Ying divided the troops. He had discovered that although the army was arranged in a cubic matrix, each cube was also comprised of four smaller cubes. One of these smaller cubes had Turtle Fishmen or other defensive Fishmen in them. Another small cube was comprised of long ranged offensive Fishmen, some of them had long reaching attacks while some were those who were able to use long ranged magic. Another small cube was composed of melee attackers, mostly comprised of physically gifted Fishmen. On the last square were the support troops. The role of these troops were to support the other Fishmen while at the same time be the ones to have contact with the central command.

These four small cubes comprised the bigger formations. Some bigger formations were even part of a much bigger formation. This was the composition of their unit. Moreover, this method can allow them to be flexible to whichever command that was given to them.

Another thing that surprised Zhao Hai was their handy way of communicating. In order to relay orders, the Fishmen were using these small messenger fish.

These messenger fishes were very special beings of the sea. Their bodies weren’t big, in fact, they were quite small. However, their swimming speed was very quick. Moreover, they can also be easily trained. Most importantly, these fishes were able to transmit information to each other. Even if two fishes were far away, they can still send forth a special signal towards one another.

The Fishmen uses this ability of the messenger fish to send message towards one another. Their messages were in code as well, and were made so that the message would be received at the shortest amount of time and at the safest way. If one doesn’t know the secret code, then even if one has a messenger fish, then they still wouldn’t know what the other party was saying.

Upon knowing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but think about his time back on earth, when he was watching a movie on the television. Both sides of the line were using telegraphs, which was naturally a more primitive version of the mobile phone or even the telephone. But in the Ark Continent, this discovery was still a very huge thing.

Zhao Hai became very interested in this fish, so he expressed his want for one of them to Luo Ying. He immediately sent one to the Space so that they can multiply. Although it didn’t upgrade the Space, its ability improved Zhao Hai’s way of communicating with the Space.

Chapter 622: Mobile Phone? Telephone?

The Space’s ability to communicate had always been a problem. Only Zhao Hai had the ability to conveniently use it. If Laura and the others left the Space, then Zhao Hai can only find them before appearing in their midst. Or he could have Cai’er tell them what was going on. But Cai’er was only one entity, making multiple communications quite inconvenient.

Now that he had the messenger fish, everything became different. When the messenger entered the space, it was immediately strengthened and improved. And since the Space came from Earth, the messenger fish’s communication has been upgraded, it can now talk!

Naturally, this didn’t mean that the fish itself was able to converse. This meant that the fish can now convey spoken word. Zhao Hai can now speak towards the messenger fish and then had the message transmitted through the Space and then to another Space produced messenger fish on someone else’s hand.

When Zhao Hai heard of this new function, he couldn’t help but get stunned. So the Space would essentially function like a satellite while the messenger fishes would act as mobile phones.

Although messenger fishes cannot leave water, which was their weak point, this wasn’t an issue for Zhao Hai and the others. He can have space bags that contained bottles in them. Once the fishes were placed on the bottles, then they can be stored inside the space bags.

These messenger fish weren’t large, and their appearance were also beautiful, so they can pass off as ornamental fishes. Even if it wasn’t placed in a space bag, it would still function like a landline when placed at someone’s office.

It wasn’t only Zhao Hai who was pleasantly surprised at this new discovery. Laura and the others were also extremely stunned. They immediately had Cai’er mass produce these messenger fishes inside the Space, then had them sent over to Kun, Green, and the others. In the future, communicating with everyone would be much more convenient.

Zhao Hai and the others weren’t expecting to reap huge harvests in their trip to the Fishmen this time. For them, this harvest was very important. Because of this, every single important matter of the Buda Clan would quickly reach Zhao Hai’s ears at the quickest possible time.

While Zhao Hai and the others were busy with the messenger fish, Luo Ying wasn’t idling as well. The enemy had finally made their move two hours after their previous attack.

This attack was different from the conical formation from before. This time, they were advancing in a straightforward manner. It seems like they want a huge fight. Zhao Hai and the others were inside the Azure Dragon Snail, looking at the scene through the water curtain.

Luo Ying’s table had a messenger fish. This fish was placed on a crystal bowl and was used to send messages to different people. But compared to the Space’s messenger fish, this fish naturally fell short.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the interest to pay any attention to this messenger fish at this point. He just blankly stared at the enemy forces who were slowly inching forward. Their speed wasn’t very quick, and their formation was very compact. The enemy’s formation and Luo Ying’s formation were almost similar, both formations looked like a Rubik’s cube.

In front of the enemy’s formation were the Electric Eels and other long-ranged attackers. It looks like the opposite party was prepared to launch a large scale attack.

Luo Ying was also paying attention to the lineup of the enemy. At the same time, she was using magic directed at the messenger fishes as she gave one command after another.

Naturally, Luo Ying didn’t use this to give command to the entire army. She sends messages to her officers through this fish and then the officers would them relay the message to the appropriate units.

Along with the advancement of the enemy, the defensive line had also started to change bit by bit. Those defensive Fishmen who weren’t afraid of the Electric Eels had slowly reached the front of the formation. The offensive Fishmen were also slowly going to the back.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai would see a full collision between two Fishman armies. The two sides faced off at this small piece of the defensive line. It was like there was a rule that one would attack while one defends.

The distance between the two armies was getting shorter and shorter. At about 200 meters away, the advancing army stopped. Then suddenly, blue lightning started to appear from the enemy’s formation. This lightning quickly crept towards the defending troops. Naturally, this was the Electric Eels launching their attacks.

The defensive troops quickly responded, the defensive race made a move as them and their mounts blocked the attack.

Zhao Hai paid close attention to the battle. He wasn’t expecting the Electric Eels to be able to control lightning so well. When electricity is used underwater, it would generally disperse immediately. Attacking using electricity underwater was near impossible, but the Electric Eels still managed to do it. This showed how strong their attacks were, to Zhao Hai, it was really amazing.

But the defensive troops couldn’t just sit still and not counter attack. Water arrows and ice spears had started to bombard the attacking army. At this time, long-ranged attacks from both sides had started to appear.

After ten rounds of long-ranged attacks, the Electric Eels had probably ran out of juice. Their lightnings were getting weaker and weaker. At this point, they were now starting to use water arrows and ice spears in attacking the defenders.

However, their attacks became weaker and weaker. This scene also happened at the side of the defenders .Then the enemy army started to change. Those responsible for long-ranged attacks had slowly drawn back. Those suited for close combat started to appear at the front.

Luo Ying immediately issued the command to change the formation. Their own army’s melee troops have also started to come out front. At this time, the long-ranged attacks have started to die down. Then, the melee troops started to charge.

The attacking army’s charge was similar to Sha Meng’s cone formation. But this time, instead of a single giant cone, multiple smaller cones had appeared.

Seeing this, Luo Ying suddenly issued another command, “Prepare the Falling Stone formation!”

Immediately, the other Mermaids relayed the order and the defensive army moved. The whole army seemed to be spinning all the time. Before long, the Sea Dragon army had finally come into contact with the Mermaid army. Then suddenly, innumerable stones began to rain down on the Sea Dragon army. Given the speed at which the stones were flying, it was for certain that their damage wouldn’t be small.

The enemy wasn’t expecting this move as got hit by the stones. However, they were now very close to the other army and eventually slammed into the big defensive wall. The defenders had successfully defended against the attack as their revolution remained undisturbed. Like a killing machine, the defensive army kept killing the Sea Dragon’s troops.

Upon seeing this situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. Then he turned his head towards Luo Luo who wasn’t far away. Luo Luo can be said to be well informed about the Fishman Race. There wasn’t a tribe that she didn’t have any knowledge of. It was because of this that the Queen had her go along with Zhao Hai.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s look, Luo Luo immediately knew what he would ask, so she immediately said, “These attacks came from the Rockfish tribe. They’re quite strange. Generally, we Fishmen would use our water magic as long-ranged attacks. But these Rockfishes have their stones. In their bodies was a pouch that can load a certain amount of stones. When they run into an enemy, they would spurt out these stones and wound them. Although this process wasn’t very different to any offensive water magic, the damage it would cause was much greater than any water spell.”

Zhao Hai nodded, to be honest, he already wasn’t surprised about any of these. Compared to the Fishman Race, the amount of races that were in the Beastman’s Prairie can only be considered to be miniscule.

Zhao Hai was now admiring Luo Ying even more. Knowing each race in the sea was already quite a feat, but knowing about their special abilities and bringing them out to their full potential was something only great generals can do. And Luo Ying was able to do it.

It can be said that Luo Ying’s Falling Stone Formation had already defeated the enemy’s offense. If they maintained this clash, then the enemy might be able to hold out for quite some time. However, their chance of having a deadlock has been lost. The only remaining fate for them if they continue on was a massacre.

Naturally, the opposite party knew about this, so they started to slowly retreat. Their retreat was not fast, but their formation was successfully doing it. Those who performed the attack were now acting as the rear guard while the larger formations turned back.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod, the commander of the opposite party surely wasn’t simple. In this case, giving up a few people to preserve the larger part was a wise idea.

Then Zhao Hai turned his head to Luo Ying and said, “General, get me to send some undead to attack them. Capitalize in their retreating action and leaving them with only a few soldiers left.”

Luo Ying stared, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Fighting on the battlefield at this time is too dangerous for mister.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I don’t have to go out, I can just send them out from here.” After saying that, he waved his hand as clumps of black mist appeared around the Sea Dragon army. After these black mists disappeared, clumps of skeletal beasts appeared right beside the Sea Dragon army. Then those magic beasts went into a cone formation as they charged towards the retreating army.

This development started suddenly and the enemy wasn’t expecting an abnormal person like Zhao Hai to be on the defending army. Zhao Hai’s undead was now starting to wreak havoc on the Sea Dragon army’s formation.

Although this great formation was shaken, it was clear that their commander was extremely talented. He immediately made a response as the formation suddenly rotated. And this time, the rotation wasn’t as a whole, but it was a layer by layer rotation. These layers of rotation and counter rotations managed to block the undead attack.

Chapter 623: War

However, can Zhao Hai’s undead be easily stopped? Although Zhao Hai had limited the strengths of these undead and didn’t let them exhibit 9th rank strength, their fighting prowess was still formidable. So when they clashed, the enemy got caught off guard once again.

Although the Sea Dragon Army had already employed their formation, they were facing against undead that weren’t afraid to die. The army felt how hard it was to block the undead attack. But fortunately for them, these undead would immediately turn into black gas every time they were struck at a vital point in their bodies.

Naturally, this was something that Zhao Hai deliberately did. As long as an undead was critically hit, he would immediately exchange them with a black gas before storing them back into the Space.

At this time, Zhao Hai had sent forth 500 thousand undead creatures. These undead were the magic beasts that he had acquired days before. Zhao Hai wasn’t intending to have these undead withdraw. He wanted to let them smash through the Sea Dragon army until they were wiped out. Of course, their ‘deaths’ would have to be staged.

This was the most terrifying thing about Dark Mages in the battlefield. They were able to command their undead to commit to a suicidal attack, after all, the lives of the undead didn’t matter. And when the enemy retreats, Dark Mages would gather up the corpses and turn them into a new undead army.

The Sea Dragons were currently experiencing this situation. They were facing undead beasts that had more strength than most Fishmen warriors that they had encountered before. They were able to kill one undead but at a cost of many. This wasn’t something that the Sea Dragon army can bear. So the Formation had slowly developed into a rout.

The difference between people and undead was that the undead held no fear for death while people did. Even the most disciplined army had this mentality. The Sea Dragon army was naturally the same.

But it was good for them that Zhao Hai didn’t send a lot of undead, only 500 thousand. Although the undead has caused a disorderly retreat, they still couldn’t budge the large formation of a 3 million troop army.

The fighting strengths of the Fishmen were strong as well, definitely stronger than average magic beasts. The 500 thousand undead that Zhao Hai had sent were eventually eradicated by the Sea Dragon army. This time, the army didn’t dare to stay, they quickly retreated back, afraid of any more attacks from the other party.

The entire undead attack was seen by Luo Ying and the others. No Fishmen were able to use Dark Magic, so this was their first time seeing attacks from undead. If they were to use a word to describe it, then it would be “terrifying”!

The attack power of the undead can only be considered average by Luo Ying’s standards, but the most terrifying thing about the undead was the fact that they wouldn’t die as long as their vital points aren’t hit. Even if their limbs were to be decapitated, they could still perform their attacks. Who wouldn’t be afraid of seeing something like that attacking them?

Luo Ying was a general, so she was very clear about how an attack like this would affect a troop’s morale. At this point, Luo Ying didn’t dare look down on Zhao Hai anymore. The undead that Zhao Hai had sent out had killed more than what they had, this was a terrifying thought.

When the Sea Dragon army retreated, the battlefield became peaceful. Zhao Hai turned his head to Luo Ying and said, “General, I’ll be processing those corpses.”

Luo Ying nodded and said, “Mister, do as you like. I still have some more matters to process, so I wouldn’t be able to accompany mister. Dashan, you go and be mister’s escort.” Dashan nodded and went out with Zhao Hai.

When they arrived outside the snail, they immediately rode their mounts and went to the battlefield. Zhao Hai then turned the dead unto his minions. All in all, he had added more than one million  undead into his army.

In this more than a million undead, 800 thousand were Sea Dragon troops while the remaining 300 thousand were from the defense army. But 600 thousand of those from the Sea Dragon army died in the hands of Zhao Hai’s undead. This showed how deadly the undead were.

Currently, Zhao Hai became more and more pleasing to Dashan’s eyes. He also understood what Luo Ying meant. Zhao Hai, who can minimize their losses while greatly harming the enemy was a very terrifying weapon in the battlefield.

The other Fishmen had also become aware of Zhao Hai’s prowess. The Fishmen were originally clueless about what Zhao Hai was doing. But the reinforcing army that came with Zhao Hai had told them about what he did back at mermaid island, and in addition to seeing the current attack, they were now in awe and veneration towards Zhao Hai.

After Zhao Hai turned the Fishmen into undead, he returned to the blade scale whale and told Dashan that he needed to rest and wouldn’t be returning to the Azure Dragon Snail. Dashan didn’t say anything, after all, Zhao Hai was the Fishman Race’s ally. Him, and even Luo Ying, didn’t have the authority to give Zhao Hai any commands. Because of this, Dashan just let Zhao Hai do what he wants.

Zhao Hai entered the blade scale whale and then opened the monitor. Laura and the others were also right by his side. They looked at the monitor with great interest, they didn’t care much about the situation of today’s war, but they wanted to see Luo Ying’s reaction inside the azure dragon snail.

Luo Luo remained with Luo Ying at this time, so Zhao Hai and the others can just comfortably watch the scene in the monitor.

Seeing Zhao Hai leave, Luo Ying immediately called Luo Luo over and said, “Luo Luo, how did this mister Zhao Hai arrive at our Fishman Race’s domain. Why did he come?”

Luo Luo immediately narrated about how Zhao Hai asked to see the Queen and then told her about the matter of the Divine Race. Although Luo Ying knew about Zhao Hai’s existence, the information that she received from the messenger fish was inadequate. Seeing Zhao Hai fight today made Luo Ying careful towards Zhao Hai. In her opinion, Zhao Hai was too dangerous, therefore she asked Luo Luo about Zhao Hai’s origin.

After Luo Luo finished talking, Luo Ying nodded and said, “So that’s how it is. I didn’t think that Mister would have so many status in the Human lands. It looks like mister would become our race’s most solid ally. Having an ally like him would be a great boon for our race.

Luo Luo nodded and said, “The Queen said the same thing. General will the war end soon now that Mister Zhao Hai is here?”

Luo Ying forced a smile and said, “Silly Luo Luo, how could it be that easy, do you really think that the Sea Dragons would be that weak? Also, it seems like the Sea Dragons have gained help from the Humans and Dragons of the continent. If that really is the case, then it would be possible for them to have Light Dragons and people of the Radiant Church among them. Both of those entities are well versed in Light magic. And light magic is the nemesis of dark magic. Mister Zhao Hai’s means would be limited because of that.”

The Fishmen had their own intelligence network in the continent, therefore they also had some understanding about Dark Mages. So it wouldn’t be strange for them to know that light magic was the bane of Dark Mages. But what Luo Ying didn’t know was the fact that Zhao Hai was different from any Dark Mage. General Dark Mages might be afraid of light magic, but Zhao Hai didn’t care much of it.

When Luo Luo heard Luo Ying, her expression couldn’t help but change. Then she said, “What should we do? General, we can defeat the Sea Dragons, right?”

Luo Ying looked at Luo Luo and then smiled faintly, “Of course we can defeat the Sea Dragons. Don’t worry about it. This time, the Sea Dragons just got some helpers. If mister Zhao Hai can help us hold them off for a while, then we can get the strength to wipe them out in one go.”

Luo Ying was just saying this to comfort Luo Luo. However, what she said also held some truth. The Mermaid family had ruled the Fishman Race for a very long time, and from that alone, their background was quite strong. The reason why the Mermaids became like this was because they had been caught off guard. As long as the Mermaids had time, and were able to gather their strength, then they would be able to deal with the Sea Dragons. It was just that the Mermaids would still have to pay a heavy price.

When Luo Luo heard Luo Ying, she couldn’t help but feel relaxed. Seeing Luo Luo’s appearance, Luo Ying couldn’t help but faintly smile. She couldn’t blame Luo Luo, after all, she was still young and still hadn’t seen the big world. She hasn’t even gone to a real battlefield. Therefore, this response from Luo Luo was quite normal.

At this time, Dashan arrived, he gave a salute to Luo Ying and said, “General, Mister Zhao Hai has processed the corpses. Currently, he is inside his blade scale whale, resting.”

Luo Ying nodded, then she turned to Luo Luo and said, “How is the space inside the Blade Scale Whale? If it isn’t any good, I can arrange a room for mister Zhao Hai to rest here.”

Luo Luo smiled and said, “General, you don’t know, but the inside of the blade scale whale is very comfortable. It had several rooms in it, a living room, bathroom, and even a place where one can see outside. It was a great place.”

As soon as she heard Luo Luo, Luo Ying became surprised. She looked at Luo Luo and said, “Really? It seems like the level of mister’s dark magic isn’t low.”

Luo Luo nodded and said, “Mister is very strong. His wives aren’t simple either. I can see that mister places great importance to his wives’ opinion whenever they discuss something. Moreover, their relationship is very good. Mister’s wives are very harmonious with each other. They’ve become friends with our sisters back at mermaid island as well.”

Chapter 624: You Take Command

Luo Ying nodded and said, “No matter what, mister is our ally. Dashan, Luo Luo, you have the most contact with mister. Make sure to listen to anything that he wants. Make sure that you satisfy his needs.”

When Luo Luo heard Luo Ying, she immediately responded, “General, I seem to remember something. Mister Zhao Hai wanted to collect unique beasts and plants as a hobby. Whenever he sees something along the way, he would stop and collect them alive. General, I think we should get some beasts and plants for mister, or maybe something else that is unique, what do you think?”

Luo Ying gawked, “So mister has a hobby like that. Is mister an Alchemist or a Refining Master? That doesn’t matter, I’ll have someone go and pay attention to this. Right, I have some sea dragon beads on hand. Although Mister is quite strong, it would be more convenient for him if he had these beads.”

Luo Luo nodded. Then Luo Ying turned to Dashan and said, “Dashan, what is the casualty count? Are we doing well?”

Dashan nodded and said, “The situation is good. Enemy casualties number over 800 thousand while our deaths are less than 300 hundred thousand. Six hundred thousand of those enemy casualties were due to Mister Zhao Hai’s undead”

Luo Ying knit her brows and said, “Our casualties are still more than the enemy. The Sea Dragons have gathered a lot of powerful warriors all these years, we’re much worse in terms of fighting prowess. But it was fortunate that we had more reinforcements coming soon.”

Dashan nodded and said, “It’s also good that mister has managed to gather more undead. If the enemy attacks tomorrow, then mister would gain even more undead, which would be beneficial for us. You’ve seen how strong those undead were from the earlier fight, they’re quite formidable.”

Luo Ying nodded and said, “However, I’m afraid that the Sea Dragons might have a Light Mage or Light Dragon among them. Those would bring us some trouble.What we need to do right now is to keep the enemy from advancing beyond this place. We’ll wait for more reinforcements to arrive and then grind the enemy bit by bit before we can claim victory in the end.”

Dashan and Luo Luo nodded. Luo Ying felt some tiredness as she said, “Alright, let’s go rest. I think the Sea Dragons wouldn’t make another attack today.” The two nodded before turning around and leaving.

Then Zhao Hai turned the monitor off. Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, it seems like they had finally recognized your strength. Are you happy?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “What does being recognized really do? If I weren’t afraid of exposing my secrets, then I would’ve already extinguished the Sea Dragons.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “But this is also good, they are now going to look for good things for Big Brother Hai. Brother Hai, how about asking for an Azure Dragon Snail? That thing is very good.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I really don’t envy the snail, what I want is their water refining technique. If there’s a chance, I would want to learn how they do it. It’s quite an amazing invention.”

Megan nodded and said, “Well, let’s not talk about that. Elder Brother Hai, how about we look at the battle earlier, I want to see it clearly.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he had Cai’er replay the fight from earlier. Then they analyzed it bit by bit. But when it comes to battles, it seems like Megan and Lizzy were much better than him.

After analyzing the battle, Zhao Hai and the others reckoned that he can still kill about 100 thousand more if there was good strategy involved.

After looking at the battle, Zhao Hai relaxed. Then Zhao Hai looked at Megan and Lizzy and said, “Alright, you two are indeed good at these things. I think we can talk to General Luo Ying tomorrow and ask for permission to do an attack using our undead. At that time, I can have the two of you be the commander. We’ll take the battle to the Sea Dragons while finding out who their helpers were. What do you think?”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, do you really want us to command the undead? What if we don’t do a good job?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your worries are unnecessary. No commander starts off good. Moreover, how many undead do we have? And they’re quite strong as well. Don’t forget, the 500 thousand undead that we used earlier are all doing fine. When we go to the Space, I’ll have the two of you command a unit so that you can get familiar with them during battles. Later on, whether it be the Gods or the Demons, war would be inevitable. Me and Laura cannot take command, so we’ll be leaving that matter off to you two.”

When Lizzy and Megan heard Zhao Hai, they immediately understood what he was trying to say. Zhao Hai making them command the undead was just a preparation for the war in the future. They also understood that the fight against the Gods and the Demons would be more difficult than this one. And at the same time, their side really needed good commanders in order to maximize their fighting potential.

After thinking about this, Lizzy and Megan nodded and said ,”Alright, we’ll listen to Brother Hai. We’ll be the ones dealing with the Sea Dragons tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai let out a long breath and said, “We need to make sure to take good care of ourselves. The most important thing is to prepare to receive the Gods and Demons. These two would be hard to deal with. When they appear in the continent, then we would have no other choice but to fight.”

The others didn’t speak. The Gods and Demons were like two mountains that were weighing down on their shoulders, making it hard for them to breath. Just like Zhao Hai said, they needed to use all of their energy to prepare themselves in dealing with those two.

They rested for the whole day, and on the next morning after having breakfast, Luo Luo arrived in front of the blade scale whale. Zhao Hai immediately invited her in. When Luo Luo entered the whale, she handed the dragon beads over to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, take these. The general had me give this to you. Later, you can place it on your body so that you don’t need to use magic in repelling the water.”

Zhao Hai received the dragon beads and carefully looked at it, then he nodded and said, “Alright, I was just about to visit the General. I’ll go give my thanks when I see her. Let’s go.”

Luo Luo nodded and then she asked, “What does mister want to ask the general?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s about the war. We had always been on the defensive side, we’re too passive. I want to take the fight to the Sea Dragons. I want to ask for the general’s approval so that I can go and attack them.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Luo Luo couldn’t help but gawk. She looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister wants to attack the Sea Dragons?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right, I want to see how good those Sea Dragons are.” Then he came out of the blade scale whale and stepped on the back of a turtle before heading towards the azure dragon snail.

Luo Luo looked surprised at Zhao Hai. She didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would want to attack. Yesterday, she heard that the general wanted them to hold the attacks off as long as they can while grinding the Sea Dragons bit by bit. But Zhao Hai’s request was in direct opposition to the general’s plan.

While she was thinking about this, they had finally arrived at the snail’s hall. Seeing Zhao Hai come, Luo Ying immediately said, “Mister, I think the Sea Dragons wouldn’t attack today. You can use the time to take a good rest.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I came here today about this matter. I’m here to ask the general’s permission. I want to attack the Sea Dragons.”

Luo Ying stared, then she knit her brows and said, “Mister, we can just wait for the Sea Dragons here. It’s too risky to attack them.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “General, you said that it was possible for the Sea Dragons to have received help from the Humans and Dragons. If this is really the case, then it wouldn’t be good for us to keep this defensive war. I want to use the undead in order to chip away some of the enemy’s strength. Moreover, I also want to see who their helpers are.”

Luo Ying still refused, “Mister, if the Sea Dragons had help from the continent, then perhaps they would use a Light Mage to deal with you.”

Zhao Hai actually laughed and said, “General, you don’t need to worry. I’ve been at odds with the Radiant Church for a long time. If Light magic really did affect me, then I would’ve already died in their hands. Also, I would only be using my undead in this attack, so we wouldn’t have any casualties. If we wait for them to come to us, then we would certainly suffer some losses. I think it would be better for us if I were to take the initiative and bring the battle to them.”

When Luo Ying heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but think deeply. Mermaids treat the Fishmen like their own family. If they waited for the enemy to attack them, then it was inevitable that deaths would occur. And losing people from your own side doesn’t give anyone a good feeling. Because of this, Luo Ying began to be moved by Zhao Hai’s proposal.

Luo Ying nodded and said, “Alright, then I won’t stop mister. However, Mister should do his best in order to protect your own safety. How about this, I’ll have Dashan and a group of warriors accompany you. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “General, although Captain Dashan is formidable, they don’t know how to fight along with the undead. Even if they do come with me, they won’t be able to offer any help. The general doesn’t need to worry about me, after all, I don’t have any plans to die just yet. There’s no need to have someone protect me. In any case, I’ll always be in the back, commanding the undead. If things go sour, I can just retreat.”

Luo Ying was unable to refute Zhao Hai’s statement, so she just nodded and said, “Then I can only ask mister to be careful. I’ll be waiting for mister’s good news. Right, if mister acquires some dragon beads, all of them shall belong to you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The general has my utmost gratitude. Alright then, this Zhao Hai would be taking his leave.” Then he gave Luo Ying a salute before turning around to leave.

Chapter 625: Such a Character!

About thirty nautical miles away from the Mermaid’s defensive line was a large gathering of Fishmen. These Fishmen looked much stronger than those from the Mermaid clan’s army. Among them were people from the Electric Eel tribe and the Shark tribe. This was the large camp of the Sea Dragons.

The Fishmen didn’t have the custom of constructing camps. So these large gathering, the entire camp, was actually situated in a very huge coral reef. But the reef looked very peculiar, its form was like a curled up Sea Dragon.

The Sea Dragons had some differences compared to the other Dragons, perhaps it was to allow them to better survive at sea. Other Dragons were big bellied lizards with a pair of wings. But the Sea Dragons were different, they looked like sea snakes with four feet, and on those feet were some white bristles, they also had a fin on their tails. This form suited them the most in swimming underwater. This coral reef looked exactly like huge slumbering Sea Dragon.

This giant coral reef occupied a very large area, which was a testament to how large it was. But what is even more surprising was the fact that it was evident that this coral reef was not from here. One could see that it was moved to this location.

In front of this reef were countless ropes, which were made out of high level magic beast leather. These ropes were connected to large magic beasts. It was obvious that this huge piece of coral was dragged here by those magic beasts.

The coral reef seemed to be surrounded by a huge blue bubble. One could hardly see a drop of water inside the reef. From time to time, one could see some warriors coming in and out of the structure.

Another amazing thing was that the warriors who were on patrol were all humanoid. They wore fish scales armor and dragon helmets on their heads. Their hands seem to be naked but one could see that it was covered in some sort of metal glove. The nails on the glove showed that it had quite an attacking capability.

These warriors who had gone to patrol were Sea Dragons. Dragons aren’t like any other magic beast. Even if other magic beasts were to become 9th rank, the most they can do was change the size of their body, it was impossible for them to change their shape. On the other hand, when Dragons become 8th rank in their adulthood, they would immediately have the ability to change into humanoid figures. This was an advantage that Dragons had.

And this coral reef was the home of the Sea Dragons, the Dragon Palace!

The Sea Dragons lived in this palace, but they usually don’t make the palace move around. It was because every time the palace gets moved, it would need at least 100 thousand strong marine magic beasts. And finding those beasts wasn’t an easy task.

This coral reef has been transformed by the Sea Dragons through the years. The inside of it had become like palace, with pearls and crystals everywhere. It was extraordinarily attractive, even more attractive than Mermaid Island’s palace.

Sitting inside the Dragon Palace’s Great Hall were four people, two of them wore blue robes, robes that seemed to be made out of magic beast skin. The two weren’t very tall, about 1.8 meters high. Their bodies were well-proportioned, they had dark blue hair as well as dark blue eyes. Their skins were white and their appearance seemed to be about 40 years old. They were revealing the aura of mature men, looking very handsome and unique.

Another man wore a long gold robe, he had a head full of beard, and was about 2.5 meters tall. He had long golden hair and if one looks closely into it, one could see a pair of sharp horns poking through.

The last man looked very ordinary, he wore a red mage’s robe while having a Magic Staff in one hand. He had short but still attractive beard, and had a very holy expression on his face. If a Human were to see this person, then their first impression would be that this person was a Light Mage.

At this time, the younger of the two blue robed people opened his mouth and said, “Patriarch, Envoy, Bishop, I can assure you that our army has been attacked by undead. And their numbers were quite large as well, about 500 thousand undead.”

The other blue robed person, who seemed to be the Sea Dragon Patriarch, said, “Illac, do you understand what 500 thousand undead meant? How many Dark Mages would need to command it? Moreover, you’re saying that these undead were also quite strong, are you really sure that it was undead?”

Illac nodded and said, “Patriarch, I am telling the truth. After we got caught off-guard by the enemy’s Falling Stone Formation, we began to retreat. But at that time, large quantities of undead suddenly appeared around us. The fighting strength of these undead were quite strong. If we haven’t recovered immediately, we might have suffered more losses.”

When Illac’s voice fell, the golden robed man couldn’t help but knit his brows and said, “How is that possible? Wasn’t there supposed to be no contact between the Mermaids and the Humans? Then how come there were Dark Mages present? Moreover, 500 thousand undead wasn’t something that one or two Dark Mages can summon. Were you able to see how many Dark Mages were present?”

The Red Robed Light Mage opened his mouth and with a serious tone, he said, “It’s not necessary to have a lot of Dark Mages in order to summon 500 thousand undead. Envoy Ao Ke, I know of a certain Human Dark Mage. He is able to summon 500 thousand undead by himself, maybe even more.”

Envoy Ao Ke, Illac, and the Sea Dragon Patriarch’s faces changed, these three looked at the red robed Light Mage, then Ao Ke said, “Bishop Joshua, are you telling the truth? Does the Human Race have such a character? Why haven’t you dealt with him yet?”

This Joshua was unexpectedly a Radiant Church’s red robed Archbishop. However, this golden robed Ao Ke had a much bigger background. He is of the Dragon Race and was the current Dragon Patriarch’s younger brother, but only a half-brother.

The birth of Dragons is very difficult, but they were still quite fertile. A peculiar thing about them was that they can more successfully procreate with those that wasn’t of their own race. Although there were still some Pure Dragon births here and there, their numbers were still inferior to those who were born between a Dragon and of an inferior race.

In addition to giving birth to a Light Dragon because of his wife, Ao Ke’s father was also able to give birth to him with a Metal Dragon. However, since Dragon law states that only Light Dragons can become Patriarchs, Ao Ke’s chances of leading his race has become impossible. Although Ao Ke had both the advantages of being a Light Dragon and a Metal Dragon, he still had to give up the position to his brother. However, his status in the Dragon Race was still quite high. He was even entrusted with the responsibility of being the Envoy of the Dragon Race in this battle between the inferior Sea Dragon Race and the Mermaid Clan.

As soon as Joshua heard Ao Ke, he nodded, and with a heavy expression he said, “Patriarch Alex, General Illac, Envoy Ao Ke, our Human Race did have such a Dark Mage. Moreover, he had become our church’s archenemy. To be honest, at this point, we are very willing to pay any price in order to eliminate him. But this person is very difficult to deal with, causing our Radiant Church to lose repeatedly by his hand. The reason why the Radiant Church has been pushed into a corner in the continent was partly due to this man. You might not know but this person is quite famous in the Human lands. He’s the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, the son-in-law of the Emperor of the most powerful nation, the son-in-law of the Dark Mage Alliance’s Calci Family, the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince, as well as being a very big merchant. He is also an extremely formidable Dark Mage, one time, he had turned the Aksu Empire’s 600 thousand troop navy into his undead in just one night. For him, controlling 500 thousand undead wouldn’t be very hard.”

The Sea Dragon Patriarch Alex was dumbfounded upon hearing Joshua’s words. He didn’t think that such a character had popped up in the Human Race. After some time, Alex recovered and said, “I’ve got some word some time ago that the Fishman Race has been having secret transactions with Humans, maybe it’s with this Buda Clan that Bishop meant? But Bishop Joshua, haven’t you thought of a way to eliminate him yet?”

Joshua forced a smile and said, “This Buda Clan Patriarch is named Zhao Hai. He’s extremely powerful, we have thought of eliminating him for a long time. In the beginning, we weren’t aware of his strength, which cost us five white robed bishops and 18 knight guards. But in the end, the only thing we can do was drive him off to the Prairie. But when he came back, his power has greatly increased. After that, we had made continuous efforts in eliminating him, but all ended up in failure. The most recent one involved us sending forth four 9th rank experts and had them use Life Combustion in order to eliminate him. But for some reason, he was still able to successfully escape. Later on, in the war between the Beastmen and Humans, our plans had somehow become known to the Beastmen. We suspect that this Zhao Hai had something to do with it, but we had no proof. Later on, our Church haven’t had the chance to muster up the force that would deal with him. Patriarch Alex, I think this secret trade was established by Zhao Hai. This Zhao Hai had a peculiar personality that made him have a good relationship with other races. I’ve also heard about him being in good terms with the Dwarves. Based on that, it wouldn’t be strange for him to have a connection with the Fishman Race.”

Alex and the others couldn’t help but breathe in cold air. Although they didn’t know how formidable this Life Combustion that Joshua told them was, they estimated how strong it would be judging by the fact that it used the life of four 9th rank experts. For Zhao Hai to survive this attack was quite a scary thing to think about!

Chapter 626: Devil Scorpion

Joshua looked at the expressions of those present and couldn’t help but smile bitterly, “We had underestimated Zhao Hai from the start. Now that he has established his name in the continent, it would be close to impossible for us to deal with him. And since the situation of the Church isn’t very good, it would take us some time in order to make a proper move.”

Ao Ke and the others recovered and couldn’t help but breathe in some cold air. But Ao Ke’s eyes suddenly lit up as he said, “If the one we’re facing is indeed Zhao Hai, then the situation would be good for us. Although you don’t have a way of dealing with him in the continent, we are currently in the sea. Zhao Hai’s strength should be limited here, we can use this opportunity to kill him, essentially removing a huge problem of yours while at the same time removing a big helper of the Mermaid clan.”

Upon hearing Envoy Ao Ke, the eyes of Joshua and Alex couldn’t help but turn bright. This was good, even if it was difficult to deal with Zhao Hai in the continent, one shouldn’t forget that they are currently in the ocean. One of the strongest entities here were the Sea Dragons. If they can remove Zhao Hai, then they would be removing a huge problem in their plan.

After thinking about this, the group couldn’t help but get restless. Alex looked at Illac and said, “Illac, did you say that Zhao Hai’s undead were strong? Did you happen to see Zhao Hai? He shouldn’t be too far away from his undead, right?”

Illac shook his head and said, “Patriarch, this one hasn’t seen him. At that time, the situation had gone hectic, I simply didn’t have the chance to look for his shadow.”

Alex nodded and said, “When you attack tomorrow, you must pay attention to any Dark Mages or even Zhao Hai among the Mermaid army. If we become sure that it is Zhao Hai, then we’ll do our best in order to kill him. Saving the plans of the Gods from being disrupted all the time.”

Illac nodded, then Alex turned to Joshua and said, “Bishop Joshua, do you have a portrait of Zhao Hai? We don’t want Illac to mistake him for another person.”

Joshua nodded and said, “Of course, this Zhao Hai is the Church’s number one enemy. It would be impossible for me to not have a portrait of him.” Then he turned his hand before a portrait appeared. The portrait was draw masterfully, showing Zhao Hai’s figure as well as his face. Zhao Hai was holding a magic staff on one hand while also wearing a black robe on his body. His face was colored so well that the picture looked to be alive. But Zhao Hai didn’t have much expression on his face, probably due to the bias the artist had against him.

But when they saw the portrait, Alex and the others couldn’t help but gawk. They didn’t expect that this formidable Zhao Hai that Joshua was talking about to be quite young. They were expecting a skeleton looking Dark Mage, not an ordinary healthy young man.”

The group looked at Joshua, their expression probably saying, “Did you take the wrong thing out?”

When Joshua looked at their expression, he couldn’t help but force a smile and said, “Rest assured, I didn’t take the wrong thing out. This is indeed Zhao Hai, aged about 20 years old and was just recently married. Don’t be fooled by his ordinary looks, his methods are extremely brilliant. If we’re really facing him, then General Illac would need to be careful.”

Alex nodded, then he turned to Illac and said, “Illac, take this portrait with you so that you can clearly identify this guy. If it is really him, don’t go and attack him immediately. Come back and tell us first so that we can concentrate our efforts and destroy him in one go.” Illac nodded, then he took the portrait before turning back and leaving.

After Illac left, Alex turned to Joshua and Ao Ke and said, “Bishop, Envoy, if we prove that it is Zhao Hai, I would have to ask for help from the two of you so that we can be more certain of eliminating him. You should know that this fellow is a Dark Mage, and both of you can do light magic. And since he is fighting underwater, he shouldn’t be able to escape if our three sides deal with him simultaneously.”

Ao Ke nodded and said, “Patriarch Alex, rest assured, we aren’t just here to witness the fun. As long as we confirm that it is Zhao Hai, then we would immediately make our move.”

Joshua nodded as well, “Right, we’re not here to just be an audience. If we can really kill Zhai Hai here, then even if this Joshua loses his life, I would still do it in the name of the Radiant God.”

Alex nodded and said, “Good, good, we’re fortunate that the two of you are here. “The army had just experienced a huge battle, so they would need to take a day off. Tomorrow, Illac would attack once again while looking for this Zhao Hai.”

Ao Ke and Joshua were also people who can command troops. So the two knew about the impact their recent losses would have to the troops. Therefore, neither of them opposed to it.

The next day, after Alex and the others had their breakfast and were preparing to head into battle, someone suddenly sent a message. A large amount of undead were attacking them.

Alex and the others gawked, then Alex immediately gave the Sea Dragon a command, “Go and find General Illac.” The Sea Dragon nodded before turning around to leave.

Alex turns to Ao Ke and Joshua, he smiled faintly and said, “Just as we are about to look for him, he suddenly came. I want to see if this person is really Zhao Hai.”

Ao Ke coldly snorted and said, “If this is really Zhao Hai, then he’s being extremely arrogant. For a Human to dare attack the Sea Dragons in the ocean on his own is a very impatient move.”

But Joshua actually frowned and said, “We still need to be careful. This Zhao Hai is not good to deal with.”

Ao Ke couldn’t help but be unconcerned. After seeing Zhao Hai’s portrait, he had begun to form doubts about Joshua’s words. In his opinion, a 20 year old young man wouldn’t have much abilities. Ao Ke believed that since the Radiant Church weren’t able to deal with him, they chose to exaggerate his qualities in order to same them some face.

However, since Ao Ke was Joshua’s ally, he didn’t want to say anything that would embarrass the other part. So he just nodded and didn’t say anything. At this time, Illac had walked in from outside and then gave a salute to those present.

Alex nodded at Illac’s salute and then said, “Illac, someone just sent word that undead creatures were heading towards us. I suspect that this Zhao Hai is coming. Go and organize the troops for defense. Remember, don’t counter attack. Even if we lose some people, the important thing is confirming if it is really Zhao Hai.” Illac nodded, then he turned around to leave.

Alex turned to Joshua and Ao Ke and said, “Bishop, Envoy, let’s go take a look at this Zhao Hai.” The two nodded before the group headed outside.

Zhao Hai was currently inside the blade scale whales body. In front of him was the monitor and on his side were Laura and the others. Megan and Lizzy were especially anxious at this time.

Zhao Hai wasn’t planning to handle his affairs in a low key this time. He released 1 million undead, comprised of both magic beasts and Fishmen. They were currently in a cube formation as it headed towards the Sea Dragon camp.

The reason why Lizzy and Megan were anxious was because Zhao Hai had made the two of them the commanders of this attack. The calculations and strategies all came from Lizzy and Megan, so it wasn’t strange for them to be quite nervous.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and couldn’t help but smile, “It’s going to be fine, no need to be nervous. Even if we get defeated, our losses only comprised of undead. Don’t be afraid of anything and just boldly try out everything. You must learn how to command an army attack.”

When Lizzy and Megan heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but let out a long breath. What Zhao Hai said was correct, they weren’t commanding humans this time, but undead. Even if these undead were to get ‘defeated’, they weren’t essentially dead. Ninth rank undead couldn’t easily die, all they were doing was going back to the Space.

After thinking about this, they immediately calmed down. Then their expressions turned to excitement as the looked at the monitor. Their change made Zhao Hai and the others smile.

The cubic formation advanced slowly. At the same time, a cubic formation also appeared on the side of the Sea Dragon camp. Zhao Hai and the others found out that the Fishmen really liked this formation, maybe because it was very simple.

The two great formations slowly approached each other. Lizzy then turned to Megan and said, “Megan, you go first.”

Megan didn’t become polite, she nodded and said, “Alright. I’ve thought of quite a lot of formations yesterday. I want to try their prowess this time. I’ll go with the Devil Scorpion first. Brother Hai, this formation has a thick center while having two extended wings on each side. And as the battle goes on, the rear army would sprang up from above, attacking the enemy in that direction. This formation looks just like a giant scorpion.” Then Megan used her hand to move the monitor. Zhao Hai also had Cai’er help her with this. The image that Megan described can be fully described on the monitor.

Megan’s Devil Scorpion formation did indeed look like a giant scorpion. The Center army has two wings on each side that would attack the enemy in two fronts. At the same time the Rear Army was also being the scorpion’s tail, slowly going up, preparing to attack the opposite party from above.

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “Right, what you described is very clear.” Then he waved his hand, making the undead creatures move, following the directions that Megan just described.

Megan and Lizzy were going to experiment on the idea that they had come up. They weren’t like the Fishmen who already had their cubic formation, cone formation, or their whirlpool formation. For the fishmen, these basic formations were the ones that would express their potential the most.

And also, experimenting on new formations was something that would take a toll on soldiers. Soldiers much achieve near perfect movements in order to follow the idea of their commander. What their commander wants to do, they would need to do it, there was no room for any mistakes.

Chapter 627: Poisonous Scorpion Tail

Achieving this formation wasn’t easy, even the world’s most disciplined army would still have problems executing it. After all, ideas couldn’t be easily transferred to commands and movements. Therefore, any formation would need to be thought through and drilled properly before being executed in the battlefield. Formations like the cubic formation, whirlpool formation, cone formation, and others have been drilled by the Fishmen for lots and lots of years.

However, Zhao Hai’s situation was quite special. What he commanded were undead, which functioned basically like blocks. What you want them to do would be done by them. Dark Mages might have problems in doing this, but Zhao Hai had the Space to assist him. He becomes a perfect commander to a perfectly functional army with all these points in place.

Just as Megan finished describing her formation and wanted him to employ it, Zhao Hai immediately arranged for his army to execute the formation. Before long, the entire army looked like a giant scorpion facing against a large Rubik’s cube.

Illac was currently in the core of the cube. When he saw the undead going against his army, his expression couldn’t help but turn heavy. He immediately issued a command, making the cube constantly rotate.

But at this time, Illac suddenly discovered that the formation of the opposite party has changed. The center army turned still as two wings suddenly came out of the undead formation. Upon witnessing this sight, Illac’s face changed, he didn’t expect that the other party would have the ability to command the undead to this degree.

Illac immediately said, “Face the enemy with a cone formation, make sure to defend against those two outward wings.” Illac was currently inside a giant shell covered by numerous thorns, as though it was a huge sea urchin. But the shell was transparent while there weren’t any water inside, evidently due to the sea dragon bead. There were some furniture inside as well, making it Illac’s command center.

Along with his order, the cube immediately changed its shape. The front of the cube that was slowly rotating started to extend out front and straight towards Zhao Hai’s center army.  However, the left and right wings didn’t budge, they had held off the enemy attack quite successfully.

However, Illac was completely unaware that Zhao  Hai’s rear army, the scorpion’s tail, had started to attack from above.

In the war between Fishmen, very few troops chose to get too close to the surface of the sea in order to attack the enemy. This was because that position exposed them to attacks from aerial magic beasts. And since they were accustomed to the bottom of the sea, their eyes wouldn’t be able to survive the glare. If they approach the surface, it might hurt their eyes, blinding them in the process. Therefore, it wasn’t common for any Fishman to attack from above.

It was because of this that Illac managed to eat a huge loss. Just as his cone formation started, Megan turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, Use the wings to make two cone formations and make it break through their defense.” Zhao Hai nodded and then had the undead move according to Megan’s method.

Illac stared at Zhao Hai’s move, at the same time, his ears had also been open, listening to the messages from the front regarding the current situation. Illac’s expression couldn’t help but turn heavy, he really wasn’t expecting the other party’s capacity to command the undead to be this degree. In their past encounter, he thought that the other party can only command his undead to rush in and fight, he didn’t expect that the Dark Mage was able to make a formation such as this. Even Fishmen would have a hard time executing such a maneuver, but the other party had actually done it.

However, Illca can’t think about it for too long. The front of his army has finally gotten in contact with the other party. As his cone formation clashed with the other party’s cone formation, blood immediately came out. At the same time, the two wings of the opposite party started to also form a cone formation as it went towards the Sea Dragon Army.

Illac immediately ordered two armies to make a whirlpool formation to meet the opposing cone formations. But his reaction was still a bit late, after all, he was still focused on encountering the center army and wasn’t able to see the side armies. But fortunately, although late, his side armies still managed to block the approaching cone formations, which made Illac’s army fall into full defensive mode.

One could say that Illac’s response was correct, even if he was late in meeting the side armies, he still managed to block both of them as well as Zhao Hai’s center army.

But at this moment, the scorpion tail of Megan’s formation had arrived. It dived down from above and attacked the top of Illac’s cube formation.

The people at the top discovered the tail too late, so when word got sent to Illac, the division commanders at the top already met with the approaching army. But since there was no unified command, the top still haven’t done a whirlpool formation, they just met the scorpion tail as they were. And under Megan’s request, Zhao Hai had also turned the tail into a cone formation, acting like a drill as it barrelled towards the center of the cube formation.

When Illac heard the news from the top formations, he felt that his head has been hit by a stick as his vision saw stars. But since he was a competent general, he immediately took action. At this point, the enemy had already broken through the first layer of the formation. So Illac immediately sent word for the second and third layer to change into a whirlpool in order to block the enemy attack.

Illac was fortunate that the subordinates on those layers were members of warring tribes, so their response was very quick. After the first layer was broken through, the second and third layer also started to slowly rotate.

Illac knew since the first layer was already broken through, the second layer also wouldn’t be able to block in time. The whirlpool formation was quite strong, however, it would also need time to be set up. So Illac plans to have the second layer stall for time, blocking the scorpion tail just in time for the third layer to get its whirlpool formation fully operational.

Zhao Hai and the others were inside the Blade Scale Whale, paying attention to the response of the other party. At this time, Megan couldn’t help but sigh and said, “It looks like I’m only up to this point. I didn’t think that the other party would have such quick response. But the experimental formation still turned out good. At the very least, we have proven that its attacking might is quite strong.”

Zhao Hai and the others nodded. Just from this clash, the other party was already placed on their back foot. Especially during the attack of the scorpion tail, it had actually punctured through two layers of the other party’s formation. It was indeed a very good result.

Megan turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, my trial for the Devil Scorpion is done. You can have them draw back and have Lizzy give it a go.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright”. Then he waved his hand, making the three extending armies retreat back while the center army slowly backed out.

Illac’s face turned ugly when he heard about the report. Although the people at the top managed to block the opponent’s attack, the losses that they suffered wasn’t small. At the same time, he was also nearly defeated, this made Illac very angry.

At this time, the opponent army suddenly retreated slowly, making Illac stare. But he immediately ordered all of his men to keep their position and not chase after the foe. He was afraid that this might be another of those plans of the opposite party. So Illac immediately made his cone formation turn back.

Upon withdrawing, Adam immediately surveyed each division. Then he tallied their losses while also paying close attention to the actions of Zhao Hai’s group.

Adam saw that the core of the enemy was also in the middle of the cubic formation, just like the Fishmen. In the middle of the formation was a single Blade Scale Whale. But this whale was very different compared to the other undead. This Blade Scale Whale wasn’t comprised of only skin and bones. Adam reckons that the Dark Mage was inside this Blade Scale Whale. This was because he had been looking at the cubic formation for a long time and couldn’t find any other place for the opposite party to hide from. And it would be impossible for the mermaids to allow this commander to be exposed to the outside, so it was natural for this Dark Mage to be inside the great cubic formation.

Adam’s vision focused on the out of the ordinary Blade Scale Whale. And at this time, Zhao Hai was also doing the same, focusing his sight towards the big urchin in the middle of the other party’s formation. His human eyesight seemingly able to pierce into the far distance.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s cubic formation had recombined. Zhao Hai calculated his losses and found out that more than 50 thousand undead has retreated into the Space. Such a short encounter actually made them lose that much, this was beyond what Zhao Hai was expecting.

However, Zhao Hao also found out that the other party had lost significantly more people compared to him. One must know that from the start of the attack to the present, only one hour has passed by. And in this one hour, the other party had already lost tens of thousands of people. This casualty count was very big.

But Zhao Hai didn’t become merciful, he knew that if his heart were to turn soft, the losses due to this war would escalate even more. So he turned to Lizzy and said, “Lizzy, it’s your turn. How do you want to attack?”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “I also want to try out a formation. I have given this formation the name of Four Armed Demon!”

Chapter 628: Four Armed Demon

Zhao Hai said, “Four Armed Demon? That sounds scary. Tell me how you want to arrange it.”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “Big Brother Hai, did you manage to see the weakness of the opposite party’s cube formation? It actually has a weak point.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Weak point? What weak point? How could something that the Fishmen had used for so many years have flaws? So tell me, what is it?”

Lizzy smiled faintly, then she waved at the screen, enlarging the Sea Dragon’s cubic formation. After looking at the formation, Lizzy said, “Big Brother Hai, look at this, although the formation looks very secure and compact, it still had one shortcoming. When this formation makes a move, the are edges in the back that almost always stayed motionless!”

Zhao Hai had always felt that there was something off with this formation, but he wasn’t able to know the difference. But now that Lizzy reminded him, Zhao Hai finally saw it. Although the formation looked like a rubik’s cube, it functioned much more like a square. The square was able to rotate but the four back edges always stayed in place. Even when the top face rotated, they still stayed completely still. Although some Fishmen were on those faces, they seem to be isolated from the rest of the cube and weren’t participating in the fight.

When the group heard Lizzy, their eyes couldn’t help but light up. Lizzy looked at their expressions and faintly smiled, “This point looks like nothing, but it was actually a point of importance. Once you break those four edges, the cube would break. So I designed this Four Armed Demon formation in order to deal with that weakness. The center army would be attracting the attention of the enemy commander. And when the opportune moment comes, four arms would make their move and target those weak spots!”

While talking, Lizzy drew the image of her formation on the monitor. The formation looks like a four armed man that would hug up the enemy’s cube box. And his four arms would be grasping the back edges of the opponent’s formation, effectively breaking it apart.

Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but look at Lizzy in a new light. The way Lizzy and Megan attacked were very different. Megan’s attack emphasized on good attack and battle maneuvers, going head to head with the opponent’s formation. But Lizzy actually looks for weaknesses in the enemy’s formation and capitalizing on that knowledge to make a formation that would be able to break the enemy’s formation.

If Megan were to be described as open and aboveboard, like a Warrior wanting a duel, overthrowing any ideas of underhanded tricks, Lizzy would be like a strong assassin, always actively looking for weaknesses in the enemy that she can exploit.

Lizzy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “So Big Brother Hai, is it possible?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “How could it not be possible? Look at this.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as the cube of undead advanced. While it was advancing, some undead magic beasts slowly crawled and formed four distinct armies on the edges of the army, ready to launch an attack at any time. Other places of the formation didn’t change in order to not attract Illac’s attention.

But this time, Illac was already being very careful. Zhao Hai’s attack managed to make him focus on his next movement. It doesn’t matter if the other party was Zhao Hai or not, but their command of undead made Illac startled. Because of this, even if Zhao Hai kept his cube formation as it advanced, Illac didn’t dare to lower his guard. Moreover, he was prepared for any change that might suddenly spring out.

Zhao Hai pushed forward slowly, carefully making sure that nothing would be noticed on his formation. Zhao Hai knew that for Lizzy’s formation to be successful, preliminary moves needed to be taken into consideration. Only when the enemy’s attention gets focused on the center army would the four arms be allowed to make their move.

Illac was somewhat confused at Zhao Hai’s slowly approaching army. He didn’t understand where the other party’s awesome formations went. If they had used a formation before, then they should have a formation for this time, that was for sure.

However, do they really want to attack like this? Illac didn’t know what to think, therefore, he sent an order to stand by, preparing for any changes that might occur. His eyes were completely stuck at the other party’s army, looking for signs of any changes in the formation.

Seeing the other party’s reaction, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly and said, “We should employ multiple cone formations in order to attract the attention of the opposite army, then we’ll go attack the four edges. Lizzy, what do you think?”

Lizzy nodded and said, “Alright, the most important thing about my formation is the attack on the four edges. If we lost this chance, then the other party might quickly come up with a solution. After all, the enemy is an experienced general.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand as his cube formation changed into small cone formations. Then it slowly advanced towards the other army.

After seeing this move, Illac couldn’t help but let out a long breath. As long as it’s not those special formations, then he would have means to deal with it.

However, Illac still didn’t treat this matter lightly. Rather, he was currently focusing on his defense. He couldn’t risk making a wrong move at this time. The tail of the Demon Scorpion was still fresh inside his mind.

Before long, the cone formation finally clashed with the opposing army. Everything seemed to be quite normal, there were not special things happening. This made it easier for Illac to command his army, everyone was perfectly following his commands.

In this fight between Zhao Hai and Illac, there was almost close to no long-ranged attacks. Zhao Hai didn’t use any since he didn’t want Illac to know that his undead were able to use long-ranged attacks. Illac didn’t use any long-ranged attacks either because he knew how ineffective those would be against the undead. Unless these undead were hit in their vital points, they could still continue on and attack.

Hitting these undead with long-ranged attacks wasn’t easy. And most importantly, whether it be Fishmen or magic beasts, once they use magic, they would appear weak for a short time. Doing these against close-combat undead was akin to courting death. Because of this, Illac chose to refrain from using any long-ranged attacks. Both sides were using melee in order to draw losses from each other.

Zhao Hai had a lot of cone formations in his attack, but Illac managed to block all of them while using the conventional whirlpool maneuvers. But Illac didn’t use small whirlpools, he was using a big whirlpool in order to maximize the amount of defensive power that he can exhibit against these cone formations. At the same time, this would also slowly dull the tips of the enemy’s cone formations.

This whirlpool formation was deemed to be the most defensively powerful formation of the Fishmen. Almost all Fishman armies were able to skillfully use and execute it, after all, it always comes in handy, especially in situations like these.

Zhao Hai’s performance has also been satisfactory. It also seems like his use of small cone formations was the right decision.

At the same time, Zhao Hai and the others were also waiting for the opportune moment, that moment when the enemy starts to relax. Time passed by, and Illac started to feel relieved. The other party wanted to grind them down. But although Illac’s rate of losses was greater than the other party, the enemy still only had 1 million people. If Illac can sustain for a bit more time, the enemy would have no troops left to grind them down.

At this time, Lizzy saw that the other party was quite attracted to the current situation, so she immediately turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, it’s time to attack.” Zhao Hai nodded, then with an intention, four arms suddenly sprang out of the four corners of his formation. All of them simultaneously going for the four edges of the opposite party’s cube formation.

This change came very abruptly, the enemy didn’t expect that Zhao Hai and the others would make this move. The Fishmen were already used to this cube formation. Not moving the four edges was done in consideration of it being easier for the overall command of maneuvering. But Zhao Hai didn’t have this problem, he was commanding the undead, even if the entire formation were to make a collective move, it was still very possible. Zhao Hai’s formation was extremely flexible to any change in form.

The Demon’s four arms had now changed into four cone formations as it struck the four edges of the opposite party’s cube formation. And since Zhao Hai had already attracted the enemy’s attention into the center army, their response to this surprise attack came very late. Before Illac and the others made a response, the four cone formations were now making their way into the core of the cube formation.

The four troops on the edges didn’t expect that they would be receiving an attack, so naturally they weren’t able to make a proper response. And since their position was at an edge, it was close to impossible for them to make any significant moves. The four undead formations were now killing through the cube formation as it headed towards the center. At this time, the whirlpool at the front was having problems, so Zhao Hai used this opportunity to have his center army push through.

Illac was looking for any changes in the battle. When the four arms came, Illac stared for a moment before his face paled and he commanded, “With me as the center, block the enemy, quick!”

His subordinates were truly worthy of being warring tribes, they were quite strong. After their initial reaction, they were immediately stabilized by their leaders. Then with Illac as the center, all other formations made their move and surrounded Illac. Then layers of rotation and counter-rotations began. Before long, a huge rotating bead was spotted in the middle of the cube formation.

Chapter 629: Interesting Thing

The weakness that Lizzy had found out was actually already known to the Fishmen. They have used this cube formation for many years, so how could they be unaware of its weakness? The four edges supported the formation, they just couldn’t ignore it.

Some people have been using this weakness in order to break the cube formation, so the Fishmen quickly found a way to deal with it. The method was actually very simple. It was to gather a group of elite troops into those edges in order to not let it be broken into. At the same time, they also developed a defensive formation, called Ball.

This ball formation was what Illac was using right now. With the commander at the center, the sphere would keep revolving and counter revolving layer by layer. It looks like meat grinder, anyone who entered this formation would be ground to paste.

In addition to these two methods, there was also a weakness in this method of breaking the formation. The troop requirements needed to accomplish such attack was very high. Their actions must be fast and their movements must be unified, making its composition very strict. This was because if there were any defects in any one of those four attacking divisions, then the entire operation would be placed in jeopardy. It was precisely because of this that this method of breaking the cube formation has slowly vanished from use, allowing the cube formation to dominate in the Fishman armies.

Although the ball formation was a very good defensive maneuver, and can defend against an attack on the four edges of the cube, its defensive power was still inferior to the whirlpool. Moreover, its counter-attacking capabilities are extremely low. Because of this, the formation had always been a backup formation. Almost nobody used this formation at this time.

Naturally, Lizzy and the others weren’t aware about those considerations as well as restrictions in using their attack. After all, they were commanding undead, so they don’t need to worry about minute flaws in their formation.

But when Illac did their ball formation, Zhao Hai’s attack became useless. The ball formation might not be good in offense, but it can certainly hold its own when it came to defense. Especially against small attacks such as the Lizzy’s four demon arms, it was incredibly effective. Before long, the four divisions of undead that Zhao Hai had sent had been grinded into nothingness.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry about any of this and just commanded his undead to retreat, reforming their cube formation before going away.

At this time, Illac didn’t dare to take pursuit. The recent attacks had almost scared him to death that the thought of pursuing didn’t even enter his mind. Illac didn’t expect Zhao Hai to use a formation that targeted the cube’s weakness. One must know that this method hasn’t been used for so many years. If Illac’s troops weren’t formidable, then he might have lost his life just then.

Illac doesn’t understand what the other party wanted to do. The other party was using undead, so it was natural to think that all of them were expendable. However, the other party was using his undead as though it was an army, and also retreated after suffering some losses. This was completely unlike what a Dark Mage was supposed to do.

Illac and the other Sea Dragon’s relationship with the other Dragons haven’t been established in just a day or two, so they clearly knew what Dark Mages were. And they were clear that Dark Mages, when commanding a lot of undead, would just let them attack in a swarm-like manner. This way, the Dark Mages would use less magic as well as mental power.

When Dark Mages command the undead, they use magic power, however, the consumption of their mental power was even more. When Dark Mages use formations, they would surely be using more mental power than usual. Because of this, Dark Mages rarely used formations when attacking with large numbers of undead.

But contrary to normal customs, Zhao Hai actually arranged the undead in formations and also had them fight like any normal army. This made Illac confused as well as afraid of Zhao Hai.

At this point, Illac was almost sure that the other party was Zhao Hai. If the other party was composed of a battalion of Dark Mages, they wouldn’t be able to control the undead to such an astonishing degree. Not only can the undead change formations, it can also target weaknesses in the opponent’s defenses. This was absolutely not something that a group of Dark Mages were capable of.

A Dark Mage can surely command undead into delicate positions, however, a group of them can’t. After all, it was very difficult to find dozens of Dark Mages that were of the same strength and skill in Dark Magic. And since their skills were different, it was an inevitability that their control would have slight mistakes as well. These slight mistakes can be fatal to the battlefield. The only logical explanation to what just happened was that only one person was controlling the entire army of undead.

The reason why Illac dared to affirm the other party’s identity was the fact that he was facing against undead and not people. In the end, Dark Mages weren’t military men. Their genuine might in the battlefield relied on their undead. Only a few Dark Mages would dare study army formations at the same time. After all, shuffling between cultivating magic and studying formations was something near impossible to do.

Most importantly, an undead army doesn’t have any low and middle-level officers. The quality of these officers would heavily affect the effectiveness of the army. Some good low and middle-level officers can spot any small change in the battlefield and would make the appropriate adjustments. A commander’s word would just act like a guide for these kinds of people, they can already do what was expected of them, and maybe even more.

However, the undead was different. They don’t think before they fight, they just do what they were commanded to do. This led to Dark Mages seeing formations as useless in their way of fighting. They might as well let their undead rush the enemies down until one of them prevailed.

Once he had confirmed that the other party was Zhao Hai, Illac couldn’t help but feel dread. For Zhao Hai to have the ability to command the undead to this degree was very terrifying to think about. This was something Illac wasn’t expecting. At this time, Illac felt that he was fighting against a wise commander and his army, not a Dark Mage and his undead.

Although Illac managed to defend against the opponent’s attack, the losses that he had suffered weren’t small. Especially during the last encounter, it almost claimed Illac’s poor life. Because of this, when Zhao Hai retreated, Illac immediately reformed his cube formation. However, he kept the ball formation ready just in case another attack came in their way.

But even if Illac was being careful, he was still very worried. Not because of the other party, but because of his army’s current strength!

The troops that he commanded were all made up of Fishmen, and Fishmen were alive beings. Unlike the undead, these people had limits on how much stress their bodies can handle.

Illac was currently worried about the overall strength of his army. After going through offensive and defensive maneuvers, his army should be quite tired right now. When their strength gets too low, their situation would reach disastrous levels.

Illac didn’t quite understand Zhao Hai’s purpose of coming today. Why did he come? Did he just want to attack with 1 million undead only to get turned back? How could this be possible? Was Zhao Hai this arrogant?

….

Zhao Hai and the others were currently inside the Blade Scale Whale. Lizzy’s face turned quite ugly as she said, “Big Brother Hai, it seems like this method had already been thought through by the Fishmen. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have come up with a response this quickly.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Their reaction was indeed very good. But since the Fishmen already knew about this weakness, why haven’t they used it now? I’m quite confused about this.”

Lizzy sighed and said, “It looks like I failed this time. I didn’t think that my formation was already been used before.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “That may not be the case. Although the formation seems like it has been used before, it doesn’t mean that you can’t use it anymore. Since the Fishmen rarely used it, then there should be some shortcomings in the your formation. If you can find solutions to those, then wouldn’t you be invincible in the battlefield?”

Lizzy thought for a moment before she nodded and said, “This formation truly has a lot of weak points. I’m going to try and improve it. Megan, let’s go.”

At this time, Cai’er’s voice suddenly came, “Young Master, I’ve discovered something interesting. Want to take a look?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he nodded and said, “Alright.” After he responded, Cai’er changed the monitor’s display, showing the image of the Dragon Palace.

Zhao Hai and the others were shaken upon seeing the image. They didn’t think that there would be such a large reef. Moreover, the other party was actually able to move it, this was too shocking.

But when the monitor zoomed it, the group discovered something. Naturally, it wasn’t the Dragon Palace that Cai’er wanted to show them, but something in the palace instead.

Zhao Hai and the others were still some distance away from the Dragon Palace, so their eyes weren’t able to see it. Only through the monitor were they able to see it.

After Cai’er enlarged the image, several people appeared. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when he saw these people. He hasn’t seen Sea Dragons before, but he had heard about them from Luo Luo.

The reason why the Sea Dragons wore blue robes was because these robes were actually their scales. Dragons normally didn’t wear any other clothing, otherwise it would transform along with them.

Because of this, Zhao Hai was sure from Alex’s blue robes that he was a Sea Dragon. Moreover, it was certain that his status wasn’t very low. This was because all other Sea Dragons were having him as their center.

Chapter 630: Definitely

But this Sea Dragon wasn’t the focal point of Zhao Hai’s attention, it was the two other people right beside him. One of the two was a person that wore a golden robe. The other person wore a red robe and seemed to exude a sacred aura.

When Zhao Hai saw this red robed person, his eyes suddenly shrank. He knew what this sacred person was, he was certainly someone from the Radiant Church. At this point, Zhao Hai already had a certain understanding of the church. For someone to be able to wear this red robe meant that this person was an Archbishop.

After having thought about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at Joshua for a few times. Although he didn’t know Joshua’s name, Zhao Hai stil engrained the person’s image into his mind. This was a good opportunity to understand the enemy. Zhao Hai was already thinking of turning Joshua into an advanced level undead. After that, Zhao Hao would then know about the internal workings of the Radiant Church.

After remembering Joshua’s face, Zhao Hai turned his attention towards the golden robed man. This person had the temperament of someone formidable. Moreover, Zhao Hai can feel that this person had a similar aura with the Sea Dragons. This made Zhao Hai guess that this person was from the Dragon Race!

Zhao Hai carefully looked at Envoy Ao Ke, when he saw the horns hidden on Ao Ke’s golden hair, Zhao Hai became sure of Ao Ke’s status.

Laura and the others were similarly looking at the two and were also quick to discover their characteristics. After all, the two people looked extremely obvious, they didn’t even make an effort to hide their identity.

Laura’s face turned heavy as she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, it seems like the Radiant Church and the Dragons are indeed allies. It seems like our speculations have been confirmed. The Dragons were truly people of the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The emergence of these two people further confirms our guesses. The Divine Race is indeed already in action. Since the Radiant Church had failed, they moved to the Fishman Race instead. Regardless or not the Radiant Church succeeds, they would still conquer the sea. As long as they establish their influence here, then they can be considered invincible.”

Lizzy frowned as she said, “So what do we do now? Do we deal with them?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, we retreat and go tell Luo Ying about this information. After that, we’ll go to the Prairie and the Dwarves, telling them of this information as well.”

Megan nodded and said, “Right, information is of utmost importance. Moreover, the Dwarf Mountains isn’t far from the Accra Mountain. If the Dwarves are unaware of this, then it would be possible that they would suffer great losses.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved as the undead creatures spat out a black gas towards the Sea Dragon army. When Illac saw this, he didn’t dare to ignore it, so he immediately gave the command to slowly retreat. He didn’t want to be wrapped up by the black gas, who knew what that can do.

Fortunately, the black gas wasn’t quick, so Illac’s army managed to successfully turn back. However, Illac suddenly discovered something out of place. The black gas just fluttered around the battlefield, not going any further. Moreover, the clump of gas started to shrink towards the center. At this point, Illac immediately understood what the other party was doing as his face couldn’t help but change. Then he immediately had his army fully retreat, at the same time, he also sent word asking Alex for reinforcements.

The reason why Illac did this was because he understood that the black gas did none other than turning the corpses into undead. Zhao Hai was collecting more undead! Once Zhao Hai completes this process, his undead army would increase. When that time comes, Zhao Hai would become much more troublesome to deal with.

Before long, the black gas vanished, completely cleaning out the entire battlefield. No corpses were left on the scene. Illac’s face was incredibly ugly, but he still ordered his army to do a full retreat.

However, what surprised Illac was the fact that Zhao Hai’s undead army was currently slowly backing away. They seem to be retreating, with no intentions of continuing their attack.

This surprised Illac, but at the same time he felt relieved. He was really afraid of the other party attacking. If they did attack, Illac wasn’t sure that he would be able to block it.

Naturally, Illac didn’t dare to pursue. Although he didn’t understand why the opponent retreated, it was good for him that they turned back. Illac was genuinely terrified of Zhao Hai today. Not to say about the strength of the undead, but the abrupt movements of the formation were formidable as well. To be honest, Illac was quite envious of Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s command over the undead was something that Illac wanted to have. Being able to command an army as though it was your limb was the pinnacle of a commander’s dream. But that dream would be impossible to achieve. Even if one had the world’s most disciplined army, coordinating them together would still prove to be quite the problem. This made Illac wish that he had an army similar to Zhao Hai.

Illac thought that if he were to have any army like Zhao Hai’s undead, then he would remain undefeated in every battle that he’s in. However, it was a pity that he wasn’t a Dark Mage, he can’t achieve what Zhao Hai had.

At this time, Alex and the others also noticed Zhao Hai’s retreat, so he stooped the reinforcements that was headed towards Illac. However, the recent battle made Alex’s eyes shrink. He thought that if he were in Illac’s place, he still wouldn’t be able to fare better.

At this time, Ao Ke’s voice was heard, “Joshua, can you pinpoint the origin of the other party? This guy is not only good at commanding undead, his formations are also clever. Such people aren’t very good to deal with.”

Joshua forced a smile and said, “I can confirm 100% that the other party is Zhao Hai. Only Zhao Hai can command the undead to this extent. Other Dark Mages simply aren’t able to do it.”

Alex nodded and said, “Let’s return to the Great Hall and talk.” Then the group returned to the Great Hall. But before they continued on, Alex left a message to a person next to him, “Go call General Illac over to the Great Hall.” The person nodded before turning around to leave.

Before long, the three people have returned to the Great Hall. After taking care of his guests’ seats, Alex turned to Joshua and said, “Bishop, are you really sure that the opponent is Zhao Hai?”

Joshua nodded and said, “I’m sure of it. No other Dark Mage can do what he just did. Even the people from the Calci Family aren’t this proficient. In the entire continent, the most skilled in commanding undead is Zhao Hai. Therefore, I’m pretty sure that the other party is him.”

Alex’s face sank, then he said, “This Zhao Hai is too difficult to deal with. We need to make sure that he gets eliminated here. Otherwise, he would be a bad factor in God’s plans.”

Ao Ke nodded and said, “Right, this Zhao Hai is too fierce. Not only can he command undead, he can also exhibit battle formations. Most importantly, his undeads were very strong, at least 5th or 6th rank in strength. This is too scary. At the same time, he also managed to acquire more corpses before he left. It seems like he can also make undead en masse. Imagine the  implications of 1 million 5th or 6th rank warriors on land.”

Joshua nodded and said, “It is indeed scary. This person must be removed. He’s a danger to our plans.”

At this time, Illac came. Alex immediately beckoned him over. Illac gave the three a salute before Alex gave him a seat. Then Alex looked at Illac and said, “Illac, what did you feel when you fought with the opponent? Can you identify their identity?”

Without delay, Illac answered, “Your Majesty, I’m quite sure that the other party is Zhao Hai. Such an army cannot be commanded by a team of Dark Mages. It can only be directed by one person, otherwise, that degree of control couldn’t be achieved.”

Alex nodded, he was now entirely convinced that the opponent is Zhao Hai. Then Alex asked further, “The undead, how strong are they? The opponent’s ability to do formations, how is it?”

Illac replied, “The undead are very strong, about the same as a 5th rank magic beast. As for the formations, they seem quite weak. However, with constant practice, they would definitely be a threat on the battlefield. Your Majesty, this person must be removed. Otherwise, he would be a huge threat to our Sea Dragon tribe.”

Alex’s face completely sank. Illac, Joshua, and Ao Ke reached the same conclusion. With Zhao Hai’s strength, he cannot be allowed to remain alive any longer.

Alex turned his head to Joshua and said, “Bishop, what are your ideas? This Zhao Hai must never leave the sea, we absolutely cannot let him escape.”

Joshua nodded and said, “Naturally, it would be easier to deal with Zhao Hai here. It would be difficult to kill him in the continent. I’ve heard that the Buda Clan has multiple 9th ranks, moreover, this Zhao Hai’s personal strength is quite good as well. Rumors have been circulating in the continent saying that he has a Space Divergent ability. When we deal with him, we absolutely must not let him run away.”

Ao Ke stared, then he frowned and said, “He also has a Space divergent ability? If this is the case, then things just got more troublesome. I have heard that people with that ability is almost always impossible to catch. Their ability to escape is unparalleled under the heavens.”

Joshua nodded, “I know that. So I’m planning on having our church’s relic sent over. This time, no matter the price, we must eliminate Zhao Hai!”

Then Alex said, “Relic? What relic? Can it prevent a person with a Space divergent technique from running away?”

Joshua nodded, “This relic is specifically meant to deal with people who have Space divergent abilities. As long as we have that relic, Zhao Hai certainly cannot run away!”

Chapter 631: Lukewarm Elven Race

Envoy Ao Ke frowned and said, “Archbishop, it’s not time for cracking jokes. Is this relic something bestowed by the Gods? Otherwise, how could it possibly freeze space?”

Joshua shook his head and then sighed, “Although this relic wasn’t bestowed by the Gods, it actually held great significance for the Radiant Church. There have been several people with space divergent abilities in the continent before. These people were extremely difficult to deal with. Not only do they possess strong attacking power, but they are also impossible to catch. Every time the Radiant Church encountered these people, we would always take huge losses.”

Ao Ke and Alex nodded, they also understood that space divergent ability users were the most difficult people to deal with. If you offend someone like that, they would do their best to harm you while also having the leverage of being able to escape whenever they wanted. This ability made many people frustrated about space divergent ability users.

Joshua continued, “Then our Church’s 31st Pope came into existence. Not many knew about this, but he was a space divergent ability user himself. Being one of those people, the pope knew that there was no way to study nor pass on such an ability. So he thought of another way, he used his own body to perform experiments. He used both alchemy and magic formations in the whole process. And after years of research, he finally produced a metal element magic formation, this formation can be used to isolate space, making space divergent abilities malfunction. However, this achievement claimed his life. Because of this, the 32nd Pope declared the formation to be one of the Radiant Church’s sacred relics.”

Ao Ke and Alex couldn’t help but reveal shock in their faces. They couldn’t fathom how someone would used their own bodies to perform experiments, all of it for the sole purpose of dealing with space divergent ability users. But after their initial shock, the two of them expressed their heartfelt admiration towards that Pope.

Alex sighed, then he calmed his mood and said, “So there’s actually such a treasure. Then that’s good. As soon as Zhao Hai arrives, then we would lure him towards this magical formation.” Ao Ke also nodded, “I’ve also sent word back to the clan. The Patriarch would be sending five 9th rank Dragons in order to participate in this war. However, since they would be using dragon beads, their power would be lessened. In the end, the main force in this war would still be the Sea Dragons.”

Joshua nodded and said, “Alright, but you have to know that the range of the formation isn’t very far. Moreover, it can only lock the Space inside it, conventional methods of movements would still remain unhindered. Therefore, if we want to deal with Zhao Hai, then we should be assured of our means.”

Alex nodded, then he turned to Illac and said, “Illac do you have any means to lure Zhao Hai? We’ll set the formation beforehand and then have Zhao Hai lured inside before having him besieged by the experts. This is the only surefire way of dealing with him.”

Illac nodded and said, “This shouldn’t be difficult. After we attack, we could just retreat slowly. Seeing this, I’m quite sure that Zhao Hai would capitalize on the opportunity to do damage. And even if we don’t attack, I can still take the defensive line forward, making Zhao Hai come in before he notices that the formation.”

Alex nodded and said, “Good, I think that we shouldn’t make a move in the following days. Let’s preserve our strength and wait until the Dragons and the Radiant Church’s relic arrives. After that, we’ll deal with Zhao Hai in one go. As long as we can deal with Zhao Hai, the Mermaids would certainly fall shortly after.”

Ao Ke nodded, “Although dealing with the Mermaid Clan isn’t easy, it doesn’t mean that it is impossible. As long as we attract their forces here, the Dragon Clan can dispatch some people and attack Mermaid Island. As soon as that place falls down, we would achieve victory.”

Joshua nodded and said, “Right, then we’ll wait until the sacred relic arrives before dealing with Zhao Hai. In the meantime, we’ll be staying back, defending against further attacks by him.”

Zhao Hai was completely unaware that Joshua and the others were already thinking up of ways in order to deal with him. He was currently inside the blade scale whale, discussing with Megan and Lizzy about today’s tactical situation. They had fought for about half a day and had managed to find that their battle formations had weaknesses. However, these weaknesses also meant that there was room for improvement. Because of this, even if Megan and Lizzy hadn’t defeated the enemy, they were still elated about the result.

They kept talking up until they had reached the Mermaid Clan’s defensive line. Upon arriving, Zhao Hai immediately received his undead since he didn’t want to cause any panic among the troops.

Luo Ying and the others were outside the formation, waiting for Zhao Hai to come back. Luo Ying was also somewhat worried, they had even prepared to reinforce him. So when she saw Zhao Hai return, she immediately felt relief.

After inviting Zhao Hai over to the Azure Dragon Snail, Luo Ying looked at him and said, “How was mister Zhao Hai’s trip?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Very good. I managed to get more undead. But more importantly, I also to come across a very interesting thing.”

When Luo Ying heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but ask, “Interesting thing?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Among the Sea Dragons was a person from the Dragon Race as well as an Archbishop of the Radiant Church. Isn’t this very interesting?”

“What!” Luo Ying was in great surprise. “Really? Did mister really see a Dragon and a person from the Radiant Church?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I wouldn’t dare joke about this matter. I did see a Dragon and someone from the Radiant Church. One wore a golden robe while the other wore the clothes of a red robed Archbishop. It seems like the Sea Dragons did indeed have a relationship with the Dragons and the Radiant Church.”

Luo Ying’s face turned ugly, “So it’s like this. The implications of this is very heavy. Mermaid Island is in the surface, completely vulnerable to the attacks of flying Dragons. If they suddenly attack the island, then it would mean great trouble. I have thank mister for this information, I shall immediately pass it over to the Queen.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Aside from this, I really don’t have anything else to say. General, I’ll be heading back first. I think that the Sea Dragons wouldn’t be attacking today. So General doesn’t need to worry.”

Luo Ying nodded, she knew that Zhao Hai must have hit the Sea Dragons very hard this time. They shouldn’t be thinking about attacking right now.

After Zhao Hai returned to the blade scale whale, he immediately used the Space in order to return to Iron Mountain Fort before telling Green the information. He also gave Green a messenger fish and taught him how to use it. After that, he went to Golden Island and relayed the information to Kun, Rockhead, and Blockhead. Then he went to the Dwarf Mountains in order to tell them of the news as well.

Zhao Hai didn’t appear inside the village, but instead, he flashed on the square outside the Divine Palace. There was currently nobody here, so he wouldn’t be noticed, at the same time, this place was also not far from the Dwarf Village.

Not long after Zhao Hai appeared, a Dwarf came. It didn’t take too long for this Dwarf to recognize that their Foreign Elder Zhao Hai has come. So he immediately welcomed him to the village.

Billy was currently setting up for work, so when he found out that Zhao Hai had come he immediately invited him over to his office. After they sat down, Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, why did you come? Did something happen?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, and it’s not something trivial. Patriarch, did you know about the relationship between the Dragons and the Divine Race?”

Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Relationship between the Dragons and the Divine Race? What does the two of them had to do with each other? Did the Dragons participate in the war against the Divine Race?”

When Zhao Hai heard Billy he immediately knew that the Dwarves had not recorded the relationship between the Dragons and the Divine Race. Fortunately, Zhao Hai went to the Fishman Race. Otherwise, the wouldn’t have known about this hidden chess piece of the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “The Dragons did participate in the war against the Divine Race. However, they weren’t helping the people of the Ark Continent. Instead, they sided with the Divine Race, becoming their running dogs.”

Billy stared, then his face couldn’t help but change as he said, “Really? Where did you get this information? How could the Dragons be the dogs of the Divine Race?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he narrated to Billy his experience with the Fishman race. Billy calmly listened to Zhao Hai, and when Zhao Hai finished Billy said, “I didn’t expect that the Dragons and the Divine Race would have such a relationship. Fortunately, we found out about it. Otherwise, we would certainly suffer losses. What do you plan to do right now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I want to help the Fishmen deal with the Sea Dragons first. Then after that, I’ll go and try to deal with the Dragons. They needed to be taken care of, them occupying the Accra Mountain is too big of a threat. Accra Mountain houses the magic beast kingdom. If we have them control the magic beasts, then they would become good weapons of the Divine Race come wartime.”

Billy nodded, “If they indeed are people of the Divine Race, then it is right that they get eliminated. High level magic beast have wisdoms no less than us. If Dragons were controlling them, then it would be absolutely bad for us.”

Zhao Hai agreed, then he asked, “How’s the information about the Elves? If there’s nothing, we’ll tell them about this matter. Let’s see how they react to it.”

Billy nodded, then he sighed, “The Elves have always been slow to move, we cannot be anxious about this matter. Right, how are my people? Are they doing well?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They’re doing great. They’ve already adapted to the environment and had even managed to make new friends. Right, since I’ve already told you about what happened, I need to leave. I still need to head to the Prairie and inform the Beast King about this matter, having him prepare for the future.”

Chapter 632 – Imperial Water Oyster

The Beast King has been very happy these days. The Beast God’s Spear has been returned to the Beastman Prairie, and for the Beastmen, this was a monumentally important matter. And for the Beast King, having the Beast God’s Spear back would give him advantages in ruling the entire Prairie.

Although the name ‘Beast King’ held power and prestige, the actual authority that it held wasn’t that big. Moreover, the Lion Race was also at the side, waiting. This made the Beast King quite uncomfortable.

But now that their Divine Artifact was back, his prestige has increased. In the past, those huge Warring tribes wouldn’t give him too much face. But now, the situation has been improved. This was also good for his future plans.

The Beast King didn’t dare to tell the other Beastmen about the Divine Race. The Beast King knew that the Beastmen had a flaw. Aside from the Patriarchs of the tribes, the other Beastmen were very simple minded, it was very easy for them to reveal any secrets. The Beastmen were different from the Dwarves. The Dwarves operated inside their mountain, which was structured like a fortress, no Human can simply go in and out of it. Due to this, there was little to no chance of any Dwarf revealing secrets to the outside world.

The Beastmen, on the other hand, was placed in the wide Prairie where Human merchants were free to go in and out, being able to easily contact with the Beastmen. If the Divine Race’s matter was revealed too soon, then the Radiant Church would surely get wind of it.

Because of this, the Beast King’s preparations for dealing with the Divine Race were all held in secrecy, hiding it from the majority of the Beastman population. For this plan to succeed, the Beast King would need the full cooperation of the various big warring tribes. In the past, this was fairly impossible, but now that the Beast God’s Spear is back, the Beast King’s influence has reached its apex, allowing him to carry out his plan.

The Beast King has been in contact with trustworthy Patriarchs of the warring tribes in recent days. He told them about the Divine Race, making them swear to hold the matter in secrecy before he had them return and prepare.

On this day, the Beast King had just finished doing a task when a guard suddenly gave word. Zhao Hai has come. When the Beast King heard this, he stared for a moment before instructing his people to lead Zhao Hai into his living room.

Zhao Hai’s is  the Foreign Prince of the Beastman Race, so it can be said that his position in the Prairie is above the majority of people while his reputation isn’t lower than the Beast King. Since he retrieved the Beast God’s Spear, the Beastmen were very respectful to him. Even his Magic Lily Shop has received good reception by the Beastmen, making its business very good.

This Magic Lily shop was something that was opened by Zhao Hai, and since he was their Foreign Prince, the Beastmen treated him as one of them. The Beastmen knew the value of buying from one’s own people. This made the shop’s business very popular in the entire Prairie.

Fortunately, the Buda Clan has the Markey Family’s business network at their back, so no matter what, they can service all of the Beastmen that came to them. And since Magic Lily shop always did business fairly, it’s reputation soared in the Prairie, which added to Zhao Hai’s prestige.

After being led by a Tiger clansman to the room, the Beast King immediately cleared the room, only leaving Zhao Hai and him behind. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you came, did something happen?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Your Majesty, I came upon something while I was visiting the Fishman Race. There’s a rebellion currently happening in the sea. However, this isn’t so simple. I saw a Dragon and a person from the Radiant Church there. Moreover, I’ve also learned something from the Mermaid clan. The Dragons have participated in the war between the Ark Continent and the Divine Race. However, the Dragons were on the side of the Gods. This made me suspect that the Dragons were aces that the Gods have hidden, preparing all this time to deal with us. If they manage to conquer the seas, then they would gain a huge advantage in the future war. And if we add the Radiant Church and the Dragons, we would stand no chance. I’m telling you this because it might be possible that the Dragons would send people here. When I’m done dealing with the matters of the Fishmen, I would immediately go to Accra Mountain in order to cope with those Dragons!”

The Beast King listened intently to Zhao Hai, upon hearing everything, his face couldn’t help but change, “Are you sure? The Dragons claimed to be invincible in the continent, but I don’t think so. I can send some Beastmen to help you. You can also discuss this with the Dwarves and have them send troops as well. Our men would deal with the Dragons first!”

But Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, the Humans of the Continent are still unaware about the Divine Race. If you suddenly send troops to deal with the Dragons, the Dragons would certainly stop it. At that time, a great war might happen, causing our side some losses. Just preserve your own strength. You can rest assured that I can manage this. You don’t need to worry too much.”

The Beast King looked at Zhao Hai, then he lightly sighed and said,” Alright, but if you need our help, don’t hesitate to send word. We Beastmen are always willing to die for our brothers!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No need to be uptight about this. Right, Your Majesty, I’ll be heading back to the Fishmen. The war is still going on, I can’t just leave for a long time.”

Then the Beast King personally delivered Zhao Hai outside. Upon seeing Zhao Hai leave, the Beast King couldn’t help but sigh. He suddenly felt helpless deep inside. The Beastmen generally didn’t fear anything, but their enemy this time is just too strong. Even if they are Beastmen, they needed to bear with it patiently. They can only look at Zhao Hai like an outsider as he deals with the Radiant Church and the Dragons. The thought of this made the Beast King feel uncomfortable.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about this, to him, the importance of informing the Beastmen and the Dwarves about the Dragon Race was just to make those two races defend themselves. He wanted them to be safe as much as possible. Dealing with the Dragons isn’t very difficult for Zhao Hai.

When Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he finally let out a sigh of relief. He had finally plugged the leak. He was really afraid that this leak would be exploited by the Dragons.

Nobody in the continent knew about the relationship between the Divine Race and the Dragons. If the Dragons were to attack with the Divine Race, then the Beastmen and the Dwarves would surely be placed in great danger. It was good that he came to the Fismen at this time.

While thinking about this, Zhao Hai entered the Space’s villa. But when he entered, he couldn’t help but stare. He wasn’t expecting the place to be so lively.

When he walked in, Zhao Hai saw Laura, Lizzy and Megan inside, discussing tactics. Naturally, Laura was only giving comments from time to time, the ones who talked a lot were Lizzy and Megan.

Lizzy and Megan both seem to have a natural instinct for strategy. This was something that one is born with, not learned. Once they are able to sense the changes of the battlefield, the two of them would surely become famed generals before long.

Zhao Hai didn’t go and disturb them, he just went to the hot spring underground and soaked in it, relaxing his body and mind. In the past few days, the Divine Race’s matter had made his entire being stiff, making it hard for him to breathe. But what gave Zhao Hai more headache was the fact that the Demon Race still haven’t revealed themselves. Zhao Hai already has some understanding about the Divine Race, but for the Demons, he was entirely clueless. This gave him a huge headache.

After having rested for the rest of the evening. Zhao Hai was invited by Luo Ying to the Azure Dragon Snail the next morning. But Luo Ying wasn’t intending to discuss war with Zhao Hai, she came to look for him for a totally different matter.

When Zhao Hai came to the hall, Luo Ying immediately said, “Mister, please sit down.”

The Luo Ying who was generally cold had suddenly turned warm, this made Zhao Hai feel strange. He looked at Luo Ying, puzzled, before he said, “What matter does general want me for?”

Luo Ying smiled faintly and said, “Something good has arrived. The clan had sent me some items to give to Mister.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Something for me? What are they?”

Luo Ying smiled faintly and said, “Take them here.” Then two Mermaids carried two bottles over. The bottles had sand and some aquatic plants in them, but they weren’t relevant. What’s relevant were the actual contents of the bottles. One held a white oyster, while the other had an azure snail.

The white oyster had no patterns on it, it was pure white, the kind of white that would make one stare at it for quite some time. As for the azure snail, it looked just like a snail, nothing was special.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s confused look, Luo Ying couldn’t help but smile and said, “I came to know that mister likes to collect unique lifeforms. This oyster is a special type of being in the sea, we call it Imperial Water Oyster. This oyster can grow a pearl that held some properties. The pearl can increase one’s water element attacks. The bigger the pearl, the better its effect. It’s quite a precious magic beast of the sea.”

Zhao Hai’s face changed into glee as he looked at this common looking oyster. He didn’t think that this little thing would have such good use.

Seeing that Zhao Hai liked the oyster, Luo Ying smiled and then continued, “This snail is actually a young and living Azure Dragon Snail. Young Azure Dragon Snails have yet to form patterns on their shells. Only after ten years would the dragon patterns appear. The more years pass, the more distinct the patterns would become.”

Surprise! This was definitely a surprise for Zhao Hai. He had long yearned for an Azure Dragon Snail, but this snail was a treasure for the Mermaid Clan, so he was too embarrassed to ask for one. And since the snail is too rare, he might not even be able to find one. He wasn’t expecting the Mermaids to gift him one today, this was really a good gift.

Chapter 633: Frequent Each Other

For ordinary people, these two things would be impossible to be put into good use. The Imperial Water Oyster would need years before a pearl can be made. And the longer the pearl stays inside the oyster, the better its effect would be. However, the life of a Human can only be so much. When the pearl reaches a formidable level, its owner might have already died.

The same was true for the Azure Dragon Snail. Although the snail had a lot of uses, it would still need several hundred years before it can become good. If one wants to have the same Azure Dragon Snail as the Mermaid clan, then one would still have to wait for a thousand years. Even 9th rank experts couldn’t live for that long, much less average people. It was virtually useless.

But Zhao Hai was different, he has the Space which was going against heaven’s will. So these two marine beings have great use for him. The Space can accelerate growth, so if he placed the Azure Dragon Snail inside, it wouldn’t take too long for it to grow into something formidable. Moreover, he can also produce more Azure Dragon Snails.

There is also the Imperial Water Oyster. It might not be relevant to have one or two, but if this thing can be mass produced, then the situation would become different. This water element treasure was something extremely useful for Water Mages since their attack would become three times stronger. If the pearl gets mass produced and handed over to the Water Mages of the continent, then the overall power of the continent would be increased.

Naturally, since this thing is precious to the Fishman Race, they weren’t able to mass produce it. But it was different for Zhao Hai, if he wanted more, then he would have more. And the oyster would be much different in the Space. The oyster might not produce a pearl in the sea, but in the Space, it was certain that it would make one.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s expression, Luo Ying knew that Zhao Hai was satisfied with the gifts. Luo Ying couldn’t help but appreciate Luo Luo. The information that Luo Luo gave her had become very important.

Zhao Hai received the two bottles, then he turned to Luo Ying and smiled, “I’ve made the General go through much troubles for me. This one is indeed interested in collecting unique things. I wish to have as many unique marine things as possible.”

Luo Ying smiled and said, “Mister is too polite. I’ve already sent word, making people collect as much unique things as possible. I believe that they would be sending those over in a few days.”

Zhao Hai smiled and then said, “Then I’ll have to thank the general. I’m planning to suppress the Sea Dragons today as well. I also want to see how the Radiant Church and the Dragons respond. What do you think?”

Luo Ying thought for a moment and then said, “Alright, then I’ll have to trouble mister. In two days, the clan’s reinforcements would arrive. When they come, we can do a general attack.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, then I’ll attack the Sea Dragons in the meantime. When your army is completed, then we can attack together. Just take these following days as a break and take a good rest.”

Luo Ying nodded, then she stood up and bowed to Zhao Hai, “Mister’s great kindness towards my Mermaid Clan will not go unremembered. If mister needs something in the future, me and my clan would surely come to your assistance.”

Zhao Hai stood up and laughed, “General is too polite. I’ve only come to help this time because we have a common enemy. What General said made this Zhao Hai blush. If General has nothing else to say, then I shall be taking my leave.”

Luo Ying nodded and then said, “Then I won’t be stopping mister.” Then Zhao Hai gave Luo Ying a salute before turning around to leave. When Zhao Hai left, Luo Ying turned to Luo Luo and said, “Luo Luo, you have contributed greatly this time. It seems like mister really likes to collect strange things. We must collect more things for mister, the sea is near endless, we should be able to find things that he likes.”

Luo Luo smiled and said, “General is too polite. But General, I don’t understand. It takes a lot of effort to collect such things. All of this just for mister’s help?”

Luo Ying smiled faintly and said, “Silly thing, you’re quite clueless. All this effort is not just a gesture of gratitude towards mister Zhao Hai. You might have heard, the Radiant Church, Dragons, and Sea Dragons have started to work together. I’m afraid the coming of the Divine Race would arrive soon. Mister Zhao Hai is an ally of the Dwarves as well as the Beastmen. He will surely be a central figure in the fight against the Divine Realm. Such a person is worth all of our effort.”

When Luo Luo heard Luo Ying, she stared for a moment before she completely understood. Her face was pale when she asked, “General, will the Divine Realm really invade us?”

Luo Ying sighed and said, “According to the recent developments, the invasion is for certain. The races in the continent would surely suffer a disaster.”

Zhao Hai didn’t know about what Luo Luo and Luo Ying were talking about. After all, he was currently in the Space, staring at the two bottles in his hand. Inspecting them with great curiosity.

Just as the group was staring at the bottle with the Azure Dragon Snail, the Space issued a prompt. It told them that it was possible to rear the two marine magic beasts, this made Zhao Hai feel relieved. At this time, Laura tapped the Azure Dragon Snail’s bottle and said, “Brother Hai, make Cai’er raise this one. When the time comes, we would also have our own Azure Dragon Snail.” The Azure Dragon Snail that Laura meant was naturally the one that Luo Ying was currently using.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and smiled, “How could that be so simple ? The Mermaid Clan’s Azure Dragon Snail had underwent many years of refining. Let’s wait for a few days, then I’ll go and ask whether we can gain access to this Water Refining method. This method is going to be very useful.”

Lizzy didn’t care about this so much, she turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, let’s go. I want to test my formation on the Sea Dragons today.”

Upon hearing Lizzy, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, “Alright, we’ll be heading to the Sea Dragons in order to practice battle formations.” Then he waved his hand to summon his undead army before they went forward.

Alex and the others have set up their army formation quite early and waited. They knew that since Zhao Hai gained the upper hand yesterday, he would surely come back today. So they decided to not go on the offense, but instead focused on defense.

They were waiting as well, as long as the sacred relic of the Radiant Church arrives along with the Dragon Clan’s experts, Zhao Hai would finally be dealt with. So what they want to do right now was to defend with all they have.

However, Illac had pushed their line of defense forward. This was to prepare for Zhao Hai in the future. Because they had gone forward, when they plan to deal with Zhao Hai in a few days, they can just move the army backwards, making Zhao Hai fall into the center of the magic formation. At that time, he would then be besieged by experts.

Illac was currently sitting inside his huge sea urchin, his eyes focused on the distance. He had a hunch that the enemy would be coming today. And sure enough, a cubic formation slowly appeared. Illac immediately ordered the army to prepare themselves for battle.

The men of Illac’s army didn’t dare to be neglectful this time. They had already experienced the might of Zhao Hai’s undead yesterday. They didn’t expect that they would be placed in such a predicament by those undead.

Zhao Hai was sitting inside the Blade Scale Whale’s body, he looked at the monitor and then said, “Lizzy, Megan, what formations do the two of you want to test today?”

Lizzy smiled and said, “Let me try first. I want the same Demon as yesterday.”

Zhao Hai looked at her and said, “Alright, how does your Demon plan to deal with the enemy?”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “Big Brother Hai, the cube formation that the other party was doing today might be very good. But you can see that it has distinct edges and corners. My new Demon formation would look like a big octopus. Combat units on the tentacles of the octopus would attack those edges and corners. Although those places are filled with elite troops, changing their position wouldn’t be very easy for the commander. Making it possible for us to slowly, bit by bit, grind those edges.”

Then Lizzy drew her formation on the monitor. Zhao Hai understood what Lizzy wants, she wanted those troops to entangle the cube like an octopus’ tentacle. These troops would then be akin to a file, grinding down on those edges of the cube.

Zhao Hai thought that this formation seemed to be quite interesting. So he nodded and waved his hand, ordering the undead like how Lizzy wanted. Then he sent them out to attack the other party.

Illac was currently in his command center, calmly looking at the enemy. He wanted to know what formations the other party had prepared for him today. To be honest, Illac couldn’t help but feel like he was currently playing chess with the enemy. This feeling was something that had stuck to his mind.

Zhao Hai’s undead quickly arrived at the other party’s cube formation. Then the undead formation suddenly changed, it had sprouted a lot of tentacles, all of which were heading towards Illac’s formation

But Illac was an experienced war General, so he knew what the other party wanted to do. Upon seeing the enemy he immediately commanded, “Change formation, make a ball formation with me as the center.” Then his command got passed through as the formation moved slowly. With Illac as the center, troops were rotating, layer by layer around him.

Lizzy didn’t expect the other side to change formation this quickly. Her Demon formation was highly effective against the cube formation, however, it was unsuitable against the ball formation.

At this time, Megan said, “Good, they turned into a ball. Elder Brother Hai, use my Connecting Thorns in order to deal with them.” After Megan saw how the enemy used the ball formation yesterday, she immediately racked up her brains in order to find a way to deal with it. The method that she had developed was exactly this ‘Connecting Thorns.

This formation is very basic and simple, it was just a bunch of small cone formations lined up with each other. Then this line would oppose the direction that the ball formation was rotating, scratching its surface and breaking some of the enemies off.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he immediately changed the arrangement for the undead. The tentacles shrank as small cone formations appeared, then it went to oppose the spinning motion of the other party’s formation.

Chapter 634: The True War

Everyday in the next four days, Zhao Hai had brought his undead to attack the Sea Dragons’ base. Fighting with the Sea Dragons had become a game to Lizzy and Megan. The ideas that they had come up were endless, most of them were something that Zhao Hai wouldn’t have thought of. Seeing the two women being excited made Zhao Hai speechless. He really didn’t expect these two to be this enthusiastic.[1]

In these four days, the Sea Dragons were also very calm. But now, they are ready, the Radiant Church’s sacred relic had arrived. It was a huge magic formation made using seven minor metallic formations . But this formation didn’t have a very large area of operation. The whole formation can only encompass about a thousand square meters. After this area, the effectivity of the formation would largely drop up until it couldn’t suppress space anymore.

This thousand square meter area is not very big, especially to experts like Zhao Hai, they can pass this distance in just a blink of an eye. But if he were to be surrounded in this thousand meter squared area, he would still be in deep trouble.

At this point, the Sea Dragons were only waiting for the experts from the Dragon Clan to arrive. The Radiant Church had also sent four 9th rank experts, with Joshua in the mix, the Church had 5 9th rank experts participating. Besides Ao Ke, the Dragon clan had sent 5 9th rank experts, all in all counting up to six. Finally, the Sea Dragons had their own nine 9th rank experts. Altogether, there were 20 9th rank experts in this operation to deal with Zhao Hai. Because of this, Alex and the others were confident. They believed that Zhao Hai would finally be dealt with.

While the Sea Dragons were preparing, Luo Ying’s side hadn’t been idle either. These days, reinforcements had finally arrived. Right now, their army was numbered nearly 20 million troops.

When Zhao Hai heard this number, he couldn’t help but get startled. 20-million-troop army, what kind of concept was that? Zhao Hai felt that this number could actually fill the entire ocean.

Luo Ying also prepared to make a move in two days. It can be said that the two sides were already preparing for their war. At the request of Luo Ying, Zhao Hai rested for two days. He didn’t find any trouble with the Sea Dragons since he knew that Luo Ying was preparing to attack them.

When the Sea Dragons saw that Zhao Hai hadn’t come, they couldn’t help but stare. Then they immediately sent someone to check only to see the present Mermaid army.

After knowing about this, Alex immediately took Joshua and Ao Ke to the palace hall as he told them the scout’s report.

After hearing Alex out, Ao Ke couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Alright, then let’s wait for them to get prepared. The opportunity finally came, so while we restrict their army here, the Patriarch would also have people go and attack Mermaid Island. Extinguishing their root in one fell swoop.”

Joshua nodded and said, “The Church shall also help. We must give ruin to Mermaid Island. With the destruction of that place, the enemy’s morale would be low. When the time comes, we can seize the opportunity and counter-attack.”

Alex nodded and said, “Then I’ll be troubling you two. When the experts from the Dragon Clan arrive, we would then be able to deal with Zhao Hai. After that, we can deal with the Mermaids.”

The two nodded, then Joshua said, “We should set the formation up. So when Zhao Hai arrives, we can direct him there and the eliminate him.”

Alex nodded, “Good, I’ll have to ask the Archbishop’s help in arranging the formation. As long as that gets set up, the only thing we will be waiting for would be Zhao Hai’s attack.”

But Ao Ke still knit his brows and said, “The Mermaid army has already been assembled. If they work together, then wouldn’t dealing with Zhao Hai be more difficult?”

Alex smiled faintly and said, “Envoy can rest assured, the love of the Mermaids are quite well known. Even if they had a large army, I think they would still let Zhao Hai and his undead take the lead. This is to ensure that they would suffer the least losses. So as long as Zhao Hai takes to the front, our plan can still go through.”

Ao Ke nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll have to ask the Archbishop to prepare. When my people arrive tomorrow, we shall prepare our ambush. The moment Zhao Hai enters the formation is the moment he gets exterminated.”

Joshua nodded, then he walked out of the hall along with Ao Ke and Alex. The other two wanted to see how this formation was going to be arranged.

Joshua arrived outside, and long with several Sea Dragons, he went towards the battlefield. A couple of days ago, he had already chosen a place not too far from Illac’s army position. The place was in a narrow valley, so if Zhao Hai chases after Illac, he would surely come upon the formation.

After arriving at the place, Joshua made several Fishmen dig seven ditches first; one in the middle and then six on the surrounding area. The ditch wasn’t too deep, only about 2 meters down. Any deeper and it would affect the strength of the formation.

After having dug the holes, Joshua retrieved seven one-meter diameter discs from his space bag. These seven discs were made out of unknown metal, all of them were sparkling and beautiful. Etched on top of them were some mysterious symbols.

Joshua delicately placed the seven discs on each hole, carefully adjusting its angle and direction. After some time, when the discs were adjusted properly, the seven discs had started to give out a faint glow, but faint enough that it couldn’t be easily spotted.

After seeing this, Joshua knew that the magic formation had been placed properly. Then he instructed the Fishmen to carefully bury the discs. After that, the magic formation had already been set.

The next day, the experts from the Dragon Clan had arrived. Ao Ke and the others immediately handed them some water repelling dragon beads. When they prepared for the ambush, the Fishmen also took out a few large shells for them to stay in. These shells were also special products of the sea. Although its offensive and defensive strength wasn’t very good, it still had the ability to mask the breath of a person. The Fishmen had given this shell the name Stealth Shell. I cannot really make someone stealthy, it just manages to hide a person’s aura.

The stealth shells were placed right next to Joshua’s magic formation. When they became disguised, nobody can see them from the outside anymore.

Since the formation was placed right behind Illac’s army, Luo Ying wasn’t able to spot it. At this time, they were still in preparation, getting ready to deal with the Sea Dragons in one go.

But at this time, Ao Ke and Joshua had also written a letter to tell the Dragon Clan and the Radiant Church about the current situation. The Dragon Clan and the Radiant Church immediately organized a group of experts and had them sent over to Mermaid Island, prepared to eliminate the Mermaid Clan.

Two days after Luo Ying started her preparations, the battle would finally begin. And just as Alex guessed, to Luo Ying had Zhao Hai take the lead with his undead army.

This idea was actually proposed by Zhao Hai, and Luo Ying didn’t object to it. During the days where Zhao Hai was fighting with Illac, the undead in his hand had not reduced. Instead, it had gotten more and more. At this point, the Fishman undead that he had amounted to more than 2 million.

After everything had been prepared, Zhao Hai left with his undead first, then followed by Luo Ying’s army. While sitting inside the Blade Scale Whale and looking at the monitor, Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy and Megan and said, “When the battle starts, I’ll have the two of you take command. What do you think?”

Lizzy turned her head and took a glance at the army that was not too far behind them. Her eyes couldn’t help but turn red from excitement as she said, “Alright, commanding in battles is really fun.”

The similarly excited Megan nodded. When he saw the two, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. Megan and Lizzy had become more and more like generals in the past few days. Their strategies were getting more and more decent compared to their first ones. It had become more impossible for the enemy to break their formations as the flaws have gotten less and less.

The army was getting closer and closer to the Sea Dragons’ defensive line. Adam had also spotted their army, but he didn’t plan to challenge Zhao Hai right now. His purpose was to direct Zhao Hai to the magic formation. Therefore, he immediately ordered his army to slowly retreat.

This was also a normal thing to do. Illac’s men numbered 10 million while Luo Ying had 20 million. With a difference of more than double, it wasn’t a mystery why Illac retreated.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this as he commanded his undead to go forward. But at this moment, Zhao Hai was suddenly stunned as he turned to Lizzy and said, “Look, right there, aren’t those people?” Then he pointed towards a spot in the monitor.

Lizzy and the others followed Zhao Hai’s finger and saw that nearby Illac’s army were several big shells. In these big shells were people, some were Humans while some were Dragons. Moreover, their strengths seem to be formidable.

Lizzy frowned and said, “Big Brother Hai, what do they intend to do? Do they want to ambush us? They look strong, perhaps 9th rank experts.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he still didn’t make army stop. He proceeded to advance slowly as the magic formation appeared in the monitor. Lizzy and the others carefully looked at the magic formation, but since they weren’t acquainted with the art, they were puzzled when seeing it.

Zhao Hai was also clueless, at this time, Laura frowned, “Brother Hai, what is this? I can understand them using 9th ranks to deal with us, but a magic formation? What are they planning to do?”

Zhao Hai frowned as well as he looked at the buried magic formation. After a while, he shook his head and said, “I don’t know, but it doesn’t matter. We’ll come to know about it soon.” He said as he still urged his undead to go forward.

* * *

I did a double take, it really did just skip xD

Chapter 635: Besieged

ZHao Hai knew that informing others about this was impossible. Although these people were 9th rank experts, they were currently inside a shell, with their aura’s completely hidden. Moreover, these shells were also buried under the seabed. If Zhao Hai didn’t have the monitor, then it would be impossible for him to spot these people.

However, Zhao Hai also didn’t understand what this magic formation would do. So to be safe, he had Laura and the others return to the Space. In any case, nothing will happen to him, he can crystallize, making people unable to do damage to him. Moreover, he also has so many undead. Although they have 5th or 6th rank strength right now, all of them can instantly return to being 9th ranks. With these many 9th rank creatures, the enemy’s 9th ranks would be useless.

But Zhao Hai didn’t want to show his cards so easily. He still wanted to see what the other party wanted to do and what effects this magic formation had.

Laura and the others didn’t object to Zhao Hai’s idea to deliver them to the Space. Although they were also 9th rank experts, their experience in battle was very low. At the same time, they also didn’t have Zhao Hai’s crystallization ability. They would only burden Zhao Hai if they chose to remain here.

Zhao Hai commanded his army to move forward as though he didn’t notice the ambush at all. He believed that as soon as he enters the magic formation, the other party would start to attack. He had counted the number of opponents, 20 people, not more not less, 20 people.

Twenty 9th rank experts! Seeing this number made Zhao Hai smile, the enemy surely did regard him very highly. Sending 20 9th ranks just to deal with him was very interesting.

Although Illac was retreating, he made sure that his retreat wasn’t fast. If he went back faster than he wanted, Zhao Hai might stop and send his undead towards him. Illac managed his army carefully, attracting Zhao Hai closer and closer to the formation. As soon as Zhao Hai enters, then everything would be taken care of.

Zhao Hai sat inside the blade scale whale, in his hand was his Blood Ghost Staff. His two eyes intently staring at the opposing army as he calculated his entry to the magic formation.

The people in ambush were also waiting for Zhao Hai to enter the formation. Time passed by bit by bit as Zhao Hai got closer and closer to their encirclement

Zhao Hai counted in his mind, “Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one,” When the reached ‘one’ he had finally entered the formation.

Sure enough, when he entered the formation, the seabed suddenly moved as 20 shadows appeared from the bottom of the sea. Upon coming out, these people immediately got to work. Some of them were charged with handling the undead while some barrelled towards the blade scale whale.

Zhao Hai also made his move, he received the blade scale whale to the Space and then turned towards the approaching enemies. What made Zhao Hai feel strange was the fact that the enemy hadn’t used their magic formation yet.

Zhao Hai didn’t know that the formation was already in effect. It’s just that its function was to lock the space, nothing else.

If Zhao Hai really had a space divergent ability, then he would have already felt that his power was suppressed. But unfortunately, Zhao Hai didn’t have such an ability. His Space and the Ark Continent’s space divergent ability were two different things.

Space abilities of the Ark Continent were different, no matter how good it was, it still uses the space of the continent. On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s Space was another thing completely. His Space was inside his body, a variant Space that had no relationship with the Ark Continent. Because of this, the enemy’s magic formation was useless to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai had thought that the purpose of the enemy’s magic formation was to attack him, or maybe to suppress his movements. But it looks like the magic formation was not functioning right now, which made Zhao Hai puzzled. He couldn’t understand what this magic formation would do, why did they set this up?

However, the situation didn’t allow him enough time to think. Ninth rank experts were currently throwing themselves towards him. Zhao Hai smiled and then had the undead try to block those people. Zhao Hai didn’t have them show their 9th rank strength, so they were still 5th to 6th ranks, he wasn’t planning on revealing his hand too soon.

Although there were 20 people on the opposing side, these people weren’t a threat to him. So he just wanted to test his strength against these people.

Zhao Hai looked at the enemy, they were composed of Sea Dragons, Dragons, and people from the Radiant Church. This scene made Zhao Hai feel excitement. He really wanted to see how strong these Sea Dragons and Dragons were.

The 5ht to 6th rank undead were unable to block all of the 9th ranks. Faced with the attacks of the enemy, Zhao Hai waved his staff and said, “Condense!”

This ‘Condense’ magic was a basic spell of Water Mages. This magic made all of the surrounding waters solidify, trapping any enemy within it.

One must know that Zhao Hai was now a 9th rank expert, so his ‘Condense’ magic couldn’t just be ignored. If an 8th rank were to receive Zhao Hai’s Condense magic, then that 8th rank wouldn’t be able to move.

The enemy that Zhao Hai was facing right now were 9th rank experts, 6 people at this time. These 6 people were all from the Sea Dragon tribe. The Sea Dragons knew that they were the strongest ones when it came to underwater combat. Although the Dragons and the Humans were also 9th rank, they’re strengths were still suppressed by the sea. Therefore, the Dragons and the Humans became in charge of dealing with the undead while the six Sea Dragon experts were going to deal with Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai played along and had his undead bluntly attack. Although the present strengths of these undead were 5ht or 6th rank, they still numbered about 2 million. No matter how fierce one was, even if they were 9th rank, one still couldn’t ignore such numbers.

The six Sea Dragons felt the change of the surrounding waters, but since they were 9th ranks, it only affected them a little. After all, Sea Dragons were experts of Water magic as well. The eyes of the Sea Dragons couldn’t help but turn smug before it was replaced by a cruel expression. They gave a shout before their blue robes turned into blue armor, their head ornaments turned into Dragon helmets, and their gloves became sharp claws.

Zhao Hai stared at what just happened, he just saw clothes that acted as the one that he had, both were clothing that can transform.

Zhao Hai knew that adult Dragons had three transformation. The first one would be their humanoid form, the one where they wore their robes. This form was called Human form by the Dragon race. The second form was their armored state, this was the fighting form of the Dragon race. Moreover, in this form, their strength would be twice their strength on their Human form. The final form is their true body state. This was when they completely become Dragons, of which they can exhibit their full power.

But since Zhao Hai was trapped inside a formation and was unable to escape, he was just akin to a fish in a barrel. Moreover, if they used their true form, the place would get crammed, given how small the area of the formation was. Only two Dragons can attack Zhao Hai each time. Therefore, the Sea Dragons opted to fight using their Armored form.

While Zhao Hai stared, a Sea Dragon rushed towards him. His claws extended as he swung towards Zhao Hai’s head. His entire claw was covered with blue scales which also flashed some blue radiance, showing that this attack was a serious one.

Zhao Hai’s hand moved, meeting this attack with a sideways stroke. The Blood Ghost Staff in his hand met the other party’s attack. Zhao Hai didn’t transform the staff into a sword, he struck with the intention of testing the defensive capabilities of the enemy.

The other party wasn’t expecting the Mage Zhao Hai to retaliate with a strong melee attack. He couldn’t block it, so the staff smashed into his chest. The Sea Dragon felt as though his chest was hit with an extremely heavy hammer. His lungs emptied as his body was smashed backwards.

This startled the Sea Dragon, he had actually been injured. He immediately retreated as he took a few breaths and suppressing the blood flowing out of his body. At the same time, the eyes of the Sea Dragon focused entirely on Zhao Hai.

One must know that the bodies of Sea Dragons were very formidable. Zhao Hai’s blow actually damaged the Sea Dragon’s armored body. This was beyond what he had expected, this also made him understand Zhao Hai’s strength.

At this time, the attacks of the other Sea Dragons also arrived. Although all of them were 9th ranks, this was the first time that they had ganged up on one enemy, so their cooperation wasn’t the best. However, they still surrounded Zhao Hai, they absolutely cannot have Zhao Hai leave the formation.

After Zhao Hai’s staff repelled the Sea Dragon, the attack of another Sea Dragon had already arrived. The Sea Dragon shone a blue light as Zhao Hai felt the water around his body turn a lot heavier. Zhao Hai’s eyes flashed, this was ‘Condense’, the same spell that he used just earlier. It seems like the other party wanted him to see how they do the spell.

Then Zhao Hai wielded his staff as black gas appeared all around. This black gas wasn’t the ordinary Dark Mist of the Dark Mages, this was another kind of Dark Magic, Corrosive Mist’.

Chapter 636: Fierce Struggle

‘Corrosive Mist’ was one of the most commonly used Dark Mage spell. This magic can be both weak and strong. This spell was mainly dependent on the Dark Mage and on what type of poison he decided to use.

Corrosion magic was like this because it was a kind of growing magic. Magic is divided into low-level, high-level, and forbidden-level magic. And aside from these three classifications, there is also growing magic.

Growing magic is a magic that can be slowly upgraded. Take corrosion for example, when practicing this magic, a Dark Mage would find a certain toxin and then slowly refine it with magic. After that, whenever a Dark Mage uses corrosions magic, it would then have the properties of that toxin.

When a Dark Mage gets into a higher level, he can refine a stronger toxin, making the strength of his corrosion much stronger. The more formidable one’s toxin was, the more powerful the spell would be.

Zhao Hai’s corrosion spell was not simple, the toxin that he used was the one that the Space had. It was strong to the point that it can affect 9th rank experts. Most importantly, it can also become a water element technique. Although it still needed the dark mist, which was a gas, the poison can still diffuse into the water.

When the Sea Dragons entered this mist, their breathing suddenly became difficult, their minds turning dizzy. This startled those who were attacking Zhao Hai. Blue light came out of their bodies as they formed a protective layer around it. However, these experts didn’t expect that Zhao Hai’s spell would also corrode their protective layer. This shook the Sea Dragons, they immediately retreated soon after.

One must know that even ordinary barriers can still remain untouched by 8th ranks as long as it was a 9th rank that used it. But Zhao Hai’s corrosion can actually melt the protection of these 9th ranks. The Sea Dragons couldn’t help but stare at the strength of Zhao Hai’s ‘Corrosive Mist’.

The Sea Dragons might have retreated, but one of them actually stayed. He saw how formidable Zhao Hai’s corrosion was, but he still didn’t go back. Instead, his eyes flashed as blue light reinforced his body before he rushed straight into the mist.

However, when he broke through the mist, he didn’t see Zhao Hai in front of him. The person stared, before suddenly feeling alarms going off inside his head. He had a slight delay but was still able to promptly react as he blocked the attack from above using his trident.

Bang! A resounding sound was heard as the armor on the Sea Dragon’s arm was broken by Zhao Hai’s staff. The Sea Dragon let out a painful roar before he withdrew from the mist.

The scale armor of the Sea Dragons were derived from their own scales. The toughness of Dragon scales was famed throughout the continent. Nobody expected Zhao Hai to be able to crush it.

Dragon armor had many advantages, one of them was the fact that they were harder than most materials, making their defenses very good. However, their flaw was the fact that the scales were part of a Dragon’s own body. So after being crushed, the pain that was brought to them would be much stronger compared to when one’s full body armor gets crushed. Therefore, it wasn’t a mystery as to why the Sea Dragon gave out a cry of pain.

The Sea Dragon was just repelled not killed. And after Zhao Hai hit the arm of the Sea Dragon, another on appeared on top of his has he went to grab the back of Zhao Hai’s head. However, Zhao Hai’s managed to quickly turn his body and blocked the other party’s attack with his fist.

The Sea Dragon got excited, bodies of Dragons were always better compared to Humans. Even if they are both 9th ranks, bodies of Dragons still came on top. For Zhao Hai to use his fist to meet his attack, the Sea Dragon thought that Zhao Hai was just courting death.

Although the strength that Zhao Hai showed was quite formidable and revealed that he wasn’t just a Mage, but also a very strong warrior. Still, the Sea Dragon believed that Zhao Hai’s body wasn’t so strong that he can manage to survive this encounter.

However, the Sea Dragon failed to notice that Zhao Hai’s hand had already crystallized. Boom! When claw and fist met, the Sea Dragon cried in pain as he retreated immediately. Moreover, one could see that the Sea Dragon’s fist was oozing out blood. If Dragons didn’t have great bodies, his hand might have already been erased.

After repelling yet another person, Zhao Hai’s figure rushed back into the fight. He flew towards to the recently injured Sea Dragon while also waving his staff, causing a few ice spears to appear and attack the other Sea Dragons.

The Sea Dragon who just retreated didn’t think that Zhao Hai would attack. But since he was a 9th rank expert, his reaction also came quick. He didn’t retreat but instead charged to meet Zhao Hai. His eyes were blazing as he stared at the Human. His two fingers extended as an ice weapon appeared and attacked Zhao Hai. The Sea Dragons had started to use magic in order to deal with Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai saw the Sea Dragons’ movement, however, he didn’t stop his charge and just sidestepped the attack. The Sea Dragon didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would dodge like this. But he still followed up with a horizontal attack towards Zhao Hai’s chest.

However, this Sea Dragon had forgotten about Zhao Hai’s staff. Although the Blood Ghost Staff wasn’t lengthened, it still came up longer in addition to the length of Zhao Hai’s arm. Because of this, Zhao Hai’s attack had come in contact with the Sea Dragon much sooner, Bam! The scale of the Sea Dragon broke as the Sea Dragon felt extreme chest pain. The Sea Dragon preserved his breath, otherwise he might have already fainted.

But since his defense was still strong, he managed to survive Zhao Hai’s attack. His body was repelled back which also took him out of Zhao Hai’s attacking range.

Zhao Hai stood in place, and just as he was about to chase, a Dragon suddenly appeared. This person was different from the Sea Dragons, his body was covered golden armor, a style the same as the Sea Dragon but was thicker. Moreover, in addition to his sharp claws, this Dragon also had sharp protrusions on his two elbows. This made his elbows a good weapon for attack.

The Dragon used his elbow to attack Zhao Hai. The reason this Dragon stopped attacking the undead was because Zhao Hai was about to leave the magic formation. It was imperative to their plan that Zhao Hai stayed inside.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about this, so he was concentrating on meeting the enemy attack. Zhao Hai saw that the enemy attack was quite strong, so he retreated and slammed into a Sea Dragon that was close who, at this time, was on his way to grabbing Zhao Hai’s arm.

Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai waved his staff vertically, hitting the Sea Dragon upwards, blocking the Dragon attack. If the Dragon continued his attack, he would then be hitting the Sea Dragon, which was his ally.

As soon as Zhao Hai stopped, he felt a strong wave of pressure on his head. And behind him, another attack from the Sea Dragons arrived.

Zhao Hai flew down, then the staff on his hand suddenly lit up. One must know that it was very dark at the bottom of the sea, therefore the Sea Dragons had already adapted to the darkness. When Zhao Hai lit the area up, this caused to surrounding Sea Dragons to be blinded, feeling like their eyes were on fire. They gave a grunt as they stopped their attack and then turned back.

Ninth rank experts all have their Divine Sense, making them aware of their surroundings without even needing to see. However, if one was used to seeing and then were suddenly blinded, one would still have the instinct to retreat. The Sea Dragons were experiencing the exact same thing.

At this moment, another wave of light appeared, but this time, it didn’t come from Zhao Hai, but from the Mages of the Radiant Church instead. The Mages were using light magic in order to attack Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, then waved his staff as a Dark Mist appeared and surrounded him. The Dark Mist also began to spread, beginning to swallow the surrounding Sea Dragons.

The light magic of the Radiant Church’s mages disappeared into the mist. People said that light magic was the bane of dark magic, but this statement felt useless to Zhao Hai. Instead, he had just used dark magic in order to fight light magic.

Inside the mist, Zhao Hai fought with the swallowed up Sea Dragons. And due to the corrosive property of the mist, the Sea Dragons were simply unable to fight in their full strength.

However, although the Dark Mist can block sight, it cannot do the same thing to a 9th rank’s Divine Sense. Zhao Hai’s attackers were all 9th ranks, they didn’t need their eyes to know Zhao Hai’s location. So after going through the undead, the 9th ranks immediately bombarded Zhao Hai with both magic and battle qi attacks. They didn’t allow Zhao Hai to continue fighting with the Sea Dragon experts.

At this time, Luo Ying and the others were present, witnessing all that happened. When Luo Ying saw Zhao Hai’s predicament on the water curtain, her face immediately changed. But just as she was about to send help, several people suddenly appeared inside the hall.

Luo Ying stared before seeing that it was Laura’s group. Laura smiled faintly and said, “General, you don’t need to worry about Brother Hai. You can just stay here and watch. Those who are fighting him are all 9th ranks. If you send people over, they will just die. Just let Brother Hai handle the enemy.”

Chapter 637: Sacrificial Offering

Luo Ying stared at the eyes of Laura and the others. The Mermaids had some understanding about Zhao Hai. He was famous in the continent for his dark magic and the Mermaids have also heard that the Buda Clan possessed numerous 9th rank experts. However, nobody had heard that Zhao Hai was a 9th rank expert himself.

Having said that, even if Zhao Hai was a 9th rank expert, he was still against numerous people of the same strength. In this case, how could Zhao Hai’s group be confident? Where did this confidence come from?

But seeing that Laura and the others were unworried, Luo Ying couldn’t help but hesitate. Can Zhao Hai really deal with so many 9th ranks on his own?

Luo Ying stared at Laura, Laura understood what Luo Ying was thinking, so she smiled faintly and said, “General, rest assured, even if Brother Hai can’t kill them, he can just escape whenever he can. There’s no need to worry.”

Luo Ying nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll keep our eyes on Mister. If Mister needs help, we can send them at any time. My Azure Dragon Snail can deal with several 9th ranks with no problems.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “General, rest assured, if such a time arrives then we’ll be impolite. General, we’ll be taking our leave.” Then the group vanished.

Luo Ying was stunned at what just happened, her expression couldn’t help but change. She thought and reckoned that Laura and the others might also have Space divergent abilities.

Luo Ying knew about the rumors of Zhao Hai having a space divergent ability. However, she hasn’t heard anything about Laura and the others having it as well. It seems like Zhao Hai has a lot of things that he kept secret from the continent.

Luo Luo looked at the place where Laura and the other vanished, then she said, “I’ve been with them for a good number of days. I didn’t expect them to be this formidable.”

Luo Ying smiled faintly and said, “Silly thing, if they don’t want you to know then there’s no way for you to find out. I think they revealed themselves this time because they wanted us to feel at ease, otherwise, they wouldn’t have shown us their ability. It seems like Mister Zhao Hai has the capabilities to deal with the enemies this time.”

Then Dashan, who was at the side, said, “General, the Sea Dragons have accumulated a lot of 9th ranks. This might place us in a dangerous predicament, I think we should send word to Her Majesty, have her send a few 9th ranks to aid us.”

Luo Ying shook her head and said, “That’s no good. Don’t see our situation as dangerous. In fact, it is Her Majesty that’s in peril right now. You might not have seen it, but the current situation stemmed from the fact that the Sea Dragons wanted to deal with Mister Zhao Hai first before stalling us here, having us ask for help from Her Majesty. And when Her Majesty sends help, the Dragons would then have the opportunity to attack Mermaid Island.”

Dashan stared for a moment before his expression changed, “Then Her Majesty is in danger. General, don’t we have to send word back to the island?”

Luo Ying shook her head, “I don’t think it’s necessary, you don’t have to worry about it. When I told Her Majesty that the Sea Dragons and the Dragons were working together, she should’ve already prepared her defenses.”

Dashan nodded and didn’t talk anymore. Then Luo Ying turned her gaze back to the water curtain. Zhao Hai didn’t know this, but this water curtain wasn’t any ordinary magic, but a kind of magic unique only to the Azure Dragon Snail. After refining this thousand year old snail for countless years, it managed to gain this ability. Luo Ying named this curtain the ‘War Curtain’.

Once they left the Azure Dragon Snail, it would be impossible for the Mermaids to use this magic again. If Zhao Hai showed Luo Ying his monitor, Luo Ying would surely be surprised.

Luo Ying’s gaze turned to the water curtain just in time to see a scene that made him surprised. Zhao Hai was now fighting with the Sea Dragons once again, but now he seems to be having the advantage.

Zhao Hai’s magic prowess was now in full bloom, he used all kinds of magic, including fire magic. Even if fire was heavily affected by the water, Zhao Hai still managed to use it, moreover, its power was also quite strong.

In addition, Zhao Hai had close combat ability that was much stronger than the Dragons due to his body being able to crystallize. Therefore, although he was besieged, he still managed to dominate.

Luo Ying stared blankly at the water curtain, she didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this strong. She saw with her own two eyes how Zhao Hai hit a Dragon and managing to repel the latter. This made Luo Ying speechless, making her doubt if those were real Dragons at all.

At this point, the Sea Dragons were much more surprised than Luo Ying. They also didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this strong.

Zhao Hai’s current mood was very good, the blood inside his body was burning. He didn’t know that fighting actually felt this good.

He was now getting acquainted to fighting more and more, he seems to be born to fight. This wonderful feeling made Zhao Hai crave fighting even more.

But the extraordinary thing about this was the fact that even if his blood was boiling with excitement, his mind stayed calm, allowing him to always react to the attacks of the enemy and counter them. This unusual and contradictory feeling made Zhao Hai even more excited.

On the other hand, the people from the Sea Dragon side were getting startled more and more. In the past, they had heard about Zhao Hai’s clashes with the Radiant Church, but now, they seem to understand that Zhao Hai was much more difficult to deal with than they had thought.

The Sea Dragons and Dragons didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this fierce. Moreover, they didn’t think that he would have the body that wasn’t any worse than a Dragon. Their initial expectation of Zhao Hai being a mage was crushed at this point. This huge discrepancy from their imagination made them startled.

The thing that the Sea Dragons and the Dragons failed to notice was the people of the Radiant Church going outside of the formation, surrounding the two as well. Then these people took out a set of magic formations and placed them on the ground. After that, they shackled their bodies to the formation as they took a knife and slit their wrists. Blood immediately spurted out and fell on the magic formation. Then these people started to loudly recite magic incantations, and it seemed like this process would take a long time.

But along with their incantation, a layer of barrier slowly rose from those magic formations and surrounded not only the Dragons, but the Sea Dragons as well. Even the people from the Radiant Church were enclosed, including Joshua.

When they saw this barrier, Alex and Ao Ke stared before they stopped and turned their gaze towards Joshua. Alex loudly said, “Joshua! What are you doing?!”

Joshua’s mouth didn’t stop saying the incantations, the barrier slowly turned white as its pressure became stronger and stronger. This was not true pressure, but a kind of force that pressed down on Zhao Hai like a mountain.

Ao Ke loudly shouted as well, “Joshua! What do you want to do?”

Joshua had finished saying his spell. So he looked at him and said, “I said that Zhao Hai must fall here at all costs. This is a magical formation called ‘Sacrificial Offering’. You guys along with me will be sacrificed and no one can escape. All of us will be dedicated to God today.”

Ao Ke’s face couldn’t help but change, “Joshua, don’t talk nonsense. If you do this, the Dragons certainly wouldn’t let you off.”

Joshua coldly smiled and said, “Your Dragon race is the servant of our Radiant Church’s God. For the sake of God’s purpose, it’s understandable that you are to become a sacrifice. Everybody here will die, and the Dragons wouldn’t be aware of how you died.”

Zhao Hai codly smiled and said, “Didn’t you try dealing with me with this method last time? I seem to remember that it failed. If I leave right now, all of you will die while I survive.”

Joshua sneered and said, “The last time only had a few people, we have a lot more this time. And Zhao Hai, where you are right now is a magic formation that locks the space. You wouldn’t be able to use your space ability even if you wanted to. It’ll become useless.”

Zhao Hai’s expression changed before it turned into bewilderment. This was because he can feel that he hasn’t lost contact with his Space. This meant that the Radiant Church’s formation was useless.

Alex and Ao Ke’s expressions changed as well. They didn’t expect Joshua to be this ruthless, even sacrificing everyone here, including his own.

At this moment, Zhao Hai smiled and then said, “Now that your magic has been set, this meant that you people aren’t able to move anymore. I won’t be overstaying then, everyone, goodbye.” Then his body flashed as he disappeared only to reappear outside the barrier.

When Joshua saw Zhao Hai appear outside the formation, his expression couldn’t help but change as he turned into a maniac and said, “This is impossible, how can you leave? This is impossible! Our magic formation has been set. This is impossible!!! Zhao Hai come back here!!!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he looked at Joshua and sneered, “This thing is useless to me. If I want to come in, then I can come in. If I want to leave, then I can leave whenever I want. You simply don’t have the ability to block me. Hehe. The ‘Sacrificial Offering’ is about to start. All of you are going to die.” Then Zhao Hai turned around to leave.

At this time, Alex suddenly shouted, “Mister, wait!”

Zhao Hai stared, then he turned his head to Alex and said, “A Sea Dragon? What do you want? Also want me to come back in? It’s useless. I can leave whenever I want.”

Chapter 638: Resolution of the Sea Dragons

Alex shook his head and said, “No, Mister has misunderstood. I want to ask Mister to help us exit this place.”

Zhao Hai looked at Alex, then he sneered and said, “And why would I help you exit? You go and wait for your death here.” Then Joshua’s magic was completed. A strange pattern that looks like the sun appeared on top of the barrier, with lines connecting to Joshua’s magic formation. Then some crept towards Joshua as his body lost moisture, becoming very dry. After that, his body withered as as sprinkled towards the seabed.

Joshua and the others disappeared, however, in their original position were several balls of light. Then as if sensing other lives, the balls extended some yellow lines towards the Dragons and the Sea Dragon experts.

Seeing this situation, Alex immediately went to the barrier and talked loudly to Zhao Hai, “Mister, please help us. Our Sea Dragon Race will forever submit to you!”

Zhao Hai stared, his figure vanished from the barrier along with Alex and the others. There was no question that Alex had been taken out of the barrier by Zhao Hai.

Just as Alex and the others came out of the barrier, the barrier suddenly left a dazzling golden light before it turned violent. Ao Ke and his men had forever vanished inside the barrier, everything inside has turned into ash.The Radiant Church’s formation disk had similarly vanished as well. A huge depression appeared on the seabed and when the light vanished, seawater immediately filled it in.

Although Zhao Hai had taken Alex and the others out of the barrier, Alex and the others’ bodies were still tied down by vines. No matter how the Sea Dragon experts struggle, they actually cannot break it. This vine had extraordinarily strong tenacity.

Naturally, they can’t break it, these vines were from Cai’er. Cai’er had the strength of a God, the 9th rank Sea Dragons couldn’t stand a chance.

Zhao Hai looked at Alex and said, “Are you saying the truth? Will the Sea Dragons really submit to me? If you dare lie to me, I will kill you right now.”

Alex didn’t struggle, he looked at Zhao Hai and smiled bitterly, “I won’t dare deceive Mister. Mister’s abilities are exceptionally high. We Sea Dragons simply didn’t have the courage to lie to you. I’ll be candid to Mister, our Sea Dragon Clan had never been part of the Dragon Clan. The reason why we cooperated with the Dragons and the Radiant Church was because we only want our Clan to be stronger. But if we are all killed here, we would be losing all of our 9th rank experts. At that time, the Sea Dragons would surely be destroyed by the Mermaids. So I ask Mister to help us.”

Zhao Hai looked at Alex, the latter seems to be telling the truth. To be honest, Zhao Hai admired the strengths of these Sea Dragons. If he can put the Sea Dragons to good use, then it would be a good thing.

Seeing that Zhao Hai has not spoken, Alex couldn’t help but get flustered, he quickly said, “Mister, please believe me. I am willing to make a Blood Oath. I’ll give you my loyalty forever. Our Sea Dragons will forever be loyal to you.”

Zhao Hai looked at Alex, then with a serious voice he said, “Good, as long as you swear by Blood Oath, then I will let you go. But your Sea Dragon Clan couldn’t live in the seas any longer. I will take you to another place where you shall live.”

Alex stared, he lowered his head and said, “Yes, Mister.” Then Alex bit his own tongue and performed a Blood Oath. Then Zhao Hai released the Sea Dragons. The other experts looked at Alex and didn’t speak. Alex sighed as he turned his head and said, “Mister, please give us two days. After two days, our whole clan would be concentrated on Dragon Palace. We shall be waiting for Mister there.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll give you two days. If you dare violate your pledge in this two days, then don’t blame me for being impolite.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure vanished.

After Zhao Hai left, a Sea Dragon approached Alex and said, “Patriarch, will we really submit to this Zhao Hai?”

Alex sighed, “We don’t have any choice other than to submit. Don’t forget about our present situation. Those Radiant Church fellows are surely a group of lunatics. But I believe that it would be impossible for them to succeed with Zhao Hai as their enemy. Even if the Divine Race were to descend, I still think that they wouldn’t have any way of getting their hands on Mister Zhao Hai. You might not have noticed, Joshua had mentioned the Divine Race a couple of times, but Zhao Hai’s expression didn’t even change a bit. I believe that Zhao Hai might have already known about this a long time ago. Also, haven’t you noticed his current prominence in the continent?”

Just as Alex’s voice fell, the Sea Dragons stared for a moment, then one of them said, “Patriarch, you saying that Mister Zhao Hai’s relationship with the other races was a cooperation for resisting the Divine Race?”

Alex sighed, “I’m almost certain about this. Don’t forget how good Mister Zhao Hai’s relationship with these races are. He had met with the Dwarves, become the Crown Prince of the Beastmen, and now he is helping the Fishmen. Doesn’t this explain the issue? One must know that these races were the same races that had participated in the last war with the Divine Race. Although those races had close to no relationships right now, Zhao Hai had become their middle man.”

The people here were 9th rank experts, so they were aware of the matters that Alex was talking about. The suddenly understood what Alex was thinking. If Zhao Hai could unite the races, then they wouldn’t be powerless against the Divine Race. Didn’t they just repel the Divine Race last time?”

Alex looked at his clansmen and said, “From what just happened, we can see that the Divine Race doesn’t treat us as people, but as puppets instead. In their eyes, we are less than servants, we are slaves, people who they could just sacrifice whenever they want. Letting such people rule us meant that we won’t have a good future. It was better to rely on Mister Zhao Hai and join them in resisting the Divine Race. Even if we were to die, we can still hold our heads up high and fight proudly instead of giving up our dignity as Dragons and becoming slaves to the Divine Race!”

After Alex said this, the bodies of the Sea Dragons couldn’t help but shake. Dragons have their own pride, their own dignity, so they only submit to those stronger than them. But if they do submit, they still must receive the appropriate respect and not work as a slave for another person. Alex’s words just touched the deepest recesses of their minds.

Alex looked at them and said, “The reason why we cooperated with the Dragons and the Radiant Church was first, because we are a branch of the Dragon Clan, so it wouldn’t be great for us if we decline. Second, because of the Divine Race, since our ancestors were once their servants. Third, we want to use this opportunity to expand our race, making the Sea Dragon Clan replace the Mermaids and becoming the ruling power of the sea. But it seems like that point will remain impossible. With Zhao Hai’s help, the Mermaids would always hold the upper hand. At the same time, the Divine Race simply doesn’t treat us as people, and only sees us as ants. We don’t need to help them if we are only going to discard our dignity as Dragons. We can submit to Zhao Hai and hope that he doesn’t treat us as trash. But if he does, our family will fight him until all of us perishes. The Dragons of the continent had forgotten their pride. Now, they have become brainwashed by the Radiant Church, just like Joshua. But we aren’t them, so we can go and have our own way.

The other Sea Dragons nodded, then Alex turned his head and said, “Go and return to your own families, move the clansmen to the Dragon Palace. In two days time, let’s see how Zhao Hai will treat us. If he respects us, then we’ll submit to him. But if he doesn’t, then our clan will just fight him until we die!”

The other Sea Dragons loudly shouted before they left. Alex turned and headed back to Dragon Palace. When he entered the palace, he immediately summoned Illac back. Since Illac was the commander of the army, he wasn’t able to participate in the battle against Zhao Hai. He didn’t know about what happened, only the massive amount of energy that eliminated the Radiant Church people and the Dragons. What Illac saw was Alex saying a few words to Zhao Hai and then to the other Sea Dragons before they all left. This made Illac sense that something was going on.

While Alex was sitting in the hall, Illac walkedin. Alex looked at Illac, he waved his hand and said, “Sit.”

Illac gace Alex a salute, then he took the seat closest to Alex. Then Alex looked at Illac and said, “Illac, you are the smartest person in our clan. Did you manage to see what is going on?”

Illac looked at Alex, then as though he was not sure, he said, “I thought about something, but I really am not sure if I’m right.”

Alex nodded, “Tell me.”

Then Illac said, “According to what I just saw, the Radiant Church had used some type of self destruct magic, intending to perish together with Zhao Hai. But their anti-space magic formation had become useless to Zhao Hai. Since Zhao Hai can run away at any time, and Patriarch is afraid that the Clan would perish. The Patriarch had reached some sort of agreement with Zhao Hai.”

Chapter 639: Two Days

Upon hearing Illac, Alex couldn’t help but let out along breath, “It looks like training you to become the next Patriarch didn’t go to waste. You’re really smart, Illac. The agreement we came up with is submission. If we don’t submit to Zhao Hai, how else would be save us? You have guessed right.”

Illac looked at Alex and said, “Patriarch, did the Radiant Church really self-destruct? Did they eliminate everyone inside?”

Alex’s face couldn’t help but change, “It’s not self destruct magic, it’s ‘Sacrificial Offering’. If not for Zhao Hai,  we would’ve become part of that sacrifice.”

Illac’s face turned complex, then he said, “Does Patriarch want to fight the Divine Race with Zhao Hai?’

Alex looked at Illac, he knew that Illac had already guessed the gist of the matter. Speaking to a smart person really is very convenient. He nodded and said, “It’s better to die in battle rather than living without dignity. Wasn’t this our Dragon Race’s pledge?”

Illac’s face looked a little bit better. He stood up and gave a salute to Alex, “I’m going to disband the army. The sharks had always been our followers, i will make things clear to them. I believe that the Mermaid wouldn’t be too harsh on them.”

Alex looked at Illac and said, “Good, if nobody dies this time and our clan continues to survive, the next Patriarch would be you.” Illac held a happy expression, then he gave Alex another salute before turning back to leave.

At this time, Zhao Hai was currently inside the Blade Scale Whale, looking at Alex in the monitor. Laura and the others were sitting by Zhao Hai’s side. When Illac left the hall, Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, it seems like everything is done.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Let’s go see General Luo Ying.” Then Zhao Hai commanded the Blade Scale Whale to head towards the Azure Dragon Snail and arriving at the hall.

The water curtain was already gone and Luo Ying was waiting for Zhao Hai anxiously. She didn’t know whether Zhao Hai survived or not. When the Radiant Church used their magic, the image in the water curtain suddenly turned incomprehensible. Because of the magic, the image became muddy, and it became impossible for Luo Ying to investigate. The only thing she could do was wait.

Although she was confident in Zhao Hai, she was still extremely worried. This was because this fight was too important. If Zhao Hai suffers an accident, it would not only affect the Mermaid Clan, but also the future war against the Divine Race. If Zhao Hai falls, then the Mermaid Clan would become criminals in the eyes of the other races in the continent.

At this time, Zhao Hai had brought Laura and the others to the Hall. Luo Ying couldn’t help but relax. She immediately asked Zhao Hai to sit down and said, “Mister, what happened? I was worried to death!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “General can rest assured, everything is alright. I’ll have the general to ask the army to hold for two days. After two days, everything will be clear.”

Luo Ying looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What does Mister mean?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Two days later, everything will go back to normal. General can be relieved, the Sea Dragons would not attack anymore. Moreover, their army might also disband in these two days. After that, I’ll have to leave the work of quelling the remnants of the rebellion to the General’s hands.”

Luo Ying gawked, then her two eyes flashed, she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Is Mister telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I didn’t lie. I also ask the General to prepare. It’s possible that the Shark Tribe might be a little troublesome.”

Luo Ying looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister can rest assured, I shall wait for two days. Then after that, I’ll see for myself what you mean.”

Zhao Hai stood up, then he bowed to Luo Ying and said, “Then I’ll have to thank the General for your trust. I;m quite tired, so I’ll go back and rest first. After two days, the General shall get your answers. The only thing that I can guarantee to the General is the fact that you won’t be seeing Sea Dragons in the sea in the future.”

Luo Ying stared, she couldn’t understand what Zhao hai said, “Mister’s meaning is?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Everything will be clear in two days.” Then he lead Laura and the others to leave.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s departing back, Luo Ying was utterly confused. She frowned and then muttered, “Two days later? What would happen in two days? I’m becoming more and more curious now.”

After Zhao Hai and the others returned to the Space, they opened the monitor and looked at the situation of the Sea Dragon Clan. Zhao Hai was able to peer through the Sea Dragons’ situation at a far place because when he talked to Alex, he had also placed his staff down in Dragon Palace in order to monitor the area more clearly.

The Sea Dragons had now truly dissolved their army. In fact, most of the people from the Sea Dragon Army wasn’t willing to fight in this battle. But due to the strength of the Sea Dragons, they had no other choice but to participate. Now that the Sea Dragons had disbanded their army, these people immediately turned around and ran.

However, the sole trouble came from the Shark Tribe. The Sharks were extremely willing to join the Sea Dragons in this rebellion. This was because they also want to use this opportunity to enhance their status in the sea. Therefore, when the Sea Dragons decided to end everything, the Sharks immediately expressed their refusal.

But the Sea Dragons had a different mindset right not, they didn’t have their initial ambition. They knew that if they go on with the battle, it would be impossible for them to continue. So they disbanded their army, so that the Mermaids wouldn’t be hard on the other tribes.

The Shark Clan was extremely unwilling, they were adamant on killing the Mermaid Clan. They wanted to replace the position that the Whale tribe held. However, the Sea Dragons had started to lose heart, which was something that the Sharks didn’t want to happen.

At this time, the Sea Dragons became impolite. The Sharks certainly have ambition, but they don’t have the strength. If the Sea Dragons allow the Sharks to continue, then the Fishman Race would be placed into further turmoil. And this situation would affect their future fight with the Divine Race.

On the minds of the Sea Dragons, since they were now fighting the Divine Race, then they would have to preserve all the resources necessary to resist the descending gods. Whether they were killed or not, they had sworn their allegiance to Zhao Hai, so the ambition of the Sharks must be extinguished. After all, this wild tribe was brought up by them.

Illac already thought that the Sharks would cause a ruckus once he announced the dissolution of the army. Therefore, Illac led an army of Sea Dragons to kill. The Sharks were totally not the Sea Dragons’ match. The Sea Dragons took the lead in extinguishing the Shark tribe. The remaining Sharks were those who were initially honest. Therefore, the image in Zhao Hai’s mind didn’t appear.

Zhao Hai didn’t think that Illac would be able to handle things this easily. He didn’t even give the Sharks the chance to cause trouble. This made Zhao Hai look into Illac more. Illac had been their opponent, and it seems like Illac wasn’t someone simple.[1]

Seeing that the matters in the Sea Dragon side had been solved, Zhao Hai felt relief. Then he adjusted his monitor to see the situation back at Mermaid Island. Zhao Hai didn’t know when the Dragons would go and attack the island.

When the monitor changed, ZHao Hai saw that everything was normal. There weren’t any signs of a fight. It seems like the Dragons had yet to make their move.

However, Zhao Hai can also notice some difference in the place. The leisurely mermaids on the island can no longer be seen. What replaced them were Mermaids who wore armor, fully prepared for the battle ahead. There were also other 9th rank Fishmen present. It also looks like the 9th ranks at the Azure Dragon Snail had also returned to the surface. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel relief upon seeing how prepared the Mermaids were. Even if the Dragons were to attack, they surely wouldn’t be able to affect the situation in the sea.

Seeing no developments in Mermaid Island, Zhao Hai turned his vision to the Dragon Clan. To be honest, Zhao Hai liked the look of Dragon Palace. It was a naturally occurring coral reef, this reef should also be considered to be quite a treasure.

Additionally, Zhao Hai also took a liking to the Sea Dragons. The Sea Dragons were the beings that were closest in appearance to a Chinese dragon. This made Zhao Hai regard the Sea Dragons very much. Therefore, he decided that since Dragon Palace was their home, he wouldn’t be taking it away from them.

Zhao Hai was prepared to arrange the Sea Dragons to the Space. The Sea Dragons were also some type of magic beast whose strengths were formidable. If they go to the Space, then it might be possible for them to turn loyal towards Zhao Hai.

At the same time, Zhao Hai had also found appreciation towards the guts of the Sea Dragons. Sea Dragons were people who would rather die than lose their dignity, such people were worthy of respect.

Two days passed in a blink of an eye. Luo Ying had also been holding back her troops all this time. But she also knew that there wouldn’t be any huge fights going on. After all, the Sea Dragons had already dissolved their army. They would just wait until Zhao Hai gives them word, then they can go to the other Fishmen and had them go back under the rule of the Mermaid Clan.

At the same time, Sea Dragons had also been arriving at Dragon Palace. The Dragon Palace was their main residence, so not many people went too far from it. But since they were going to battle, the young and old people had stayed back. This time, their entire Clan had gathered.

The main residence of the Sea Dragons was initially Dragon Island. They have been living at that place for many years. But ever since they had found the Dragon Palace’s reef, Dragon Island had only become their root. This time, they abandoned their root and gathered to Dragon Palace. The Sea Dragons weren’t many, only about 10 thousand people. Naturally, these 10 thousand people were all pure Sea Dragons. They also had near 100 thousand Lesser Dragon Race people, which also joined the move.

* * *

Of course he isn’t simple. You’re just using an OP army xD

Chapter 640: Attitude

Alex told his clansmen about the situation, they truly are worthy to be Dragons. The people of this clan did indeed have hard bones. After listening to Alex, it didn’t matter whether they were old or young, nobody in the hall flinched. Everyone was in one mind, not one of them wanted to work as a slave.

Zhao Hai saw the response of the Sea Dragons while he was inside the Space. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile over the two days, he was liking these Sea Dragons more and more.

Upon seeing that the Sea Dragons have arrived, Zhao Hai knew that it was time to show himself. He didn’t use his Space and just used his Blade Scale Whale to head towards Dragon Palace.

Dragon Palace was currently surrounded by Sea Dragons as well as their lesser relatives. Although they had less strength than the Sea Dragons, these Lesser Dragons still had the blood of Dragons within them. Their strength was still quite formidable.

These Lesser Dragons were guarding the surroundings of the Dragon Palace. All of them looked at Zhao Hai with discerning eyes. These people were absolutely loyal to Dragons. Even though they weren’t Dragons themselves, they were still descended from them. Among the Sea Dragons were their parents, so how could they betray them?

Even if their status wasn’t high in the Sea Dragon Clan, they were still representatives of the clan to the other tribes. No other tribe would dare move them. Moreover, whenever the Sea Dragons need anything, the ones who would act would be these Lesser Dragons. This stemmed an interdependent relationship between the two of them. Although most of them were the children of two Lesser Dragon parents, they still couldn’t let go of their relationship with the Dragon Race.

These Dragons held their word with extreme importance. Once they said that they would submit to Zhao Hai, then they would submit to Zhao Hai. However, if Zhao Hai treats them like a slave, then these Sea Dragons would surely fight even at the risk of their life.

Therefore, these Lesser Dragons were quite hostile to Zhao Hai. They wanted to know how Zhao Hai plans to treat them.

Zhao Hai’s Blade Scale Whale arrived at Dragon Palace. Since there was no water inside the Palace, Zhao Hai stopped his whale right outside of the place. Then he took Laura and the others to see the people waiting inside. All of the Sea Dragons were currently looking at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t dare become arrogant, he bowed to the people and said, “Zhao Hai Buda requests an audience with the Patriarch of the Sea Dragon Clan.”

The Sea Dragons gawked at Zhao Hai’s manners. Their face changed, but one of them said, “We have met Mister Zhao Hai. We have been sent by the Patriarch to welcome Mister.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then I’ll have to trouble everyone.’ Then he walked towards the hall with the others. Zhao Hai’s attitude was seen by all the Sea Dragons as well as the Lesser Dragons. Seeing Zhao Hai’s manners, they couldn’t help but change their view of him by a little bit.

Alex had told them about how powerful Zhao Hai was. He also told them that if Zhao Hai didn’t have a bad attitude, he wouldn’t have been worried that they would be humiliated. However, he was desperate at that time so he didn’t have any choice. Because of this, their expectations of Zhao Hai was different that what he was showing right now. This made the Sea Dragons and the Lesser Dragons very surprised.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these as he arrived inside the hall along with the group of Sea Dragons. The coral was very huge and had underwent a lot of renovations by the Sea Dragons. There were many palaces inside the entire Dragon Palace and they held no difference compared to the palaces in the continent, it might even be more beautiful compared to those. The palaces of the continent didn’t have as much pearls and crystals as those inside Dragon Palace.

Zhao Hai followed the Sea Dragons towards the Dragon Temple inside the Palace. This Dragon Temple was the largest hall inside the Dragon palace. It was also the place where Alex and the elders decided to greet their guest. Usually, Alex wouldn’t be here, he would only be inside his palace.

Before the entrance of the hall, two Sea Dragons stood guard. When the two saw Zhao Hai arrive along with the other Sea Dragons, both of them announced, “Mister Zhao Hai has arrived!”

Then the two turned their heads to Zhao Hai and bowed, “We invite Mister Zhao Hai to enter.” Then they shoved the door of the Great Hall open. Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude to the two before leading Laura and the others towards the hall.

As soon as he arrived inside the Hall, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. There were a lot of people inside the hall, some of these were elder Sea Dragons while some were 9th rank experts of the Sea Dragons. It can be seen that the people present here didn’t have ordinary status.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he took several steps forward before bowing to Alex, who was currently on a high platform,  and said, “Zhao Hai has seen Patriarch Alex.”

Alex gawked at Zhao Hai’s attitude, he returned the bow and said, “We welcome Mister Zhao Hai. Mister, the entire Clan is already here. I don’t know how Mister plans to deal with us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Sea Dragons and the Mermaids wouldn’t be harmonious after this. I’m afraid that the Sea Dragons don’t have a place in the seas anymore. I have my own place which also has a sea. That place didn’t have any Fishman in it, only a few marine magic beasts. I want to move the Sea Dragons to that place. What does Patriarch think about this?”

After hearing Zhao Hai speak, the hall immediately turned into a sea of murmurs. These Sea Dragons have lived in this sea for generations. And they were also clear that this endless sea was the only large sea in the entire Ark Continent. They had not heard of any seas that didn’t have a Fishman tribe and only having marine magic beasts.

Alex frowned as he looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister, are you joking with me? I don’t think there’s such a place in this world. If there is really such a place, then we’ll be extremely willing to move.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Then, I’ll have to ask the Patriarch to have all of the Sea Dragons and the Lesser Dragons be inside Dragon Palace. After that, I’ll be sending you to that place.”

Seeing that Zhao Hai seems to be serious about this, Alex couldn’t help but nod. In any case, things have already reached this point. Even if he wants to hide, he wouldn’t be able to hide. In addition, Zhao Hai was very respectful to them, his attitude was not bad. Therefore, Alex turned to the people outside the hall, “Have everyone come inside the Palace.” Then the people outside issued a sound before going off. Before long, the Sea Dragons and Lesser Dragons had come into the Palace. Although they didn’t know about what was happening, they still didn’t ask any questions.

After talking to Alex, Zhao Hai just stayed there, standing calmly. He even closed his eyes as though he wasn’t curious about anything. On the other hand, Laura and the others were sizing Alex up as well as everyone inside the hall.

Before long, people from the outside had sent word, “Reporting to the Patriarch, everybody has entered Dragon Palace.”

Alex nodded, then he turned to look at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai slowly opened his eyes and then said, “Great, now I ask the Patriarch to have a look outside.”

Alex was confused at what Zhao Hai just said, “Look outside? What does Mister mean?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “We already arrived at the place that I said. I want to ask the Patriarch to see if he likes it.”

Alex stared, he was thinking that Zhao Hai might be cracking a joke. But Zhao Hai’s expression told him that he was serious. Although he was confused, he still walked outside.

After Alex went out, he couldn’t help but gawk. This was because even if there were still underwater, Alex can feel that they were somewhere different.

Dragon Palace had already stopped at its position for a long time. Therefore, Alex was quite familiar about its surroundings. However, the reefs and plants that was currently around him had become different. Alex can be sure about this due to the magic beasts swimming around the coral reefs. He can see that these things didn’t have any traces of Fishman activities.

At this time, Illac also arrived, he was in charge of keeping the other Sea Dragons and Lesser Dragons in control. Therefore, when Alex saw Illac, he immediately said, “Illac, what’s all this about? How come everything around us changed?”

Illac was stern faced as he shook his head. “Patriarch, I have no idea. When I asked everyone to go inside the Dragon Palace. I only felt a small fluctuation on the water around me. Then the scenery changed.”

Alex turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, where is this?”

Zhao hai smiled faintly and said, ‘This is the Sea Dragons’ new home. As for what this place is, I ask the Patriarch to join me to the surface. I’ll explain everything to the Patriarch.” When the Sea Dragons entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard. It seems like the Space was considering the Sea Dragons as an intelligent race, so it cannot subdue them immediately. Zhao Hai didn’t care, since the Sea Dragons have entered the Space, everything else will be easy to do. He had already calculated what would happen.

Zhao Hai joined the Sea Dragons as they slowly went to the surface. Upon reaching the surface, Alex and the others were shocked. This wasn’t the endless sea, they knew this because they can see land in a not so far place. On this land were plants and houses. The atmosphere of the place was also very different from the Ark Continent.

Alex turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this, where are we?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This is my Buda Clan’s territory, my Clan’s root. This is also my domain. Here, I am a god!”

Alex was confused at Zhao hai, “Mister, you mean that including the sea, everything here belongs to the Buda Clan? We aren’t in the continent anymore?”

Chapter 641: Turning Misfortune into a Blessing

Alex looked at Zhao Hai and said, “So we’re in a completely independent space, and this space belongs to Mister?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at Alex and said, “Right, this independent Space is mine. I shall bestow this place’s ocean to your Sea Dragon Race. This ocean would be your domain, you can kill the beasts that live here save for a few that I personally raise.”

Alex turned his head towards the Space’s endless sea. He turned to Zhao Hai and then suddenly knely on one knee, “Alex has met the Master!”

Alex understood that this Space was a place where the Sea Dragons wouldn’t be able to blow any winds. However, why do they need to gain control here, is there a better place in the world? The whole ocean was theirs, nothing greater can satisfy them. So Alex called Zhao Hai ‘Master’. This was akin to making Zhao Hai the king of their Clan. In the past, Alex had always called Zhao Hai ‘Mister.”

Zhao Hai looked at Alex and said, “Get up, then next time, I would prefer being called Young Master. Since your Sea Dragon Clan decided to side with me, then you’ll have to prepare yourselves to battle the Divine Race as well as the two chess pieces that they have, the Radiant Church as well as the Dragons. These people are on my kill list. Your Clan used to be in this list too, but since you’ve become my followers, you’ve been saved. If I ever need your assistance in the future, you must now decline. Understand?”

Alex replied, “I understand, Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he summoned Cai’er and said, “This is Cai’er, the Space’s manager that I had appointed. Normally, I won’t be able to be inside the Space all the time. If you need anything, just look for her. If I have something for you to do, then Cai’er will be the one looking for you. However, I won’t be needing you for the majority of the time. You can just live your lives here as you see fit.”

Alex nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master. Actually, the Dragon Palace is already enough for us to live in.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then that’s good. You settle yourselves in while I go and see Luo Ying. The situation of the seas needs to be stabilized. Its fortunate that you’ve failed, otherwise the Divine Race would gain the continent’s endless sea as their backing, allowing them to attack and retreat without any consequences. Right, Alex, did you know about any matters of the Divine Race? Do you know when they’ll attack?”

Alex shook his head and said, “I’ll be unfair to the Young Master, I really have no information regarding this. Although we are in a cooperation with the Radiant Church and the Dragon Clan, we have only been in contact for a short amount of time. For this reason, I was still able to hire oneself to the Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Forget it, you go and settle your people down. Cai’er will tell you which magic beasts you aren’t allowed to touch. The others, you can hunt and kill. Alright, then I’ll be taking my leave.” Then Alex bowed to Zhao Hai before Zhao Hai’s figure vanished.

At this time, Cai’er looked at Alex and said, “Were you the one that submitted to the Young Master?”

Alex looked at Cai’er. To be honest, Alex really couldn’t identify what race Cai’er belonged in. If Alex considers people with the same size as Cai’er, then he would be able to name a few Fishman Tribes. However, it was evident that Cai’er wasn’t a Beastman. He had never heard of a race that looks like Cai’er.

However, Alex still nodded and said, “It’s me.”

Cai’er coldly snorted as a pressure erupted from her body. Alex was stunned where he stood as he looked surprised at Cai’er. Alex didn’t expect that Cai’er would have the ability to freeze a 9th rank expert. Also, Alex knew that it didn’t matter if he goes to his Armored Form or True Form, he would still be suppressed just like this, it was too scary.

Cai’er looked at Alex and said, “I don’t care about what the Young Master promised you. But if you dare disrespect the Young Master, then I will make sure that you will be the one to suffer first. The Young Master is a good person, and is someone that is easily approachable. But if you dare to be betray him, I will eliminate your Sea Dragon Race. Take this, it’s the list of all the magic beasts that you’re not allowed to touch, it’s a small list. You can do what you want with the other beasts. Talk to me if you need anything.” Then her figure vanished.

When Cai’er left, Alex finally relaxed. He felt like a baby facing a 9th rank expert under Cai’er’s pressure. He was simply not on her level. Alex completely believed Cai’er, if Cai’er did want to extinguish him, then she could do so at any time. And if she were to destroy the Sea Dragon Race, then she wouldn’t take too long to do  it. Alex couldn’t help but wipe a cold sweat while thinking about these.

Alex finally understood that when Zhao Hai was fighting with others, he wasn’t using his full strength. If he did use all of his strength, then him enemies wouldn’t have survived for long and played around with Zhao Hai. Alex knew that Zhao Hai did this in order to deal with the Divine Race. And from listening to Zhao Hai, Alex understood that Zhao Hai might have been even more informed regarding the Divine Race than him. This made Alex feel glad that he had surrendered to Zhao Hai. Otherwise, Zhao Hai would surely have destroyed all of them.

Alex now had a change of heart regarding Zhao Hai, he immediately changed his mood as he returned to his own people. At the same time, he also told his people about what he had found out about Zhao Hai, which made the little dissatisfaction in the clansmen’s hearts completely disappear.

This time, they had really turned a misfortune into a blessing. The didn’t even need to be the kings of the sea, they don’t need to snatch anything they need, the whole sea was theirs. Aside from those that Zhao Hai prohibited, everything else was free game. The materials here can also be used at will, which was definitely a great news for them.

Zhao Hai didn’t care much about these, although the Space has raised a lot of marine beasts, it was actually still quite short in life. It was good that the Sea Dragons are present, making the Space’s sea much more livelier.

When he teleported the Sea Dragons, he also made the effort in absorbing the surrounding seawater and obtaining a lot of tiny marine lifeforms. These things managed to balance the sea’s food chain. One could say that the Space’s sea has become complete.

The reason why the Space couldn’t subdue the Sea Dragons was perhaps because it was the first time that the Space had absorbed creatures like them.

The Sea Dragons had entered the Space in their Human Form, therefore, the Space had no method of subduing them. But if they were to turn into their Dragon form inside, things might become different. Zhao Hai was curious about this and wanted to look for an opportunity to find out.

But for the Lesser Dragons, the Space was naturally impolite. The moment they entered the Space, they were immediately subdued. The Sea Dragons didn’t know about this.

Zhao Hai came out of the Space and immediately went to Luo Ying’s Azure Dragon Snail. Luo Ying was currently waiting for Zhao Hai, she was paying attention to Zhao Hai’s interaction with the Sea Dragons. If the Sea Dragons dared to attack Zhao Hai, then she would immediately send an army to destroy them.

But what happened next made Luo Ying surprised, Zhao Hai and the Sea Dragons suddenly vanished right in front of her. Disappearing without a trace, nothing was left behind, this made Luo Ying startled.

However, Luo Ying believed that this was Zhao Hai’s doing, it was impossible for the Sea Dragons to have the capability to perform such a feat. If the Sea Dragons really did have something like this, then they should’ve already used it to deal with Zhao Hai, they shouldn’t have waited to use it until now. Only Zhao Hai can cause such a huge group to disappear in front of her.

Therefore, Luo Ying wasn’t very worried as she sat still inside the Azure Dragon Snail, waiting for Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai arrived, Luo Ying immediately asked him to sit down and said, “Did Mister deal with the Sea Dragon Clan?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No, I just sent them to another place. Saving them from being shunned in the sea. The General can rest assured.”

Luo Ying nodded, and didn’t ask about this anymore. Then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I just received word from Her Majesty. The Dragon Clan and the Radiant Church had sent 9th rank experts to attack Mermaid Island. However, they had been repelled by Her Majesty. The enemies lost some of their experts as well. We believe that they won’t dare to do such a thing again. The Fishman Race has been saved.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, good. Then General should go and appease the Fishman tribes. I can’t help you with these matters. I’ll stay in the sea for some time and collect some marine magic beasts as well as some unique plants before going back to the continent.”

Luo Ying quickly said, “Mister shouldn’t be quick to leave. Her Majesty had sent word that since Mister has helped us greatly, she wanted to invite you over to Mermaid Island. I ask Mister to consider giving us face.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, then before I return to the Continent I’ll stop by and visit Mermaid Island.”

Then Luo Ying smiled and said, “What magic beasts does Mister want? Our Fishman Race might be able to help Mister with this. We have been living underwater for generations, there aren’t a lot of things in the sea that we cannot find. If Mister can tell us, then we shall certainly do our best to acquire it.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I appreciate the General’s words. However, my target is the Devil Octopus. I’ll get a couple of them before I head back. I can handle it myself.”

When Luo Ying heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but stare. Then her face changed as she said, “Does Mister really want to get those Octopus? That’s too dangerous. Those magic beasts are living in an extremely cold environment. People who go there are instantly frozen to death. It wouldn’t be a good idea if Mister were to go there.”

Chapter 642: Demon Realm Aura?

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The General doesn’t need to worry about it. There are ways of dealing with the chilling cold. Those octopus really do have a great use to me. If General has anything else to do, then I won’t be holding you back. You don’t need to worry much about me, I can manage on my own.”

Luo Ying knew from Zhao Hai’s words that there was no way for her to stop him, so she didn’t say anything else. After all, Zhao Hai has already revealed his strength, he had the qualifications to do whatever he wants.

After exchanging a few more words with Luo Ying, Zhao Hai left the Azure Dragon Snail. He was now ready to catch those Devil Octopi. These beings grow up to be 9th ranks, almost not any worse than Dragons. This fact made Zhao Hai very curious.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately go catch some octopus after leaving Luo Ying. Instead, he returned to the Space and observed if the Sea Dragons have been properly settled in.

However, he didn’t go and personally see the Sea Dragons and just looked at them through the monitor. Upon seeing that they had settled down quite well, Zhao Hai felt relief. After all, they were in the sea, at the same time, they also had all the room that they want.

Then Zhao Hai switched the image on the monitor to see Mermaid Island’s situation. He didn’t expect the Dragons and the Radiant Church to be prompt in their attack of the Island. Zhao Hai wanted to see the state that the Island has been turned into.

When he saw Mermaid Island, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. It wasn’t destroyed due to the attack, it was the exact opposite, he couldn’t see any traces of battle. It seems like nothing happened, this scene showed Zhao Hai how strong the Fishmen were.

From Luo Ying’s words, Zhao Hai knew that the ones who attacked Mermaid Island were the people from the alliance between the Dragon Clan and the Radiant Church. But there were only limited ways in order to attack the island. First was by using ships, but this was impossible. Aside from the Buda Clan, no other power would be able to navigate the sea in order to head towards Mermaid Island.

The second method was by flying, which can be done by the Dragon Clan. However, it would be impossible for them to have the tolerance to ferry people over on their backs. Therefore, the attack on Mermaid Island could only be done by 9th rank experts.

Being assaulted by 9th rank experts but not leaving a trace of battle was a testament to the might of the Mermaid Clan. Ninth rank experts aren’t easy people to deal with.

Seeing that nothing happened on the island, Zhao Hai felt relief. He was now preparing to catch a Devil Octopus, then he would go and see the situation of the Soul Sucking Reef. He wanted to find out why Fishmen weren’t able to leave that place.

As soon as he searched through these two places, Zhao Hai would return back to the Continent. But before heading back to land, he still needed to pay the Mermaid Queen a visit. And while doing so, he would try and see if he can learn about their art of Water Refining. Zhao Hai really wanted to learn the technique.

After recalling all of these in his mind, Zhao Hai determined his itinerary. First he would catch a Devil Octopus, this was a simple task, the trench was just a short distance away. Although theses beasts were 9th ranks, it was impossible for them to pose a threat to Zhao Hai. He plans to catch two of these beasts and see if they can upgrade the Space.

Upon thinking it through, Zhao Hai returned to the Space to rest for the entire day. The next morning, he had the Blade Scale Whale proceed towards the Devil Octopus’ domain.

In the sea, this trench has its own special name, it’s called Devil’s Trench. It was because it was the place where the Devil Octopi reside, and at the same time, because it was a place that was very dangerous. Therefore, the Fishmen decided to name it as thus.[1]

It didn’t take long before Zhao Hai reached the mouth of the trench. This trench didn’t have any special appearance, it looks just like an extremely deep canyon. However, Zhao Hai can feel the cold aura being released by the trench. It was enough for a person to shiver with fright.

Zhao Hai is a 9th rank expert, and for someone of his level to feel this explains that this place was something dangerous.

At this time, Cai’er’s voice was suddenly heard, “Young Master, I can feel the aura of the Demon Realm here. Especially inside that trench, the Demon Realm aura that I can feel there is very thick.”

Zhao Hai stared, then his expression changed as he said, “Really? Can you really feel the Demon Realm in this trench?”

Cai’er came from the Demon Realm, she was a plant that grows normally there. Because of that, she was extremely familiar to the aura of that place. Zhao Hai trusted her words, but he was not willing to believe it. If that was really the case, then this trench might be associated with the Demon Realm. This meant that this place might become a battlefield in the future.

Cai’er insisted, “Young Master, there really is an aura of the Demon Realm here. And it gets stronger the deeper you go in.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, it seems like coming here was a good idea. Let’s go and take a look.” Then he directed the Blade Scale Whale to go down to the bottom of the trench.

The deeper they went, the darker the surroundings became. Zhao Hai was now 500 meters into the trench, and not a single ray of light can be seen here. Zhao Hai can see some beasts in the distance, but they were different from those that he had seen in the surface. From what he can see, these beasts looked more fierce and aggressive compared to those at the top.

At this time, Laura and the others had arrived at Zhao Hai’s side together with Cai’er. Since the place might be related to the Demon Realm, Zhao Hai had Cai’er come out and talk to them about that place. Only Cai’er had concrete understanding about the Demon Realm.

Upon seeing these magic beasts, Cai’er turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, these magic beasts are already demonized.”

Zhao Hai was confused at what Cai’er just said, “Demonized? What’s that?”

Cai’er replied, “The Demon Realm has a very unusual toxin. This toxin will start to affect beings and change their appearances. Look at these beasts for example, it was possible that they are only ordinary magic beasts. But because they were subjected to the aura of the Demon Realm, they had turned into their current form. They had become more formidable, however, they also turned more aggressive due to the toxin.”

Zhao Hai extended a spike from the Blade Scale Whale and captured a small fish. This small fish was only the size of Zhao Hai’s palm. However, a third of its body was its head, and two thirds of this head was its giant mouth. This small fish was still struggling and would oftentimes open its mouth, revealing its saber-like teeth. It also flashed a blue radiance, showing that its attacking strength was quite strong.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and sent the small fish to the Space. He wanted to see how the Space valued such things. And just as the fish entered the Space, a prompt was heard, “Seriously polluted mutant fish has been detected. Such organisms have strong survivability, strong attacking ability, strong defensive ability. Extracting its toxin, changing organism’s temperament. Integrating properties into lifeforms in the Space. Toxin has been combined to the Space’s insecticide. Enhancing all toxic lifeforms in the Space. Increasing survival capabilities of the lifeforms inside the Space.”

This prompt informed Zhao Hai that the Space has identified these creatures as ‘polluted’. To be honest, it was quite a suitable classification.

Zhao Hai grasped other mutant magic beasts inside the trench and had them sent over to the Space. The prompt that he heard was similar, this made Zhao Hai lost interest in these mutant magic beasts.

At this time, Zhao Hai had already penetrated 1000 meters deep into the trench. Everything around him was pitch black. If they didn’t have a monitor, then they wouldn’t be able to see anything outside.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and saw that the mutant magic beasts were getting fewer and fewer. But the strengths of those who were present has been getting stronger and stronger. They also looked more and more fearsome.

At this time, Laura suddenly issued an astonished tone. Then she pointed to a place outside the Blade Scale Whale as she said, “Brother Hai, look, there seems to be a bright spot there.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he turned to look at what Laura pointed out. Currently there was a light that repeatedly flashed. In this jet black environment, it looked like a single small star.

However, Zhao Hai seemed to notice that this star had gotten brighter and brighter, it seems like it was approaching them.

Zhao Hai immediately looked at the monitor and saw a strange fish appear in front of his eyes. It looked terrifying, it was about two meters long, its body was covered with spikes. It also had a pair of small red eyes, its mouth was big and had fangs of different lengths. Most importantly, on the top of its head was a long spike, but it seems like it wasn’t hard but instead was soft of which an organ was hanging. Zhao Hai felt strange since this organ was the one that was flashing its lights. It looks just like a faulty lantern.

At this time, Zhao Hai saw another small fish approaching. Zhao Hai was curious about this small fish, he didn’t know why it was swimming towards them. Then suddenly, the small fish went towards the flashing organ of the strange fish. And just as the small fish approached the organ, the strange fish suddenly opened its mouth, its tongue flew out and stretched. Before long, the small fish was nowhere to be seen.

* * *

Named it as Death Pit before, I’ve changed it.

Chapter 643: Core and Level Up

Zhao Hai and the others stared at this strange fish. This fish actually uses this method to hunt, it‘s quite strange.

Zhao Hai and the others curiously looked at the fish as it drew near to them. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get careful, he wanted to see what this fish intends to do, does it want to attack them?

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried much about it. Although this fish had uncommon strength, one shouldn’t forget that the Blade Scale Whale was a 9th rank undead beast. This strange fish would be unable to place a dent on the whale’s body.

It didn’t take long before the strange fish arrived by Zhao Hai’s side. But what made Zhao Hai surprised was the fact that the fish didn’t attack the whale. Instead, it just stayed by its side, looking like it was acting as an escort for Zhao Hai and the others.

Zhao Hai was confused at what the fish just did, “What’s going on? Did this guy suddenly become docile? But that doesn’t seem to be the case.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, these fishes shouldn’t be considered to be marine beasts at this point, they were now more like beasts from the Demon Realm. And as long as they have a bit of the Demon Realm within them, they won’t be attacking us. This is because my aura can provide these beasts with survival. Therefore, they should be very respectful towards me.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that it would be like this, “Really? I didn’t think Cai’er would be this formidable. This is fantastic.”

Cai’er proudly smiled and said, “Young Master can rest assured, as long as we are in a place with Demon Realm Aura and I’m by your side, nobody would dare attack our group.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Good, good, then I’ll be relying on your cover. Let’s go and see what’s going on here.” Then he directed the Blade Scale Whale to dive deeper into the trench.

However, Zhao Hai still took the time to get a few fishes as he can. After all, these were creatures that weren’t seen before, there was no loss in acquiring a few more of them.

When Zhao Hai and the others reached about 2 kilometers deep, the strange fishes left while another batch of fishes came over. These fishes looked more fierce and seemed to be much stronger than the ones before. They had the forms of a fish version of an alligator. But they didn’t attack the Blade Scale Whale, instead, they escorted them one kilometer down before another batch came and escorted them for another kilometer.

Zhao Hai now knew about how Cai’er was seen by these beasts. She seems to have a status that was much better than any Human Emperor. As soon as these beasts feel her aura, they would immediately come and escort her, perhaps due to their innate instinct.

Zhao Hai and the others have now dove about ten thousand meters deep, however, they still weren’t able to see a Devil Octopus. Zhao Hai had looked around and cannot see these octopus, and at the same time, they were already 10 thousand meters under the sea yet the bottom of the trench was still out of sight. How deep was this trench? Zhao Hai was completely unsure.

But Zhao Hai didn’t worry about it as they continued diving downward. The magic beasts that they met were getting bigger and bigger while they looked more and more ugly. Most importantly, it seems like their strengths were increasing as well. The magic beasts at this level were already comprised mostly of 8th ranks. And they were quite numerous as well, if these beasts were to head to the sea, the Fishman Race wouldn’t be very peaceful.

This also aroused Zhao Hai’s anticipation. At this point, he was extremely curious about how deep this trench was. Zhao Hai had commanded the Blade Scale Whale to head straight down to the point where it was almost heading vertically downward.

They have dived for another five kilometers when a giant octopus suddenly appeared in Zhao Hai’s monitor. The octopus was swimming sluggishly. It looks just like any octopus, however, it was very big. If one includes its tentacles, this octopus would be 100 meters long.

What surprised Zhao Hai was its appearance. The entire head of this octopus was black, but behind its body was a white image of a devil. It was a large image, almost fully occupying the back of the octopus’ head. Its tentacles were white as well, looking like a Devil’s beard if one were to look at it.

All of this added up made the octopus look very scary. Although it didn’t have any spikes like the other fishes, it still instilled fear on those who looked at it.

However, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone when he saw this beasts. It was because this was the beast that he was looking for, the magic beast Devil Octopus.

Without waiting for Zhao Hai to make a move, the Devil Octopus started to swim towards them. Then it arrived at the Blade Scale Whales side and acted as an escort just like the other magic beasts. This made Zhao Hai stare, but he relaxed soon after. The Demon Realm aura this deep into the trench had gotten very strong, so naturally this octopus should’ve also been demonized.

But Zhao Hai didn’t stop, in addition to finding this beast, he also wanted to see the cause of the Demon Realm Aura in this trench.

After going down for another 1 kilometer, the Devil Octopus that followed Zhao Hai had now numbered to about 100. What made Zhao Hai startled was the fact that all of these 100 Devil Octopus were 9th ranks. This number of experts would cause a commotion if revealed to the continent. Except for Zhao Hai, nobody would be able to match this number of experts.

Zhao Hai’s face couldn’t help but turn ugly. If these octopus were to escape the trench while taking the mutant beasts along with them, then the endless sea would be placed into turmoil.

At this moment, Zhao Hai suddenly noticed a group of black gas in the distance. Zhao Hai gawked at this black clump. It wasn’t very big, only about 100 meters wide. However, Zhao Hai actually can’t see through this gas.

Zhao Hai immediately had the Blade Scale Whale swim towards the black gas. At the same time, he turned his head to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, what do you think this thing is? Why do I feel that its the source of the Demon Realm aura?”

Cai’er nodded and said, “Young Master, it is indeed the source of the Demon Realm Aura. This should be a type of High Level Demon Core.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Core? What is that?’

Cai’er answered, “Demon Realm beasts have cores, it is the source of power for all the residence of the Demon Realm. The cores of High level beasts are extremely formidable. From what I can see, this should be a core of a God-ranked magic beast. Even in the Demon Realm, this thing is a treasure. These God-ranked beasts aren’t any weaker than God-ranked experts, they may even be stronger, at the same time, they also have much longer lives than God-ranked experts. And when they die, these beasts would look for a place where nobody would be able to find them, making it extremely hard to find their cores. This God-ranked core is extremely useful to God-ranked experts. They can use this core in order to manufacture weapons and also absorb it and make its power their own. Although some energy would be lost in the process of absorption, it was still a huge help for the God-ranked experts. After all, increasing one’s strength upon reaching God-rank is very difficult.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he still couldn’t help but feel startled. He didn’t think that a Demon Realm’s God-rank beast’s core would arrive at this place. At the same time, this core actually managed to change an entire landscape on its own, creating these formidable 9th rank Devil Octopus.

The Blade Scale Whale had already penetrated through the clump of black mist. Then Zhao Hai saw a fist-sized black bead. This bead was peacefully floaiting there, about a meter above the bottom of the trench.

Zhao Hai made the whale go right by the bead as he carefully examined the bead. However, besides being black, there wasn’t any other aspect to be seen.

Cai’er then said, “Young Master, absorb this thing into the Space. I think it would be extremely useful in upgrading it.”

Zhao Hai stared, then nodded as he absorbed the bead into the Space. And just as the bead entered, a prompt was heard, “Extremely strong energy has entered the Space. Absorbing energy. Upgrading the Space’s environment. Incorporating upgrades to the Host’s Body. Improving lifeforms inside the Space, lifeforms has been strengthened. Robotic objects in the Space has been upgraded. Spatial Water and Spatial Soil has been upgraded. Space’s toxin has been improved as well. Space upgraded to level 60. Hoping for the Host’s continual effort.”

Zhao Hai was wild with joy, he didn’t expect the bead to upgrade the Space. This is a very fantastic outcome. Moreover, Zhao Hai had felt that his body has been strengthened after the level up. Zhao Hai immediately turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, how do you describe my present strength?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, your current strength is the same as that of a God-ranked expert. You can now claim to be God-rank. This is really good, I can feel that my strength has been improved as well. Young Master, you can now buy 10 more backgrounds. However, they can only be ordinary backgrounds.”

Zhao Hai was ecstatic, “Good! Fantastic! Ordinary background is till good. Go buy a sea-based background for me. Then place those mutant beasts on that. I want a background that would specialize in breeding these creatures.”

Cai’er noddded as she immediately took action. Then Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and the others, “This is great. Now that the Space has levelled up, I can now plant more powerful plants so that you can upgrade your strengths. Even if we can’t turn you into God-ranked experts, you would still be able to tower above normal 9th rank experts.”

Chapter 644: Water Refining Technique

Laura smiled and said, “That’s great! Now we don’t have to go to the Elven Forest in order to level up. Brother Hai, you should get those plants sorted out, have Grandpa Green and the others level up.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he absorbed the Devil Octopus before heading back to the surface. As long as he sees a Devil Octopus, Zhao Hai would immediately absorb it to the Space. As a result, Zhao Hai had accumulated about 300 Devil Octopus. This turned the Octopus’ population in the trench into zero.

Zhao Hai felt that this was good. After all, if these octopus were to stay here, they would be a continual threat to the Fishman Race. But Zhao Hai still had some worries. Although the trench had a very strong Demonic presence due to the core, it still hadn’t spread outside the trench. At the same time, the inhabitants of the trench were all  spotted outside. Why was this possible?

Zhao Hai was thinking about these while the Blade Scale Whale continued to go upward. Every magic beast that they had come across were all grabbed by Zhao Hai.

The whale slowly went up the trench before they had finally reached the exit. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but give out a long breath. Although they got huge harvests in the trench, Zhao Hai and the others still felt down while inside there due to the lack of light. It was good that they were now approaching the brighter parts of the sea.

At this time, a pressure suddenly dawned on them. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get stunned, he didn’t know what was going on. Where did this pressure come from?

Zhao Hai immediately turned on the monitor to see what was happening. At this time, the Soul Sucking Reef suddenly emitted a black energy that formed into a magic formation. This formation pressured the trench making Zhao Hai and the others feel as if a mountain was pressing down on them. No matter how hard the Blade Scale Whale swam, it was still unable to progress further.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised upon seeing this. One must know that when the Space levelled up, the undead got an upgrade as well. Compared to average 9th rank experts, these undead were a notch better. And because of the Demon Aura, they all became much stronger. But after all of these, the whale was still being suppressed by a formation. This magic formation wasn’t simple.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry about it, he had the whale dive back down as the pressure vanished along with the magic formation.

Zhao Hai was stunned as he turned to Laura and the others, “What’s going on? Why does the formation appear when we go up and vanish when we go back down?”

Laura and the others were clueless about this as well, however, Meg suddenly said, “Young Master, when we got down, we weren’t stopped. Only when we came up were we blocked from exiting. I think it’s because we had been tainted with a bit of the Demon Realm’s aura. Maybe this formation’s purpose was to block those Demonized creatures.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he thought carefully about it. It seems like this was the case. They weren’t able to hear about this from the Fishmen, but judging by the fact that no mutant beasts were able to get out of the trench meant that this formation had the function to block them from exiting. It might be just like Meg said, the formation was something that was sensitive to Demonic aura. When they got close to the exit, the formation had detected some of the aura that had stuck to them and thus promptly blocking them from leaving the trench.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at Meg in surprise. When Meg was with everyone, she would basically stay quiet and didn’t express her opinions too much. Therefore, one would see that it was Zhao Hai and the others that were doing well. All Meg was doing was taking care of Zhao Hai and the others.

But Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting Meg to talk at this time. It’s not that she wasn’t smart, Meg just doesn’t want to fight for attention. Usually, Zhao Hai and the others would have taken care of everything before needing her help, so she just kept a low profile. Seeing her express herself, Zhao Hai felt a little bit happy.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh and said, “I think you’re right, Meg. Hahaha. Don’t be reserved too much in the future. If you have anything to say, just say it. Alright?”

Meg nodded, which made Zhao Hai smile. Then he waved his hand as light magic and water magic cleansed their bodies. Then he commanded the Blade Scale Whale to head upwards. This time, nothing stopped their progression. The whale swam continuously before passing through the mouth of the trench and going back to the battlefield.

When they came out, Zhao Hai became surprised, this was because the Mermaid Clan’s Azure Dragon Snail was still there. They had been inside the trench for about four days. The trench wasn’t shallow, and after heading down, they still went out of their way to collect magic beasts, making the time they spent inside quite long. Zhao Hai and the others were 9th rank experts, so it wasn’t an issue for them to go sleepless for a few days. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting the Mermaids to be still here. Why would they stay?

At this time, Zhao Hai saw some black spots coming out of the Snail and was swimming towards him. Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and identified the other party as Dashan. When they arrived by the Blade Scale Whale, Zhao Hai immediately went to the whale’s mouth and greeted, “Captain Dashan, why are you still here? Weren’t you going to deal with the other Fishmen tribes?”

Dashan gave Zhao Hai a bow and said, “The General was worried for mister, so she had me wait here for your arrival. However, the General also had sent some parties on order to deal with the important matters, so everything is going according to plan. The General had left word that if you come out, she wanted you to see her.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, I also wanted to apologize to the General for making her worry.” Then he had the Blade Scale Whale swim towards the Azure Dragon Snail.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others had arrived inside the Azure Dragon Snail’s main hall. Luo Ying was already waiting inside along with Luo Luo. Other than the two of them, nobody else was present inside.

Seeing that Zhao Hai had arrived, the two immediately stood up. Then Luo Ying said, “Mister, please sit down. How was the trip? Did everything go well?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Very well. I can tell the General that the Devil Trench wouldn’t be dangerous anymore. You might even go there and settle. However, I suggest you don’t do that. It is extremely pitch black inside.”

What Zhao Hai said was reasonable, although the seabed was also dark, there were still some luminescent shellfish and plants to illuminate it. However, the trench had no light at all, it was filled with depressing black color all around it.

Luo Ying smiled and said, “Then I’ll have to thank mister. But I’m afraid that nobody would want to settle there either. The endless sea is too big, so there are still places that are much better than the trench. Right, what is mister going to do now? Will you be returning to the Continent?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he shook his head and said, “I wont, I also want to see what the Soul Sucking Reef is all about.”

Luo Ying wrinkled her brow upon hearing Zhao Hai. She doesn’t understand, Zhao Hai was obviously a Great Noble of the continent, he should have a lot of matters to be taking care of. So why must he risk his life in all of these locations? Casually going to dangerous places was too unreasonable.

After thinking about it, Luo Ying couldn’t help but get the courage to ask Zhao Hai, “What does mister want to see in Soul Sucking Reef? You should know that our Fishman Race has always been investigating the place. However, we still weren’t able to find anything despite doing it for generations. At this point, we won’t dare going there anymore.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod and said, “I know about this. But it’s possible that I may get something that is very important to me. So I want to go there and search for it. After that, I’ll return to the continent.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t lying, he really wanted to see how the reef’s magic formation could get that strong. It can actually pressure the mutant magic beasts for many years. This made Zhao Hai very curious about it.

If there was really such a formation, then Zhao Hai would naturally want to take a look at it. If he studies this formation, then it would be similar to gaining a weapon to battle the Demon Realm in the future. .

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Luo Ying knew that she couldn’t persuade him, so she just said, “Then I’ll be waiting for mister’s return. If mister encounters any danger, don’t hesitate to retreat.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, General can feel relieved. Right, I have a matter to ask Her Majesty and I might need the General’s help.”

Luo Ying stared, she was curious about what Zhao Hai wanted help with, “What does mister need? I shall immediately send word to Her Majesty.”

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “I want to ask Her Majesty if it was possible for me to learn your Mermaid Clan’s Water Refining Technique. Rest assured, I certainly won’t spread it to other people.”

Luo Ying stared when she heard Zhao Hai, then she forced a smile and said, “Mister, I think you are misunderstanding something. My Mermaid Clan’s Water Refining Technique is not a secret. The reason why this technique is only used by a few was because its requirements are very high. In addition to having the person be gifted in controlling water, the water used for the technique needed to be special as well. The technique would need high quality water in order for it to succeed. Our Mermaid Clan has our own innate technique that can purify water, making sure that the water is as high quality as possible. Because of this, only our race was able to use this Water Refining Technique. If other people don’t have the means to purify water, then it would be impossible for them to use this technique.”

Chapter 645: Soul Sucking Reef

Zhao Hai was calm while listening to Luo Ying, but was actually very excited deep inside. Luo Ying said that others weren’t able to use this method of refining due to the lack of water purifying methods. However, this wasn’t a problem for Zhao Hai. One shouldn’t forget that Zhao Hai has Bubble, the source of Myriad Water. Bubble was more than qualified to be used as a helper for Water Refining.

After Luo Ying finished talking, Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “I ask the General to still convey my request to Her Majesty. I want to use this Water Refining technique as a reference. The General should know how much importance I place in this war with the Divine Race, but when the war starts, we would need to have a lot of weapons. Relying on Human and Dwarf artisans simply wouldn’t do. Therefore, I want to add this Water Refining Technique to the equation and see if it can help with the demand.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Luo Ying immediately nodded and said, “Mister can rest assured, I will surely take responsibility for this matter. Our Water Refining Technique isn’t a secret, it just needs appropriate preparations. However, I can assure you that this method has its own brilliant methods. Mister, you can handle your matters first. When you come back, I will have the Water Refining technique to give you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, then I’ll have to trouble the General. I’ll be heading to the Soul Sucking Reef now, farewell.”

Luo Ying stood up and gave Zhao Hai a salute, “I wish for Mister’s good luck.” Zhao Hai returned the gesture and then smiled faintly before turning around to leave.

After returning to the blade scale whale, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Brother Hai, I didn’t expect that obtaining the Mermaid Clan’s Water Refining Technique would be that smooth.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Mermaids do care about the other Fishmen, but since no other race had the ability to purify water, they weren’t able to pass this technique around. Even if they spread the method, nobody would be able to use it. But we have Bubble, although I get angry every time I see him, at least we had found a use for him.”

When Laura heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but chuckle. Bubble was really an interesting thing, he was quite bold and loved to mingle with the ladies. Seeing Bubble makes Zhao Hai feel discomfort.

However, Laura and the others didn’t care about this. In their eyes, Bubble was like a small pet that was just a bit smart. Bubble has also been like this, so it was impossible to change him. More importantly, Bubble makes Zhao Hai jealous.

To be honest, Laura and the others loved seeing Zhao Hai being jealous of Bubble. It was because this meant that Zhao Hai really did treasure them.

Lizzy chuckled as well and said, “Big Brother Hai, do you think that this Water Refining Technique would be something useful?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “With our current techniques, this Water Refining Technique should be of use. Additionally, Father might want to research it. When we get the technique, perhaps he would find some avenues of which to improve on.”

Lizzy naturally knew that the father that Zhao Hai meant was Karen. The man was a research maniac, therefore Lizzy didn’t become confused and just nodded.

Then Zhao Hai said, “I want to head to the Soul Sucking Reef to look for the thing that made it suppress the things inside the Devil Trench. If we can find out about it, then it might prove useful in our fight against the Demon Realm.”

Laura nodded and said, “Soul Sucking Reef is truly formidable. Its quite a distance away from the trench, btu it can still sense the Demon Realm’s aura and suppress it. At the same time, it also imprisoned the mutant beasts of the trench.”

Megan wrinkled her brows and said, “But I haven’t heard of such a formation in this world. Elder Brother Hai, you should ask Luo Ying and see if this formation was something that they had set up.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “There’s no need to ask, it definitely wasn’t them. Otherwise, Luo Ying might have already told us about it when I informed her of my intention to investigate the place. It’s also because of this that made me curious about who had the ability to set up this formation or maybe why the reef came into existence.”

Megan nodded, if the Mermaid did indeed set up the reef, then they should have already informed the other Fishmen.

There were two places that the Fishmen couldn’t understand. One of them gave Zhao Hai a God-rank magic beast core which upgraded the Space to level 60, gave Zhao Hai ten more slots for backgrounds, and gave him plants that can become God-ranked. This was a huge harvest.

As for the other place, they still haven’t investigated it yet. That place was full of mystery and Zhao Hai didn’t want to rashly charge through it. So Zhao Hai decided to take a break and maintain a good condition for himself.

Zhao Hai and the others returned to the Space and had a hot bath before taking ample rest. After that, they immediately rode the blade scale whale and headed towards the Soul Sucking Reef.

Zhao Hai hadn’t told Green and the others about the Space’s upgrade yet. Although the Space had raised some Messenger Fishes, their number wasn’t very large. Therefore, Zhao Hai wanted to wait until all of the Fishman race’s matters got dealt with before telling Green and the others everything as well as handing them some Messenger Fish. In any case, they had gone uncommunicative before, and it wasn’t a big deal.

Zhao Hai and the others sat in the Space while the blade scale whale swam towards the Soul Sucking Reef. They were eager to know what is inside the place.

It didn’t take long before the blade scale whale entered the reef. Its insides were beautiful, there were strange shapes everywhere that would attract anyone’s gaze. The inside was like a totally different world, completely detached from the world outside. One might even see the shapes of some of the continent’s animals on the corals.

Zhao Hai and the others forgot about their initial purpose of coming here as they gawked at the beautiful scenery. The reef was that beautiful. Besides the reef, there were also a lot of plants as well as small fishes inside. The bodies of these fishes had attractive patterns on them making it extremely adorable to the women. Laura and the others were nudging Zhao Hai to catch some of these fishes.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t decline, he caught some fishes and placed them in the Space. Laura and the others then had a glass tank and filled it with seawater. Then Zhao Hai placed the small fishes on the glass tank for them to look at.

Laura and the others were looking at the fishes, swimming around in a very attractive manner. This made Zhao Hai force a smile.

Zhao Hai turned his attention back to the monitor, he wanted to see where they were at, but this made his startled. When Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai, they immediately turned their attention to the screen. The Laura said, “Brother Hai, what’s wrong?” Zhao Hai didn’t speak as he pointed to a corner of the screen. Zhao Hai enlarged the image and showed Laura and the others what was wrong.

On the screen, Zhao Hai’s group was represented by a small red while the other fishes were green dots. What made Zhao Hai surprised was the movement of their red dot. The red dot was circling around one area, not deviating from this circular course. It was as if it was trapped by something.

This astonished Zhao Hai, one shouldn’t forget that the blade scale whale is an undead, so it didn’t depend on its eyes for perception. However, it was still trapped, it seems like this Soul Sucking Reef is living up to its reputation.

Laura and the others also saw what was going on. They couldn’t help but stare in amazement, they didn’t expect that they would experience such a thing.

Zhao Hai immediately came out of the Space and went to the blade scale whale. He sat inside the body and felt that everything was going normal. The whale seems to be going forward and the scenery was constantly changing, he couldn’t see any duplicates in what he saw.

Laura and the others also went out with Zhao Hai. When they saw the situation, they were shocked, Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what’s all this about?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I also don’t know. But I’m sure that this is related to that magic formation. No need to think about it too much, what we have to do is go forward.” Then Zhao Hai didn’t mind the outside scenery as he directed the blade scale whale to go in a straight line. When the whale finally left its circle path, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “Did the scenery change?”

Laura shook her head and said, “No, it just felt like the whale took a small turn. Everything else didn’t change.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he now understood how formidable this formation was. It can actually bewitch not only people, but the undead as well. Otherwise, the blade scale whale wouldn’t have been duped.

However, this had made Zhao Hai even more curious. He now believed that what he would obtain in this place wouldn’t be very simple.

Zhao Hai continued to direct the whale to go in a straight line. A short while after the whale breaks out from its circular path, it would return to going in circles, which would then prompt Zhao Hai to change its course. Fortunately, Zhao Hai had the monitor, otherwise he would be trapped inside this reef.

Chapter 646: Tai Ji Eight Trigrams Chart?

After crossing through nine traps, the whale had finally maintained its straight direction without going in circles once more. However, Zhao Hai can actually feel anxiety. He felt that the thing that he was looking for was already quite near.

Laura and the others were anxiously staring at the monitor as well. The screen was now bigger than it was back in the trench. Back there, the monitor can only look at about 100 meters away, it seems like its ability was suppressed by the God-ranked core.

The situation at this time was very different, but it wasn’t anything better. It can still only display about 200 meters in front.

However, this also managed to make Zhao Hai happy. After all, when the monitor was suppressed, they had managed to acquire a God-ranked core, making the Space level up in the process. Although the suppression was weaker, only about 200 meters, the thing inside should still managed to nudge the amount required by the Space to level up.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also become careful. They hadn’t met an attack the last time because of Cai’er’s presence. However, the situation this time is completely opposite. The place where they are now suppresses the Demon Realm aura. If they were to meet an attack, then it was possible for it to be quite dangerous. Therefore, Zhao Hai had Laura and the others enter the Space while he stayed inside the whale, urging it to go forward.

After going forward for several minutes, Zhao Hai suddenly felt a very formidable aura wash over him. He immediately made the blade scale whale stop and had some undead fishes to take a look. Nobody from the outside can see the undead, so they can exhibit all of their abilities here.

At this time, a long figure arrived. Zhao Hai looked at this figure and knew that it was a 9th rank magic beast. When that long figure saw Zhao Hai, its tail immediately flashed as a blue light travelled towards the Blade Scale Whale.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the opportunity to dodge, the blue light came too fast. When he saw the light, it had already hit the blade scale whale. The whale felt the shock, but there was no further damage.

Zhao Hai identified the long figure as a 9th rank electric eel. It discharged a very powerful shock. However, electric attacks were completely ineffective against the undead.

The electric eel’s electricity might be a problem for other magic beasts, but the undead were different. The undead couldn’t be paralyzed, making the electric eel’s abilities virtually useless.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as his undead threw themselves towards the electric eel. The eel didn’t expect that his attack would be useless. One must know that the intellect of 9th rank beasts were no different than normal humans. So when it saw the undead, it immediately dodged as it discharged even more attacks, but to zero effect.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at his undead, he knew that the electric eel’s attacks wouldn’t work. It might be strong against beasts, but for the undead, it doesn’t really affect them.

Sure enough, the electric eel found itself at a dilemma. When he stopped attacking, it was already too late, he was now surrounded by the undead. Naturally, the undead weren’t polite, one of the swordfish undead attacked the eel to death.

Zhao Hai then released a black gas that enveloped the electric eel. When the gas vanished, the eel turned into an undead creature.

9th rank beasts can speak, so Zhao Hai called it over and asked, “What is ahead of here?”

Since the electric eel can answer, it immediately said, “Young Master, up ahead is a strange flower. Since I was little, I always found that flower to be comfortable, so I stayed by its side all the time.”

Zhao Hai looked at the eel and asked, “Flower?”

The electric eel nodded and said, “Yes, Young Master, it’s a very big flower, moreover, it is also very attractive!”

Zhao Hai immediately responded, “Let’s go, let me see it.” Then the eel complied as it lead Zhao Hai towards the same flower that it described.

Upon seeing the flower, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get shocked. This wasn’t a flower that he had seen in the sea. This was a lotus flower!

The lotus was very big, its blue petals were arranged in nine layers. It was very beautiful. Most importantly, the middle of the lotus wasn’t actually a seed base. There was another lotus flower inside, it seemed to be like 9th rank lotus bud.

Zhao Hai stared at this flower, he didn’t expect this thing to appear at this place. Lotuses weren’t usually found at the sea. For this one to be here was extremely strange.

However, Zhao Hai immediately became happy, this was the first time that he had come across a lotus in this world. He had seen other similar Earth plants on the continent, however, all of them were variations from what Zhao Hai imagined. This lotus was the first one that Zhao Hai can really describe as a genuine lotus.

Then Zhao Hai turned to the electric eel and said, “Are there any other flowers such as this?”

The eel answered, “There nothing else, Young Master, only this one.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he immediately went to the lotus and had the monitor examine it. He wanted to see the underside of the lotus.

Sure enough, Zhao Hai can see the lotus root under the flower. Although the root only had a thickness of an arm, it was as transparent as a crystal, it looked very tender as well.

Zhao Hai didn’t take the lotus immediately, he still wanted to see how long the roots were. Therefore, he continued to follow the root until he can see its end.

Zhao Hai looked for a long time but still cannot find the end of the lotus’ root. It seemed like the root has no end, it was very long. Zhao Hai frowned but he still didn’t stop. He felt that this lotus was becoming more and more extraordinary. If other other lotuses had such long roots, it might have already grown new buds, but this lotus only had one.

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai placed his anxiety away. Then he continued to find the tip of the lotus’ root.

Zhao Hai found a problem after searching for a long time. The lotus root started to extend, and it seems like it ran underneath the entire Soul Sucking Reef.

This finding made Zhao Hai excited, if its really like what he thought, then the magic formation of the Soul Sucking Reef might have been caused by the lotus root. If that is really the case, then he might have found another treasure.

A day had passed by but Zhao Hai still wasn’t able to find the tip of the lotus root. However, he didn’t give up, he took a rest and had Cai’er replace him. At this point, he can confirm that this lotus root does indeed cover the entirety of the Soul Sucking Reef.

The next day, Zhao Hai finally found the tip of the root. When he found the end, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be stunned. The ends of the root turned out to be circular. Then there was a curved dividing line in the middle of the circle. Then with the circumference of the root, it had actually turned into a Taiji Yin-Yang circle.

And when he traced the image of the roots and zoomed out, Zhao Hai can see that the reef, and the lotus root actually formed a natural Tai Ji Eight Trigrams Chart, with the lotus flower placed in the middle of it.

Zhao Hao stared at the diagram on the screen while being startled deep inside. He didn’t think that he would encounter this diagram in this world. This image was too familiar, it was a unique design in Chinese culture.

He couldn’t help but gawk at the mystery of creation and its ability to form a diagram like this naturally. No wonder the Demon Realm’s aura got suppressed. The Tai Ji Eight Trigrams Chart was a Daoist diagram that could restrain various Demonic creatures. For this big diagram to be placed right beside the trench meant that the Devil Trench has been suppressed all this time.

Zhao Hai knew what this chart was, however, it was different for Laura and the others. Laura and the others curiously looked at the monitor and asked, “Brother Hai, what did you find?”

Zhao Hai recovered, then he laughed out loudly and said, “We had found something good. In fact, we had found a treasure!! Fantastic, this is really fantastic. Hahaha”

Laura and the others stared at Zhao Hai, they couldn’t understand what made Zhao Hai this happy. After some time, Zhao Hai recovered, he didn’t explain the chart to Laura and the others since it was quite complicated. At the same time, Zhao Hai can only understand about half of it, so he really doesn’t have the qualifications to explain.

Zhao Hai looked at the others and then smiled faintly, “Just know that we gained something good. I can’t tell it to you right now. In any case, we must absorb the entire Soul Sucking Reef into the Space.”

Laura and the others stared blankly, then they shifted their gazes towards the reef. The Soul Sucking Reed is very huge. They even needed two days to travel through it. Can they really absorb the entire thing into the Space?

Zhao Hai also knew about this issue, so he couldn’t help but knit his brows. Then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, can we absorb the entire reef into the Space?”

Cai’er looked at the reef and nodded, “I can, however, this area might have something special going on. So I need the help of Bubbles in order to accomplish it.”

Chapter 647: Innate Treasure

When Zhao Hai heard Cai’er, he couldn’t help but be surprised. He looked at her and said, “Does that little guy have the strength to help you out?”

Cai’er just smiled and said, “Young Master, don’t underestimate that fellow. He is the source of Myriad Water. He is a very strong underwater. With his help, I would definitely be able to absorb the entire reef into the Space.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his hand to grab Bubble while pinching it a good amount of times. Naturally, this doesn’t affect Bubble, it wasn’t able to hurt him. After all, Bubble really didn’t care about what form he was in.

While Bubble was being grabbed by Zhao Hai, he tried to flee towards Laura’s arms. However, he was stopped by Zhao Hai, “If you run away, I will roast you. Making you into a boiling Bubble. Go and help Cai’er absorb the reef into the Space. That thing is useful to me.”

Bubble doesn’t dare offend Zhao Hai. Although he always stayed in the Space with Laura and the others while acting stubborn towards ZHao Hai, he was still very afraid of angering this Young Master of his. He was already part of the Space, and if Zhao Hai wanted to deal with him, he only needs to think about it and Bubble would disappear. And Zhao Hai can still retain his powers while making a new Bubble, a much different one compared to the original.

Therefore, Bubble doesn’t dare to neglect this command, so he immediately flattered Zhao Hai, “Young Master can feel relieved. As long as the Young Master needs me, I would go through fire and water for you.”

Zhao Hai tapped his own head, he feels a little headache. He already knows what kind of person Bubble was, so why does it feel the need to flatter him?

In the end, Zhao Hai decided to ignore it, he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, you can begin.” Cai’er nodded, then she turned to Bubble and said, “Bubble, imprison the water here, make it clump up before I absorb it to the Space.”

Bubble nodded and said, “So it’s only this? This is too simple.” Then his figure disappeared as he exited from the Blade Scale Whale while Zhao Hai and the others observe him.

Bubble was seen floating there, his body rotated as he loudly said, “Surrender to the Myriad Water, condense!” After hearing this voice, Zhao Hai and the others can see that the Soul Sucking Reef had experienced a change. The water in the entire reef seems to have suddenly solidified. The water around it became stationary along with the fishes inside. Everything looks as though it was sealed in ice. However, the solidified water didn’t turn to ice.

Zhao Hai hasn’t seen this side of Bubble before. This guy always had a playful look as Laura and the others play with him like a pet or a naughty child. Zhao Hai couldn’t imagine that this blob would be this strong.

Seeing that Bubble had delivered, Cai’er immediately said, “Absorb!” Then a spatial rift appeared and enveloped the entire reef like big pocket.

The reef was directly taken from the sea to the Space, even including the rocks ten meters under the sea.

Seeing this, Zhao Hai immediately turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er don’t put it in the Space’s sea. Look for a remote place close to the villa, prepare a place and place it there.”

Cai’er nodded, then a large pond appeared right close to the villa where the reef was placed in. Cai’er directed seawater towards the big pond, then she placed a small hole on the side, making sure that there was running water in the pond.

After the Soul Sucking Reef got absorbed to the Space, a prompt was then heard, “Innate Treasure found. Going in accordance to the highest good in Taoism. Laws of Heaven and Earth detected. Space Levels up. Space is now level 65. Host officially achieves God-rank. May now use Heaven and Earth energy. This was a very good level up. Hoping for the Host’s further effort.”

Zhao Hai stared before he exploded with joy. He didn’t think that the lotus was actually deemed to be an Innate Treasure by the Space. It was actually a treasure that was naturally produced, which also contained the laws of Heaven and Earth. This harvest was indeed extremely good.

Moreover Zhao Hai can feel that the Space’s classification of God-rank was different than outside. It seems like God-rank for the Space was much stronger than the God-ranks of the outside world.

But Zhao Hai had noticed something different from this level up. It didn’t say anything about the undead or the beasts being upgraded. Other than him being a true God-rank, nothing else has changed.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and probably guessed the reason. In the past, whether it be the God’s Blood or the God-rank Core, they were all based on energy, so it can manage to improve everything. On the other hand, the Soul Sucking Reef was a treasure that was based on the laws of the Heaven and the Earth. This law requires people to comprehend it. Therefore, the Space couldn’t upgrade the beasts and the undead.

After thinking through this point, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. He really got a treasure this time. Moreover, this treasure can still be upgraded. Although Zhao Hai had no idea how to improve this treasure, he can still find some time to research it in the future.

With Zhao Hai making this big move, it was impossible for Luo Ying and the others to not know about it. At this time, Luo Ying had arrived right by Zhao Hai’s Blade Scale Whale, staring blankly at the pit that Zhao Hai just made. This time, they had finally witnessed the might of Zhao Hai. Nobody but him can make the entire Soul Sucking Reef vanish completely.

Zhao Hai also noticed Luo Ying, so he turned his head and smiled, “General, I apologize, I just noticed that there was a naturally formed magic formation here. It’s very dangerous, so I took the chance to take it away.”

Luo Ying recovered, then she looked at Zhao Hai and saw the happy expression on his face. Although she didn’t know what just happened, she was sure that Zhao Hai just obtained something good. As for Zhao Hai’s gain, Luo Ying had no intention of asking about it. As far as she knows, it was virtually useless for her. Even if it was the largest treasure, the Fishman Race still haven’t managed to understand it after all these years. If Zhao Hai obtains it, then it was good. Moreover, he also got to erase a danger to the Fishman Race.

Luo Ying gave a salute and said, “I congratulate Mister and also wanted to express gratitude in behalf of our Fishman Race for erasing this hidden danger.”

When Zhao Hai heard Luo Ying, he stared for a moment before he smiled to her and said, “The General is too polite.” At this time, Zhao Hai was pulling a thumbs up for Luo Ying deep inside. She was truly worthy to be a general. She can actually notice that he had obtained a treasure just by observation.

Seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t deny it, Luo Ying became glad. This means that Zhao Hai was an honest person. So she smiled and said, “Mister, please come with me. I will be giving the Water Refining technique to you.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, then I’ll be right behind the General.” Then he commanded the Blade Scale Whale to head towards the Azure Dragon Snake.

Upon arriving inside the snail and having sat down, Zhao Hai smiled and then said, “I don’t want to alarm the General. Soul Sucking Reef is actually a naturally formed magic formation. I don’t know how to use this formation, so I planned to take it back in order to study it. Right, I forgot to tell the General last time. The Devil Trench actually houses a core of a high level Demon Realm magic beast. The Devil Octopus is actually a beast that was polluted by that core. The Core has already been destroyed by me, the octopi have been seized as well. There won’t be any problems in the future, the General can rest assured.”

Luo Ying knit her brows and said, “That the Devil Trench actually has a Demon Realm’s magic beast core? Is this a plot by the Demon Realm?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m not sure. This core is a treasure in the Demon Realm, so no Demon should be willing to just place it here. However, it is also good to keep guard. If there’s anything that you can’t solve in the future, then don’t hesitate to tell me about it. I will do my best to find a solution. We must gather our strengths before the attack of the Divine Race and the Demon Realm. We should be stable as we prepare for the dozens of battles to come.”

Luo Ying nodded, then she took out a beast skin scroll and handed it over to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this is our Mermaid Race’s Water Refining Technique. I hope that it can be useful for mister. Is Mister preparing to head to the Continent? Her Majesty also asks you to see her.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “General can rest assured, I will certainly see Her Majesty. After all, I’ve already promised before. Will General not go back with us?”

Luo Ying shook her head and said, “I’m unable to go back now. I still have a lot of things to do. I’m simply unable to find free time.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod, “Alright, then we’ll rest for a day here before heading towards Mermaid Island tomorrow. After seeing Her Majesty, I will then be returning to the Continent.”

Luo Ying nodded and said, “Then I won’t be disturbing Mister anymore. You have been working hard in the past few days.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he gave Luo Ying a salute before turning around to leave.

When Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he immediately opened the beast skin scroll and carefully read it. He was genuinely curious about this Water Refining Technique.

The Water Refining Technique wasn’t long, nor was it difficult. There were two points in this method, one was the requirement for water. The water to be used needed to be high quality. The better the quality, the better the item that was going to be produced.

The second point was about the controlling of the water. Along with its requirement for water, the control that was required for this technique was high as well. Even most water element magic formation doesn’t require this intricate control of water.

Chapter 648: Startling Changes

However, Zhao Hai had no problems dealing with these two points. As for the high quality water, he has Bubble. At the same time, who else was suitable for controlling water than Bubble?

Besides these two characteristics, there was also another property to this Water Refining Technique. It was that it was slow. Comparing Fire and Water Refining Techniques, Fire Refining Techniques were much faster. Fire Refining techniques uses fire to refine metals and other materials by hitting them with a hammer, removing impurities from these materials with each round of hammering.

Water Refining technique also has the same process but it uses water instead of fire. Naturally, control of water was extremely important in this process. If one was bad at control, then they would risk the destruction of the material, making it unable to be used anymore. Water Refining technique might remove impurities, however, it actually doesn’t change the composition of the material, instead, it actually makes it much stronger and sturdier.

An advantage to Water Refining technique that was different from Fire Refining techniques was that the usage of water makes it possible to refine more types of materials compared to using fire.

Actually, the Humans also have some sort of Water Refining technique. For example, spear shafts, these shafts were needed to be immersed in water before they were going to be used. After a lot of steps, these would then be qualified to be part of a spear. If one were to look at it, then it was exactly like refining that used water. However, this method was different. The Water Refining technique of the Fishmen was used to get rid of impurities, while the Water Refining technique of Humans was just to make their spear shafts much tougher.

On the other hand, the Fishmen also used Human techniques in their refining. While using their refining techniques, they would also incorporate many materials together in order to make new and improved items.

After reading through the Water refining scroll, Zhao Hai sighed. This Water Refining technique is truly a one of a kind technique. In fact, Zhao Hai believed that Humans might be able to use it, but in a lower probability of success. Purifying water can be done through distillation, the only problem would be the control of water.

But all of these wasn’t a problem for Zhao Hai. The reason why the Mermaids created this Water Refining technique was so that they wouldn’t rely on Human-made weapons. Therefore, most of the materials used in this technique originated in the Sea. And since Zhao Hai had the Space’s ocean, he had the proper requirements to perform the technique.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you don’t need to be anxious. The Divine Race wouldn’t be coming soon.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, he knew that Laura was just doing this in order to comfort him. And how can he not be anxious, the Radiant Church and the Dragon Clan’s moves had become more and more frequent. Zhao Hai reckoned that the time of the Divine Race’s move was not far.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but loudly sigh. Then he turned to Laura and said, “Let’s go and take a walk before resting. Then we’ll head to Mermaid Island tomorrow.” Laura and the others didn’t decline as they followed Zhao Hai.

Unknowingly, the group arrived at the big pond where the Soul Sucking Reef was placed in. Zhao Hai didn’t call it the Soul Sucking Reef anymore, instead, he changed its name to Tai Ji Pond.

Zhao Hai looked at the lotus’ naturally formed Tai Ji Eight Trigrams Chart and couldn’t help but become calm. He let out a long breath as he looked at the lotus flower. He couldn’t help but smile as he remembered his time back on Earth.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai remembered that the Water Refining Technique was able to refine a lot of materials. The Fishmen had done experiments wherein they refined living plants and animals. Although it had a small chance of success, it would yield good results if it were to succeed. Refined plants and animals would become much better than their unrefined counterparts.

When he thought about this, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but shine. He immediately loudly called, “Bubble!” Then Bubble quickly floated towards him saying, “Young Master, you called me.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at  Bubble and said, “We had acquired method of Water Refining. I will have Cai’er teach you how to do it later, then Cai’er shall provide you with living plants as well as minerals to experiment on. When you fully master the technique you’ll be living here in the Tai Ji Pond. Go and refine everything inside here, the lotus flower, the root, the stones, everything, even the small fishes. As long as I don’t call you, don’t stop refining. Understood?”

Bubble thought for a moment and said, “Young Master, I know how to read, there’s no need for Cai’er to teach me. That little girl is too hateful. I don’t need her, I can learn by myself.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he stared, then he looked puzzlingly at Bubble and said, “Bubble, you know how to read characters? Who taught you?”

Bubble shook his head and said, “I don’t know, the only thing I can remember is that I’ve always been literate. That knowledge came along with the images of women from before. As for the other specifics, I really have no idea.”

Zhao Hai looked at Bubble and said, “You really can’t remember anything?”

Bubble nodded, “Young Master, the only things I can remember were the figure of a woman as well as characters. Nothing else.”

Zhao Hai knitted his brows, he was confused about this matter. In the end, he can only give the beast skin scroll over to Bubble and said, “Alright, you go read this thing. Remember, make sure to take care in refining things in this pond. If you do badly, then I will boil you and make you into tea.”

Bubble shivered in fright, he immediately nodded and said, “Young Master, rest assured, I will certainly follow your orders.” Then he unrolled the beast skin scroll and read a bit before looking at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I’ll be heading back and do some experiments.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, provide Bubble with everything he needs to experiment with. Don’t use good things. As long as he masters it completely, immediately have him enter the Tai Ji Pond.” Cai’er nodded, then she turned to Bubble and smiled, which frightened Bubble so much that he ran away. While running, Bubble said, “Young Master, there’s no need for her to look for materials. I’ll go and acquire them myself!”

Cai’er coldly snorted as she yelled back, “You dared to call me little girl as well as hateful, you stinky Bubble, you’re dead. I’ll boil you into hot water.” Then she chased after Bubble, leaving Zhao Hai and the others behind.

Zhao Hao looked at the two and could’t help but chuckle. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Look at this, Cai’er had taken you as an example. She’s now saying that she’ll boil Bubble. You should know that Bubble is really afraid of being boiled alive.”

Zhao Hai laughed and then said, “Of course I know, but that Bubble has extremely thick skin, so he’ll definitely be fine. If you don’t threaten that fellow, then he won’t move. It’ll be good for us to have Cai’er looking after him.”

Laura and the others laughed as well. Cai’er had a deep connection with the Space. So she always places Bubble and Mu’er in check. However, she was also quite playful and wanted to play tricks, making Bubble’s life interesting.

Mu’er was usually right by Zhao Hai’s side, so Cai’er couldn’t move him most of the time. Additionally, Mu’er always kept his calm, making him a bad target for Cai’er’s pranks. Therefore, Cai’er stopped going after Mu’er and shifted her attention to Bubble. Bubble was a rascal and doesn’t want to surrender easily. He was a perfect target for Cai’er’s antics.

However, this doesn’t mean that their relationship wasn’t good. In fact, they were quite harmonious, Cai’er liked playing with Bubble while Bubble also liked being chased around by Cai’er.

At this time, Lizzy looked at the pond and said, “Big Brother Hai, will you really trust Bubble in refining this pool? This thing is a treasure, much more valuable than the God-ranked magic beast core. The core upgraded the Space by one level while this lotus actually upgraded it by five. If Bubble fails in refining it, then wouldn’t it be a pity?’

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “There’s nothing to pity about. Refining might be the only way of evolving this thing. Forget it, there’s no point in worrying about something we don’t have any hold of. We’ll just have Bubble be extremely careful in doing it. With his control over water, I don’t think that there would be any issues.”

Lizzy didn’t say anything else. This Tai Ji Pond and the lotus flower were really too strange. Even Zhao Hai didn’t know how this thing came about. They can only try what they could to upgrade it. In any case, they had acquired a new weapon for the future.

At this time, Cai’er suddenly ran over to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, Grandpa Kun came and was looking for you. It looks like an urgent matter.”

Zhao Hai nodded as his figure vanished and reappeared inside Kun’s office. When he saw Zhao Hai, Kun calmed his worried expression before he said, “Little Hai, something very important just happened.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Grandpa Kun, tell me.”

Kun sighed and said, “Yesterday, the Ocean Waves Dynasty suddenly announced that they would be handing their throne over to the Radiant Church. Their nation is now renamed to the Radiant Empire. It declared to be a nation that devotes itself to the worship of the Radiant God. At the same time, the Dragon Race suddenly attacked the Lyon Empire. The Lyon Empire’s famous cavalry suddenly rebelled and in just one day, the Lyon Empire fell. The Dragon Race changed the nation’s name to Saint Dragon Empire. They also announced their alliance with the Radiant Empire. At this point, the Dragons has complete control of the Lyon Empire while the Radiant Church has complete control of the Ocean Waves Dynasty.”

Chapter 649: The Dragons Must Be Eliminated

Zhao Hai stared blankly at Kun. Due to the shock, his mind has been unable to process the information for a short time. Zhao Hai felt that something just exploded inside his head, obliterating every thought that he had at the moment.

The news was just too sudden. After dealing with the matters of the Fishman Race, Zhao Hai was planning to wipe out the Dragons, eliminating one of the hands of the Divine Race. After that, he would slowly start to move against the Radiant Church.

However, he didn’t expect that the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race would make this sudden move. Moreover, they had taken two empires simultaneously. Although the Ocean Waves Dynasty was the fifth largest Empire and was quite small, it was known that their navy was quite invincible. Their strong navy was due to their lands being surrounded by the sea from three sides, which also made their naval transport very good.

At this point, Zhao Hai didn’t care much about sea warfare. He has the Fishman Race as allies. Even if the Ocean Wave Dynasty’s navy was know to be invincible, it was only in comparison to other Human powers. The Dynasty’s navy would have no chance in facing the Fishman Race at sea.

On the other hand, the Lyon Empire was a whole different story. The Lyon Empire was known as the second most powerful nation in the Continent. Their strength was formidable and because they were close to the Accra Mountains, they can gather wild beasts en mass then have those beasts become mounts to their Magic beast Cavalry.

A Cavalry that was made up of wild magic beasts was always more formidable than one with magic beasts that were bred. Therefore, the Lyon Empire’s Magic Beast Cavalry was well renowned in the entire continent for its strength. In fact, this mighty nation was brought to its knees by their own Magic Beast Cavalry.

Zhao Hai slowly calmed himself down as he pondered on the consequences that were brought up by this development. He planned to eliminate the Dragons because they were legends that lived in the Accra Mountain. If Zhao Hai were to kill them, then nobody would make a fuss.

But this time, the Dragons had actually taken control of Lyon Empire. This meant that if Zhao Hai were to deal with the Dragons, he would have to deal with the Lyon Empire first.

Zhao Hai didn’t believe that the Lyon Empire fell because of the Magic Beast Cavalry rebellion and the attack of the Dragons. Capturing an Empire wasn’t that easy.

The smooth takeover of the Dragons was surely aided by the nobles of the Lyon Empire. In other words, the Dragons and the Radiant Church were already controlling the Empire long time ago, they just decided to reveal it at this time.

This was troublesome. If Zhao Hai wanted to deal with the Dragons, then he would have to wage war against the Lyon Empire. More importantly, Zhao Hai had thought about the reason why the Radiant Church and the Dragons decided to make this move. What did this mean? It might be because the Divine Race was close to attacking, therefore, the Radiant Church and the Dragon Clan controlled those two empires, allowing the Divine Race to have an initial footing in the continent.

Seeing that Zhao Hai hasn’t spoken for quite some time, Kun looked at him and said, “At this moment, the Ocean Waves Dynasty and the Lyon Empire are gone. Meanwhile, the Buddha Empire was in the midst of an attack from those two new empires. Now that the Dragons have shown themselves, the other Empires in the continent have become flustered. This was due to the title of invincibility that the Dragons have held all this time. This development caused huge waves in the other Empires. At the same time, their alliance with the Radiant Church boosted the church’s influence by a huge margin.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Kun and said, “What is the Rosen Empire’s response? How are they prepared to deal with this matter?”

Kun forced a smile and said, “What else can they do? Even if they don’t want to recognize the Dragon Race’s sovereignty to the Lyon Empire, they also don’t want to offend the Dragons. After all, the Dragons have great reputation. Also, whether they are young or fully grown, all Dragons are capable of flight. In this case, the Rosen Empire had no choice but to recognize the existence of the Saint Dragon Empire and the Radiant Empire.”

Zhao Hai slammed his hand on the table, smashing it in the process. Then he talked through clenched teeth, “Radiant Church, Dragon Clan, I will not let you off easily.”

Kun gave out a sigh and said, “What do we do? I suspect that this is the prelude to the Divine Race’s invasion. If this is the case, then great troubles have come our way.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I have the same suspicion as well. The main thing we have to do is to destroy the Dragons first before the Divine Race arrive. Otherwise, the Dragons will provide the Divine Race with stable footing with their existing reputation. Moreover, the joint attack on the Buddha Empire is also very dangerous.”

Kun nodded, “It seems like the Divine Race will attack at any time. While they still haven’t come, we need to destroy the Dragons. Then we will deal with the Radiant Church later on.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “But it’s not time to act yet, wait for more news while I go and ask the Mermaid Queen for help in dealing with the Ocean Wave Dynasty’s navy. We need to stop them from supporting the Lyon Empire. After that, we’ll deal with the Dragons.”

Kun nodded, then Zhao Hai turned his hand and withdrew a bottle. The bottle held the Messenger Fish. Zhao Hai handed the bottle over to Kun and taught him how to use it. Then he produced two more bottles and gave it to Kun, having him hand it over to Blockhead and Rockhead later.

Kun was surprised when he saw the three Messenger Fishes. He didn’t think that this world would have such a thing, but he was still very happy. With these things, communication wouldn’t be a problem anymore.

Kun and the others already have their own Space Bags, so Zhao Hai didn’t hand them more and just told Kun that the bottles can be placed inside the bags. For this reason, Zhao Hai had made Bubble pay attention. If someone sends a message while the Messenger Fish was in his bag, then Bubble would go and inform Zhao Hai through the Space. Unless it was an important matter, Zhao Hai would keep his Messenger Fish inside his Space Bag.

After handing the fishes over to Kun, Zhao Hai immediately went to Iron Mountain Fort. Not only did he give a Messenger Fish to Green, he also distributed some Messenger Fishes to the stewards of every village as well as to some people with status in the Black Wasteland. The reason why Zhao Hai decided to send the fishes right now was because their numbers had already reached a high enough number.

The Messenger Fishes weren’t very large. This was because Zhao Hai wanted them to be more convenient to use outside, so he had Cai’er further reduce their size. At this point, the Messenger Fishes were about two pinky joints big.

Moreover, after the level ups of the Space, the Messenger Fishes can now survive in any type of water and were very efficient in digesting food.

After dealing with the matters in Iron Mountain Fort, Zhao Hai then went to the Dwarves. He wanted to give Billy some Messenger fishes before telling him about the Dragon Race and the Radiant Church’s movement.

Zhao Hai didn’t care so much this time as he appeared directly inside his warehouse in Dwarf Mountain. When he came cout, the Dwarves outside the warehouse were very shocked, but it quickly turn to joy as they sent word to Billy. Zhao Hai didn’t dally and directly headed towards Billy’s office.

Billy was currently worried about the Dragons as well as the Radiant Church. The sudden move of the two surely gave them a huge blow, completely derailing the plans that they had thought up before. They were planning to slowly build their strength up until the fight with the Divine Race came. But now, it seems like it would be impossible due to the recent move of the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race.

The Radiant Church had some relations with the Divine Realm, and it was certain that they also knew about the Dwarves’ participation in the last Great War. Therefore, it was impossible for the Radiant Church to just let the Dwarves off this time. It was for certain that the Dwarves would get affected with the recent development.

While he was ruminating on his thoughts, word suddenly came, informing him of Zhao Hai’s arrival. This made Billy glad, he needed Zhao Hai to talk about this matter. And Zhao Hai’s arrival was too timely.

Just as Billy was about to meet Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai had come inside Billy’s office. Seeing his visitor, Billy couldn’t help but smile and said, “Little Hai, good, you came. Come, sit down.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and the sat opposite Billy before he said, “Patriarch, you should’ve known about the recent move of the Dragon Clan and the Radiant Church. How is everything going? Did the Dragons come in contact with you?”

Billy shook his head and said, “Not yet. Their move was very sudden this time, so they might not have the time to deal with us. How about you, what do you think we should do now?”

Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “You don’t have to worry too much, just do what you’ve been doing. However, you should be alert and be ready to fight. I think that the Radiant Church and the Dragon Clan not going after you meant that they had some other matters to attend to. However, you should still be careful.”

Billy nodded then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What about the Dragon Race and the Radiant Church, will you just be watching from the sidelines?”

Zhao Hai sneered, “They think that they had everything. It seems like I need to use my real strength. I must destroy the entire Dragon Race, after all, keeping them for long will just lead to more disaster!”

Billy couldn’t help but stare upon hearing Zhao Hai, then with great enthusiasm, he said, “Do you really want to eliminate the Dragons? Then count us in, we Dwarves are never afraid to fight.”

Zhao Hai looked at Billy and the smiled faintly “You don’t need to participate at this time. However, I do have something that needs your help. Sign this thing, having the mark of the Dwarf Race would suffice.” Then Zhao Hai got a beast skin scroll and handed it over to Billy.

Billy looked at the scroll and then read the contents. He couldn’t help but stare at it for quite some time before he nodded and said, “Alright, then I shall give our mark. I think it would be better to take this out a few days after the Dragon Race’s matter. At the same time, I shall also send word to the Elves. I believe they just won’t stay quiet this time. I just can’t understand why it would take them so long to respond.”

Chapter 650: Seeing Their Reaction

Zhao Hai was going in good graces with the Elves with him wanting to repair their Divine Artifact. But how about them? After waiting for a long time for their reply, they were still quite silent about the matter. This made Zhao Hai speechless.

However, Zhao Hai would still want to have a proper response from the Elven Race. Therefore, he nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll wait for the Elves’ response while I head to the Beastman Prairie. I’ll also have the Beast King sign this scroll, the same with the Fishman Race. As soon as the Elves send word, then use this to inform me.” Then Zhao Hai took out a Messenger Fish and gave to Billy.

Billy looked curiously at the fishes, he had never heard of such a thing before. He continued to look at the swimming fish inside the bottles, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “This thing can directly speak to you?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right, but not just me. It can also make you speak with other people. I don’t have a lot of Messenger Fishes, but here’s ten. You can give them to your people so that you can more conveniently communicate with them.” Then he took out ten more bottles and handed them over to Billy, who received it with great happiness.

Zhao Hai also discussed some things with Billy. They weren’t something important, he just told Billy to not make any other moves and just keep doing what they were originally doing. However, he also made them get more alert to their surroundings. After that, Zhao Hai left the Dwarf Mountain and headed to the Beastman Prairie.

Zhao Hai went directly to the Beast King Palace. After Zhao Hai left, the people in the Palace were already instructed by the Beast King, Zhao Hai wouldn’t need to wait for approval in visiting the Palace, just have him enter immediately. However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to neglect standard procedure. So he went to the reception first before he was immediately escorted into the palace.

The Beast King didn’t hear much news from the continent. After all, the Prairie was too remote for information to quickly come through. Therefore, the Beast King was very surprised by Zhao Hai’s sudden appearance. However, he still greeted Zhao Hai and sat with him in the living room.

After having sat down, the Beast King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Why did you come? Did something happen?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he sighed, “Something significant just happened. Yesterday, the Ocean Waves Dynasty suddenly announced that they would be handing the throne over to the Radiant Church. Now, the Dynasty no longer exists and was replaced by the Radiant Church. It is now called Radiant Empire and is fully controlled by the Radiant Church’s officials. At the same time, the Dragons suddenly came out of Accra Mountain and extinguished the Lyon Imperial Clan. After that, they founded the Saint Dragon Empire and had formed an alliance with the Radiant Church.”

The Beast King stared for a moment before his expression changed. He immediately understood what this meant. As if by habit, he stood up and walked back and forth two times before he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “The Dragons must be destroyed. Their name is too famous that it instills fear to the people. If this continues, we wouldn’t be able to fight.”

Zhao Hai stared at the Beast King, he didn’t expect him to understand the core of the matter. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, I was planning to do exactly just that. I only came here to inform you of this matter while also reminding you to be alert. The Radiant Church might come and deal with you. Now that they have the help of the Dragons, they can come and attack you at any moment. Therefore, you must strengthen your defenses.”

The Beast King nodded and then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Do you want us to dispatch some troops to deal with the Dragons?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No need, I can deal with them myself. However, I need your help to sign this.” Then he handed the beast skin scroll over.

The Beast King read the scroll before marking it with the brand of the Beastmen. There’s nothing special in this scroll, it just mentioned the relationship between the Radiant Church and the Divine Race. It also contained the story regarding the Divine Race as well as the Demon Realm. This was something that Zhao Hai planned to show the Emperors of the nations as well as the Patriarchs of various Great Clans. He planned to have the signatures of the Beastmen, the Dwarves, the Fishmen, and the Elves before showing this scroll to the others. They needed to understand that they were currently facing the same enemy!

The Beast King approved of Zhao Hai’s procedure. He’s a King therefore he knew that since the Radiant Church and the Dragons have begun, it was also time for Zhao Hai to make his move. Therefore, Zhao Hai prepared this scroll ahead of time so that when he goes to the Humans, they would immediately unite against the great tribulation that was coming.

After the Beast King signed the scroll, Zhao Hai immediately took out a Messenger Fish bottle and handed it over to the Beast King while explaining its function. Then he took out 10 more bottles for the Beast King to use. This made the King very happy. Although the Beastmen had hawks for communication, they still fell quite short compared to the Messenger Fish.

After handling the matters of the Beastmen, Zhao Hai immediately returned to the Space. Laura and the others were also waiting for him inside. To be honest, they were still shaken dizzy by the news that they didn’t know what to do.

Seeing that Zhao Hai had come back, Laura and the others immediately went to him and said, “Brother Hai, what do we do now? Will we go and extinguish the Dragons?’

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s the only thing we could do in order to keep the damage at the minimum. Their bodies are too tough while they have huge strength. They shouldn’t have appeared in the continent, but they had actually sided themselves with the Divine Race. In the Fishman records, these Dragons had become the vanguard of the Divine Race’s war. One could say that the Dragons would do the brunt of the work while the God would move once in a while. It was only because of the Divine Artifacts injuring the God that the war had ended. With this information, it would be impossible for us to just let the Dragons roam free while waiting for the attack from the Divine Race.”

Laura nodded, she also knew that in the previous war, the Divine Race had only sent one person to do the job. The main force of the combat came into the hands of the Dragons and their Lesser Dragon subordinates along with some rebels from the Ark Continent’s side. The moves that the Divine Race God had done was actually quite a few. Therefore, Zhao Hai’s plan to eliminate the Dragons was quite understandable.

After she gave a nod, Laura asked, “So when do we begin?” At this point, Laura was very confident. Zhao Hai had a lot of 9th rank undead, several millions of them. With this number of 9th ranks, even if the Dragons were formidable, they still couldn’t stand a chance against Zhao Hao’s force.

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “Let’s not be too quick about this. Let’s have the Dragons savor their victory for a few days. We’ll wait after we get the Elves’ signature before beginning. Hmph. The Dragon Clan and the Radiant Church had just obtained their countries, so they still need to stabilize their situation. We still have time.”

Laura nodded. Although the Dragon Race and the Radiant Church didn’t take too much work in usurping the two nations since they had the support of the nobles, the countries still had a massive amount of commoners that needed to be appeased. Although the countries haven’t experience war this time, they were still susceptible for rebellion. It will still take quite some time before they fully stabilize their situation.

If other forces were to suddenly extinguish the Lyon Empire, then the Rosen Empire and the Buddha Empire would certainly dispatch their army. And even if they couldn’t defeat them, at the very least they could still get some profits off of them. However, since the new rulers of the Lyon Empire were Dragons, the Buddha and Rosen Empires have chosen to refrain from sending troops and instead just recognize the Dragons’ sovereignty over the Empire.

This was also the reason why Zhao Hai chose to eliminate the Dragons!

The reputation of the Dragons in the continent was just too big. They were basically synonymous with invincibility, every race were afraid of them. This reputation was exactly what was left of their conquest in helping the Divine Race. The Human records have been changed severely that the strength of the Dragons was the only one that was left written down.

Zhao Hai saw this as something that the Radiant Church had done. They had changed the history of the Humans while leaving behind the legend of the Dragon Race. This was to control the mindset of the future generations whenever they decide to deal with the legendary beings in Accra Mountain.

All of this caused Zhao Hai to think about extinguishing the Dragon Race. First was to avoid further disaster, second, to break an arm of the Divine Race, and third, to let people understand that Dragons aren’t invincible.

Naturally, if Zhao Hai didn’t exist, then the Dragons would surely be close to being invincible. After all, in addition to their innate strengths, their bodies were quite tough as well. Most importantly, they were capable of flight. This was something that the continent would deem as a nightmare.

But unfortunately for them, Zhao Hai had appeared in the continent. Even if the Dragons were quite close to being invincible, Zhao Hai would still make sure to break their reputation.

Although he had decided on his action, Zhao Hai was still carefully calculating his moves. He didn’t want something to suddenly happen and undermine his plans.

After carefully thinking about everything, Zhao Hai started to feel relieved. In fact, Zhao Hai also understood that even if the Divine Race would make a sudden move, he could still get all of the people in the continent to transfer to his Space. In addition to the main world, Zhao Hai also had an additional 20 backgrounds to live in. More importantly, security wasn’t a problem while inside the Space.

It was because of this assurance that Zhao Hai dared to go against the Divine Race. As long as he had the Space, Zhao Hai believed that he would be able to defeat them.

After resting for one day, Zhao Hai said his farewells to Luo Ying before riding the blade scale whale and heading towards Mermaid Island. Zhao Hai didn’t use his Space to go there since he wanted to use this time to wait for the response from the Elves. At the same time, he also wanted to know how the Fishmen respond after hearing the recent news.

Chapter 651: Startling the Mermaid Queen

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about the Beastmen and the Dwarves. He had fixed their Divine Artifact, making them grateful to him. Because of this, Zhao Hao told them his plans as soon as he can.

However, Zhao Hai was still in deep suspicion towards the Elves. He didn’t know if this was really their nature, or there was a hidden plot happening that made them delay the matter. Because of this, Zhao Hai plans to wait for their reaction. Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid that the Elves would tell the Dragons about his inquiries, after all, he was already unmatched in the whole of Ark Continent.

As for the Fishmen, Zhao Hai didn’t worry about them at all. The Fishmen had great enmity with the Divine Race, which also transferred to the Dragon Clan and the Radiant Church. Zhao Hai was extremely comfortable with them being in his side.

However, Zhao Hai also knew how careful the Fishmen were. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have founded the Sea God’s Merchant Union in order to get news from the continent. And it was for certain that the Mermaids had already received the news about the Radiant Church and the Dragons. Zhao Hai wanted to see their response upon receiving this information.

One must know that for these big races, there was no enmity that can’t be solved. Anything can happen in the name of benefit. If the Fishmen really did think that the Divine Race was powerful, then they may stop their alliance with Zhao Hai.

The Beastmen and the Dwarves have their own Divine Artifacts, so they already knew that their races were also hostile to the Radiant Church’s patrons. This made it impossible for them to side with the Radiant Church for benefit. Therefore, they sided with Zhao Hai to deal with the Radiant Church.

On the other hand, the Fishmen might not know about the relationship between their Sea God and the Radiant Church in the Divine Realm. This was due to them not being in the records of the Dwarves during the past great war. Therefore, Zhao Hai had some doubts about their actions and wanted to see how they would respond when faced with the current situation.

Zhao Hai proceeded onward, he didn’t rush in the daytime and he rested properly during the night. At the same time, he was also paying attention to the situation on the continent through the Space. Now that Kun and the others were in possession of the Messenger Fishes, Zhao Hai was able to have a dialog with them in the past few days.

What Zhao Hai didn’t expect was the fact that his popularity among the Fishmen had become quite high. In the eyes of the Fishmen, the conclusion of their recent rebellion was only reached due to Zhao Hai’s actions. So no matter which Fishman Tribe he meets, all of them were extremely hospitable towards Zhao Hai. They were quite polite and even brought him some gifts. At the same time, some of them even agreed to having a business cooperation with the Buda Clan.

Although the Fishman Race were mostly self-sufficient, they still want to have other things. Of course, Zhao Hai didn’t decline these offerings. Almost every Fishman tribe can offer him with unique things to trade for, this made Zhao Hai very glad when forming his business partnerships.

The Fishmen liked Human bottles, ironworks, wooden furnitures, cotton fabrics, and many more. Although things in the sea might get reduced by trading with Zhao Hai, it was still fine since Zhao Hai only needed common marine products. For the Fishmen, these things can basically be seen everywhere, there was no need for them to exert so much effort in acquiring them.

Zhao Hai certainly didn’t think that he would have this good of a reception among the Fishmen. One must know that Dark Mages in the continent never did have a good reputation. Those who were calm in front of Zhao Hai were only those who had come in contact with him face to face. As for the other people, all of them would be terrified by the mere mention of Zhao Hai’s name. After all, this was a person that can turn several hundred thousand people into undead.

Three days later, Zhao Hai had finally arrived at Mermaid Island’s region. But when he arrived, he was actually stopped by a group of Swordfish tribesmen, it seems like they weren’t able to recognize Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai can also see that they didn’t come with unfavorable intention. So he went out of the Blade Scale Whale and gave a slight bow before saying, “Might I know why I am being blocked?” The leader of the Swordfish group immediately gave a salute to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, the Queen has something important to discuss with you. We ask mister to please head towards Mermaid Island.”

When he heard this, Zhao Hai nodded and then said, “Can I know why Her Majesty is looking for me?’ Naturally, Zhao Hai knew why the Queen was looking for her, he was just asking for formality.

The Swordfish tribesman shook his head and said, “I’ll be unfair to mister, but I really don’t know. Her Majesty didn’t tell us, she just gave instructions to invite you over to the island.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, then I’ll be troubling you to lead me there.” The Swordfishes immediately turned their mounts around and swam towards mermaid Island. Behind them, Zhao Hai urged the Blade Scale Whale to follow.

The Blade Scale Whale wasn’t known for its speed, however, Zhao Hai’s Blade Scale Whale was a 9th rank undead. So how could it be any slower? It was able to comfortable keep up with the speed of the Swordfish group.

This startled the people from the Swordfish tribe. They were famed for their speed, so how could Zhao Hai’s whale able to keep up with their speed, this was something unexpected.

After advancing for two days, Zhao Hai had finally arrived at Mermaid Island. There were no changes in the island, the Whales were still in charge of guarding it. When they reached the island, the Swordfishes left Zhao Hai and handed the task of leading Zhao Hai over to the Whales.

After entering the island, Zhao Hai stepped on the back of the turtles as he went to through the pillars and arriving in front of the Mermaid Palace.

When he arrived at the Palace, Zhao Hai can already see Lola waiting for him. When she saw that Zhao Hai had come, Lola stepped forward and greeted him, “Mister, please come with me. Her Majesty is already waiting for you.” Zhao Hai nodded and then followed Lola towards the inner hall.

The Queen was already in her throne when Zhao Hai came in. When she saw Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but move. Her tail vanished and turned into feet, at the same time, her throne had turned into an ordinary chair.

The Queen stood up and said, “Mister, have a seat.”

Zhao hai gave a bow and replied, “Thank you, Your Majesty.” Then the group saw inside the hall.

The Queen opened her mouth first “Mister, you’ve helped us greatly this time. The rebellion wouldn’t have ended this soon if not for your help.” Then she gave Zhao Hai a bow.

Zhao Hai stood up to return the courtesy before he quickly said, “Your Majesty is too polite. It’s just a little effort, it’s not worth mentioning.”

The Queen didn’t delay the matter as she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are you aware of the recent developments in the continent?”

Zhao Hai knew that the main topic had come. He didn’t hide anything from the Queen, so he nodded and said, “I do. The Dragons and the Radiant Church made their move and controlled two big Empires of the Continent. At this time, they should be stabilizing their rule over their subjects.”

The Queen didn’t expect Zhao Hai to already be aware of the news. One should know that as soon as the Queen heard the news, she immediately sent people to look for Zhao Hai. He should be unaware of this news since he had always been in the sea. Zhao Hai already knowing this information gave the Queen an estimate of Zhao Hai’s resources.

So she just nodded and said, “Right, its that. May I know what Mister thinks? Do we need to make a move?”

When he head the Queen, Zhao Hai’s worries had completely vanished. He smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty doesn’t need to worry much about this. I already have a plan.”

The Queen stared, she was confused at what Zhao Hai meant, “What I just wanted to know is what plans Zhao Hai has already made.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I also need Her Majesty’s help for this plan. I’m prepared to deal with the Dragons, and I want Your Majesty to keep the Ocean Waves Dynasty away from supporting the Lyon Empire. As for the other things, leave everything to me.”

The Queen thought for a moment before she nodded and said, “This isn’t difficult matter. However, is Mister confident with dealing with the Dragons? They’re title of invincibility isn’t without proof.

Zhao Hai just smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty can rest assured, I have complete confidence in my strength. The reason why I still haven’t attacked them was because I needed to discuss the matter of the Ocean Waves Dynasty with Your Majesty. At the same time, I am also waiting for the response from the Elven Race. As long as information arrives, then I will immediately head to the Elven Forest. And after that, I will then go and deal with the Dragon Race.”

The Queen stared for a moment before she nodded, “Alright, then we shall wait for mister’s word. When the time comes, we shall fully coordinate with you.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod and said, “I’ll have to thank Your Majesty. Right, I also need Your Majesty to sign this.” Then he took out the beast skin scroll and handed it over to the Queen.

When the Queen received the scroll and saw the marks of the Beastmen and the Dwarves, she didn’t hesitate and also marked the scroll with the Fishman Race’s unique mark.

Then Zhao Hai took out a bottle of Messenger Fish and gave it to the Queen, “Your Highness, this is a Messenger Fish that I have specially bred. As long as Your Majesty has this fish, you can speak to it directly and I shall immediately hear your message.”

The Queen received Zhao Hai’s Messenger Fish. Naturally, she was very familiar regarding these creatures. However, she didn’t think that Zhao Hai would also have them. Moreover, it seems like Zhao Hai’s breed was more advanced. This startled the Queen, the Mermaid Race had been religiously doing research on marine life. Because of this, they had more understanding with regards to beings of the sea than anyone in this world. The mere fact that Zhao Hai was able to produce a more advanced Messenger Fish made the Queen freeze from shock.

Chapter 652: Buddha Empire

The Queen looked at Zhao Hai, she was very clear about what this change in the Messenger Fish represented. It was not just a mutation, this was an entire evolution of the Messenger Fish, making it more advanced and giving it much better function.

The Messenger Fish was a small and common marine beast. However, this small magic beast has a unique ability. The difficulty of making such a beast evolve  several times more than evolving any common magic beast.

To put it bluntly, even if the Fishmen were people, their differences compared to the marine beasts weren’t that huge. The reason why the Mermaid Clan was researching marine magic beasts was for them to be able to develop a method to make the Mermaids or the other Fishmen more perfect people.

This might sound simple, but once one does this for quite some time, they will discover how difficult it actually was. Each type of magic beasts might have their own unique characteristics, but the Fishmen also had their own unique properties. Gathering these strong points and matching them was easier said than done.

It wasn’t only the task of gathering strong points that was difficult. Even improving magic beasts was a difficult matter all on its own. One might see something great in a magic beast, however, improving them might result in a futile effort. Even if it succeeds, there are still more issues along the road, it was still far from being called successful.

The Mermaids were aware of these difficulties since it takes into account genetics as well as other advanced matters. However, it was impossible for them to use these matters in order to evolve magic beasts.

One the other hand, the Space can digitize beings, making it very easy for it to upgrade these beings. It was just like when one plays a game and finds a skill book that they can learn in a matter of minutes. However, reality was just too far away from this.

The Queen wasn’t aware of the existence of the Space, so when she saw Zhao Hai’s Messenger Fish, she couldn’t help but express her shock.

Billy and the Beast King didn’t understand the Fishmen and the significance of the Messenger Fish. Therefore, even if they felt strange, they weren’t startled like the Mermaid Queen.

The thought of the Messenger Fishes caused the Mermaid Queen to think about Zhao Hai’s unusual undead creatures. Although Zhao Hai had reduced their strength, they were still quite extraordinary in the eyes of the Queen. Large-scale summoning as well as impressive fighting prowess, all of these made the Queen extremely curious towards Zhao Hai.

The Queen knew that Zhao Hai had a lot of good things based on what she had heard from the Continent. It seems like Zhao Hai’s unique things aren’t only limited to the Messenger Fishes. This made the Queen think that Zhao Hai might have discovered a way to improve a being’s biology.

Zhao Hai was confused at the Queen’s surprised expression. Was it because of the Messenger Fish? Aren’t there a lot of variant beasts in this world? So why was she especially surprised this time?’

Zhao Hai looked at the Queen and asked, “Your Majesty, is there something wrong?”

The Queen looked deeply into Zhao Hai without saying anything. Then she handed the Messenger Fish over to Lola before turning her head back to Zhao Hai and said, “There’s no problem. Once Mister decides to act, don’t hesitate to let us know.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then I shall thank Your Majesty in advance. I shall say my farewells first, I’ll be leaving for the continent tomorrow to continue with my plans.”

The Queen nodded, “Alright. Mister can rest assured, this is an important matter to every race. So my Fishman Race would surely give you our full cooperation.”

Then Zhao Hai stood up and gave the Queen a salute before turning around to leave. Once Zhao Hai was out of sight, Lola immediately turned to the Queen and said, “Your Majesty, haven’t we been looking for a way to make the Mermaid Clan stronger? If Mister Zhao Hai can improve the Messenger Fish, then he surely has the means to help us. Why didn’t you tell him about this matter earlier?”

The Queen sighed and then said, “Now is not the time to say it. Mister Zhao Hai has been busy with dealing with our own matters, but we still haven’t contributed to Mister Zhao Hai’s cause even if we are allies in dealing with the Divine Race. But I’m sure that this method is Mister Zhao Hai’s biggest secret. If we want to get this method at his time, the only thing we could do would be to threaten Mister. However, we naturally can’t do it. So this matter can only be postponed to the future.”

Lola nodded, then the Queen sighed once again before she said, “Our Mermaid Race can be seen to as quite a perfect race in the continent. We can survive in the sea as well as on land, as long as there is a body of water nearby. We also have good control over water as well as being able to use various water element magic. At the same time, our combat capabilities are also quite formidable, not very different compared to any ordinary warrior. Our only downside compared to the other races is the fact that we Mermaids have the least members in the Divine Realm. Perhaps this is the drawback for our Mermaid Race.”

Lola sighed as well, she didn’t know what to say. The Mermaids were indeed unique, they had long lives, great strength, good population, and were generally 9th ranks at maturity. However, it was close to impossible for them to become God-ranked experts. All previous Mermaid Queens were aware of this point and worried about it for a long time. They sought for a solution all this time but was unable to actually succeed.

But seeing Zhao Hai’s messenger fish made the current Queen see hope. However, just like what the Queen said, they hadn’t done much for Zhao Hai yet. If they were to open this matter up to Zhao Hai, then he might develop some misunderstandings. And misunderstandings were something that they didn’t need at this moment in time.

Zhao Hai was currently listening to Lola and the Queen’s conversation while inside the Space. He didn’t think that his messenger fish would evoke this reaction from both the Queen and Lola. No wonder the Queen had a strange expression earlier.

However, it would not be difficult for Zhao Hai to make the Mermaids God-ranked experts. Now that the the Space had reached level 65, plants that would allow the creation of God-rank potions can now be planted in the farm. As soon as the plants become ready, then Zhao Hao would surely take some potions out. After all, their enemy this time was the Divine Race who had a lot of God-ranked experts in their fold. Only then can the Ark Continent truly resist the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai took a deep breath, then he changed the monitor towards the Buddha Empire’s Royal Palace. He wanted to see the response from the Buddha Empire’s side.

The Buddha Emperor surely wasn’t a fool. He knew the implications of the Radiant Church and the Dragons being in control of the Ocean Waves Dynasty and the Lyon Empire, respectively. He knew what they would be facing, and he was currently looking for the key to resisting both the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race.

Zhao Hai carefully looked at the Buddha Empire’s situation for a few days. The Buddha Emperor was certainly not a fool, his response was exactly what Zhao Hai expected. The Empire had sent some envoys towards the Rosen Empire, in hopes of establishing an alliance against the Saint Dragon Empire.

The Buddha Empire’s worries were completely justified. In the past, the Buddha Empire held a stronger army compared to the Ocean Waves Dynasty, but they were still lacking when it came to naval power. On the other hand, the Lyon and Buddha Empire was separated by the Accra Mountain, making the Lyon Empire unable to send troops towards the Buddha Empire. Also making the Empire completely safe against the attacks from the Lyon Empire army.

However, the current situation changed everything. The Dragons have gotten control of the Lyon Empire, establishing the Saint Dragon Empire. And since the magic beasts in the Accra Mountain were subordinates of the Dragons, an avenue to attack the Buddha Empire had appeared. If they were to send a force towards the Buddha Empire, then the Saint Dragon Empire can now use the Accra Mountain as a path. When that time comes, the Buddha Empire would then be placed on its back foot.

Since they knew about this, the Buddha Empire immediately sent envoys to the Rosen Empire in order to form an alliance. The Rosen Empire was the continent’s most powerful nation, so they should have no fear towards the Dragons. Being an ally to the Rosen Empire would surely make the Dragons think twice about their further actions.

While the envoys were on the way, the Buddha Empire had also entered a state of preparation. Zhao Hai’s constant supply of magic beasts also gave the Buddha Empire some courage to hold on.

However, courage and confidence were two different matters. The Dragons’ reputation of invincibility had placed a huge pressure on the Buddha Empire. The Emperor as well as the Great Nobles were constantly on talks as to how to deal with this matter. However, after hours and days of discussion, they still haven’t reached a good enough resolution.

Naturally, the Hurricane Family was aware of this matter as well. And since Juno had a close relationship with Billy, he also wanted to know how Zhao Hai plans to deal with this matter. Zhao Hai had not hidden the truth from him, he told the Hurricane Patriarch about his plan to completely eradicate the Dragons. At the same time, he also gave Juno a messenger fish.

It can be said that the thing that Zhao Hai was waiting for was the response from the Elves. Whether the Elves were willing to cooperate or not, Zhao Hai still needed their response in order to plan for his further actions. If the Elves agree to ally with him, then he would immediately head to the Elven Forest to repair their Divine Artifact while also discussing their matter of alliance along with having them sign his beast skin scroll.

If the Elves don’t agree to dealing with the Divine Race, then Zhao Hai would not care about their word any more. He would then go and deal with the Dragons. And if the Elves were to side with the Divine Race, then Zhao Hai would have no choice but to be impolite.

Zhao Hai continued to look at the situation of the Buddha Empire. However, there wasn’t any special change in the Empire. Like the previous days, they were still trying to figure out ways in order to deal with their current situation.

At this point, it was impossible for the Buddha Empire to side with the Radiant Church. They saw what just happened to the Ocean Waves Dynasty as well as the Lyon Empire, so how could they side with them? The Radiant Church was like a beast that eats people along with their bones. Sooner or later, the Buddha Empire would get swallowed up. So the Buddha Empire can only hold on for as long as they can. They couldn’t make any agreements between the Dragons and the Radiant Church.

Chapter 653: Visiting the Elves

The next day, Zhao Hai said his farewell to the Mermaid Queen before he got onboard the Haven. Zhao Hai planned to ride his ship towards the continent, this was also to give the Elves more time to send their response. After all, there wasn’t anything significant that he had to do at this time.

Once word arrives from the Elves, then Zhao Hai would begin with his action. He didn’t plan to tell the Rosen Emperor about any of these. Even if the Rosen Emperor was Zhao Hai’s father in-law, he was still an Emperor of a nation, making it difficult for him to keep secrets to himself. Who knows if the Radiant Church had set up some shadows in the Imperial Palace. If Zhao Hai reveals his plans to the Rosen Emperor, then he might risk having it known to the Radiant Church. When that time arrives, all of Zhao Hai’s plans would be placed into trouble.

Although Zhao Hai was not anxious and was just slowly sailing towards the continent, he was still paying close attention to the developments in the continent. Through the Space, he was looking at the Calci Family while also listening for information from the Crook Family. This made Zhao Hai updated with regards to the matters of the Continent.

Rosen Empire’s response was also in line with what Zhao Hai expected. Although the Rosen Empire recognized the existence of the Saint Dragon Empire, it also entered a state of war preparation. They were preparing to go against the Dragons.

On the other hand, the Aksu Empire’s response was far from what Zhao Hai thought. Although they were implicated in the conflict between the Radiant Church and the Beastmen, Zhao Hai still thought that the Aksu Empire would reignite their relationship with the Church after hearing the news. But instead, they actually formed an alliance with the Rosen Empire.

This was way out of Zhao Hai’s expectations to the point that he doubted them. But after observing the Aksu Empire for a few days, Zhao Hai found out that he was wrong. This time, the Aksu Empire did want to deal with the Radiant Church.

The way the Radiant Church handled the past matter caused the Aksu Empire to dislike the organization. Even if the Radiant Church conquered the four other nations, the Aksu Empire would still resist them. This wasn’t only due to the current ruler, Boris, this sentiment was shared by all the Nobles of the Empire as well, not to mention the commoners.

This response from the Aksu Empire made Zhao Hai glad. For Zhao Hai, this was the best outcome that could happen. An enemy of an enemy is a friend, so even if they had a past matter, Zhao Hai would still consider them as friends as long as they plan to deal with the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race.

Two days after Zhao Hai left Mermaid Island, Billy had finally brought some news. It was said that the Elven Queen wanted to meet with Zhao Hai.

To be honest, Zhao Hai wasn’t satisfied with this answer. The Elf Queen only wanted to see him and didn’t express their intention to form an alliance. However, Zhao Hai would still want to see the Elf Queen. After all, this was also an opportunity to win the Elves over to his side.

Zhao Hai appeared inside the Dwarf Mountain through the Space. At this point, the Dwarves aren’t startled by his sudden appearances anymore. When they saw Zhao Hai, they immediately sent people to inform Billy.

Billy also knew that Zhao Hai was coming. Therefore, he was already waiting for him. When they had sat down, Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I told the Elves about the Radiant Church, this prompted them to send an answer. You should go and see the Elf Queen, it seems like they are quite hesitant.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “I don’t understand why they would hesitate now that the Divine Race are almost at the tip of our noses. I’m actually surprised. How can this race survive to the present?”

Billy can understand Zhao Hai’s complaints. To be honest, he also couldn’t understand the response from the Elves. But Billy didn’t complain, instead, he urged Zhao Hai, “Just don’t mind it. The Elves just haven’t had a conflict for many years. Moreover, their archery and swordsmanship are very well suited for the jungle. Almost nobody can defeat the Elves in forest combat.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he didn’t doubt this point. If the Elves didn’t have any special means, then they would’ve already become slaves a long time ago. One must know that Elves were the most valuable slaves for the Humans. However, there weren’t any Elven slaves that had been caught in the long time.

Billy looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Maybe the reason why the Elves aren’t willing to see you is because you are a Dark Mage. Elves hate Dark Mages. And since you are the most famous Dark Mage in the continent, it would be understandable if they don’t want to see you.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smiled bitterly. The Elves were advocates of nature and respected life. And for the Elves, the act of resurrecting the dead that Dark Mages do was the most blasphemous act towards their belief. It would be strange if they were to immediately like Zhao Hai.

Moreover, the Elves were also quite famous for having more tenacity than the Dwarves. Although the Dwarves can be tenacious sometimes, they can still be accomodating. Otherwise, the Dwarves wouldn’t have done business with the Humans, and Billy wouldn’t have been Juno’s good friend.

The Elves were completely solid to their beliefs. They were people who completely disliked failure and were more strict to themselves than to others. This was the reason why all of the things that the Elves produced were all works of art. They destroy everything that they deem embarrass them.

It was because of this that Zhao Hai couldn’t help but bitterly smile. He didn’t know what to say upon meeting such a race. These people seemed to be paranoid and weren’t some people that would accept an outsider’s words.

Billy looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “No matter what, you still need to see the Elves, there’s no other way. Take a rest here first, then I shall accompany you to the Elves first thing tomorrow. Although they dislike Dark Mages, I don’t think they would go far this time.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “If they don’t agree to be allies with us, then I won’t care about them anymore. If the Divine Race decides to eliminated them, then I won’t be lending them a hand. As long as they don’t cooperate with the Radiant Church, then I will leave them be.”

Billy knew that Zhao Hai was quite angry. To be honest, Billy was somewhat annoyed as well. The Radiant Church and the Dragon Race were still holding back since they were waiting for word from the Divine Race. Time was quite precious, but the Elves were actually wasting it. Zhao Hai waiting for their response was already giving them face.

Billy didn’t say anything more as he arranged a room for Zhao Hai, making him rest well. When Zhao Hai got settled in their room, they immediately went to the Space and sat inside the living room.

Laura and the others looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and knew that he was quite unhappy. To be honest, they were in a foul mood as well. Laura boiled a cup of tea and then placed in in front of Zhao Hai. Then with a soft voice she said, “Brother Hai, you shouldn’t get angry. After all, we’ll be hearing the Elves’ side tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai slowly opened his eyes, then he sighed and said, “I really want to know what is inside these Elf leaders’ heads. They had dragged such a simple thing for too long. If not for the Radiant Church and the Dragon Race making their move, i reckon that they would have dragged this matter for a longer time. What were they thinking?”

Laura forced a smile and then said, “The Elves are more closed off compared to the Beastmen and the Dwarves. Even the Fishmen had their own merchant union in order to listen to the situation of the continent. The Elves essentially had no contact with the outside world. They might come in contact with the Dwarves sometimes, but that’s it. This is the only race that had done it in the entire continent.”

Lizzy sighed, “There’s nothing strange as to why the Elves are like this. They are different from the Mermaid Race, who can just change their appearance to that of a Human, allowing them the chance to trade with the continent. The Elves simply aren’t able to do this. And whenever an Elf was spotted, people would then make them their slaves. It isn’t strange that the Elves chose to refrain from having contact with the Humans.”

Zhao Hai also sighed with a heavy heart, he was also aware of this matter. Any race would do the same if they were subjected to the same fate as the Elves.

After resting inside the Space, Billy went to look for Zhao Hai to have a meal. Zhao Hai has been very tired in the past few days. It wasn’t fatigue of the body, but it was a fatigue of the heart.

Zhao Hai’s rest in the Dwarf Mountain that night was very good. The next morning, Billy led Zhao Hai to the Elven Forest along with ten other Dwarf warriors.

The distance between the Dwarves and the Elves wasn’t short. Moreover, there was also the Accra Mountain in the middle. However, the Dwarves have developed their own methods. After countless years of effort, they had finally made a system of underground rivers to get through Accra Mountains. This gave them the capability to pass through the mountain and come out to an area close to the Elven Forest.

This was a very large project. Although they used the underground rivers, it wasn’t something that can solve everything. It was impossible for the river to deliver the Dwarves directly to the Elves. So after about 200 years of development, the Dwarves had finally made a passage that would take them quite closer to the Elves.

In order to make it more convenient to come in contact with the Elves, this route was composed of different underground rivers, allowing them to travel by boat. But even if one were to go fast, they would still need about five days before they arrive at the forest.

However, in order for the travel to become more comfortable, the Dwarves had set up some resting points all along the route. These resting points had supply of liquor and grain. All of these just to establish a good relationship with the Elven Race.

Chapter 654: Voiceless Soundbird

The Dwarf Race’s boat wasn’t big, so Zhao Hai always found himself sitting together with Billy. Naturally, he had no chance to return to the Space, therefore, he can just stay in the ship and chat with Billy.

To be honest, he was quite bored these past five days. However, even if the boat was small, there was still space for him to lie down, so Zhao Hai was able to fully rest in these five days.

Five days came by quite fast, the boat was now stopped at a pier. Billy led Zhao Hai down to the pier and walked out from the big mountain. When Zhao Hai and the others came out of the mountain, they had discovered that they were already in the forest.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but marvel at the scenery outside the mountain. The scene in front of him was just so beautiful.

The thing in front of him was a rainforest, one with lush trees everywhere. There were shrubs under the trees as well as some plants that Zhao Hai was unable to recognize. Most importantly, the place was so primitive, he can’t find a single artificial intervention here. It seems like it was a kingdom for plants, it was very attractive.

At this time, a sound suddenly came from the forest. Zhao Hai stopped, then he turned his head only to find a small magic beast. This small beast looked like a small monkey, but it was really small. It looked very cute, it had fluffy fur, two round ears, bright eyes and a look that would seem like it was just a toy,

This small monkey was also curiously looking at Zhao Hai and the others. There was no fear that was found in its face. Zhao Hai came to like this creature more and more as time passed by. He turned his hand and took out an apple before throwing it to the direction of the small monkey.

The beast was startled, it immediately whizzed towards the opposite tree. It lashed its tongue and showed its teeth towards Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai didn’t move, he only looked at the small monkey and laughed. This left the monkey with a confused expression. Then when it found the red apple on the ground, he immediately disregarded Zhao Hai and the others as it slowly jumped down from the tree. It ran towards the apple and smelled it. It expressed excitement on its face before taking a nib out of the apple, and before long the whole fruit went into its belly.

Then the small monkey turned its head to Zhao Hai, zhi zhi, it sounded, it seems like it wanted more. Zhao Hai smiled faintly before throwing another apple towards the monkey. After eating a few more apples, the small monkey made a face towards Zhao Hai before it went up the tree and squatted on a large branch, then it just slept there.

Upon seeing the small monkey’s action, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. This little thing was too lovable. Billy and the others who were right by his side were also smiling. They saw how the monkey gave Zhao Hai a grin before going to the tree and then went to sleep, not caring about Zhao Hai anymore. This made everyone laugh.

At this time, a shadow suddenly flashed from the forest. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he became alert. Then a green figure appeared in front of them.

Zhao Hai stared, but he didn’t make any moves. He noticed that the green figure in front of him was a person, a blonde man wearing a green robe.

This person was very handsome, he had a face that would make even women jealous. He had golden blonde hair that was draped freely behind him, tied by a grass rope. In his hand was a harp, and most importantly, Zhao Hai noticed that the person’s ears were longer than that of the humans. It looks quite sharp, but it didn’t hinder the man’s beauty.

On the other hand, this effeminate man looked at Zhao Hai’s group with a stern expression. Zhao Hai knew that this person was an Elf. But he didn’t speak, he knew that the first contact was Billy’s task.

Billy knew about this, therefore he immediately took a step forward and the bowed to the Elf, “Elf friend, hello. I am the Dwarf Race’s Patriarch Billy, we came here to visit the Elf Queen.”

The Elf returned the bow, and then looked at Billy and said, “I have seen Patriarch Billy, come with me, the Queen is already waiting for you.” After that, he turned his head to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t delay, he also bowed to the Elf and said, “Hello, friend. I am the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, Zhao Hai. I came here to pay a visit to the Elf Queen.”

Zhao Hai was aware that this harp bearing man had a unique occupation. The harp in the Elf’s hand wasn’t only for decoration. The strings of this harp were made of special Elven material. This not only allowed the harp to play beautiful music, it also made it possible for the user to make magical arrows from it.

Most importantly, the Elves can cast a specific magic that can give additional reinforcement to their arrows, increasing their lethality. This was something that made Elves famous in the continent.

However, not all Elves can have a harp as a weapon. Those who do were their most formidable warriors.

In addition to music and arrows, the harp also had another function, and that was to produce a barrage of agic beads.

This barrage of beads was a special attack of the Elves. It wasn’t like the arrow that contains penetrative force, the beads were things that can store up magic and exhibit various effects like explosion or other magics.

Using this function was very unusual. The elves would place their harps to the ground, and then the fingers on their both hands would alternate in stroking the instrument. With each string that was plucked, a raindrop sized bead would eject from the harp that would cause a lethal blow towards the enemy.

When the Elves waged war with the Humans, these magic beads had become a nightmare to the Human army. Ten harp-bearers working together could decimate a thousand man army almost instantaneously.

But when Zhao Hai heard this, the only thing he could think about was a machine gun, a machine gun that had explosive ammunition.

The harp-bearing Elf returned Zhao Hai’s bow and said, “We welcome the arrival of Patriarch Zhao Hai. Her Majesty is already waiting for all of you. Please come with me.” Then he turned around and led Zhao Hai’s group through the forest.

During the journey, Zhao Hai was fully convinced that the Elves were invincible in this forest, they were indeed formidable. Animals in the forest, even the most efficient predators, would still produce a sound every time they make a move. On the other hand, the Elves were completely silent. It seems like they had melded themselves to the forest, it was very astonishing.

The group ran along with the Elf as they progressed through the forest. Then all of a sudden, the Elf stopped, he played a gentle note on his harp which transformed into an beautiful melody. Then the group suddenly heard a cheerful cry from atop the tree. While Zhao Hai was still in a daze, several shadows suddenly fell down in front of them.

Zhao Hai and the others fixed their vision towards the shadows and what they saw were a group of big birds. These birds looked like cranes, but their claws were something that should belong to a hawk. Zhao Hai hadn’t seen a magic beast like this before. Moreover, these birds also have big builds, it wouldn’t be a problem for them to have a person sitting in their back.

After playing his harp, the Elf turned to Zhao Hai and the others and said, “Patriarch Billy, Patriarch Zhao Hai, please ride these Voiceless Soundbirds. Our Tree of Life is quite far from here.”

Then the Elf rode on the back of a Voiceless Soundbird. After seeing the Elf, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t delay and also rode on the backs of the other birds. Then the harp-bearer played another tune before the birds whipped their wings and flew off into the sky.

Zhao Hai already has experience with flying due to his Blood Hawk, so he didn’t feel anything in this ride. On the other hand, Billy and the others were still inexperienced in air travel. This made each and every one of their faces quite pale.

While the Elf lead the group of Voiceless Soundbirds across the forest, Zhao Hai examined the birds as he sat on the back of one of them. These birds had a mouth that was longer than the average bird’s, but not longer than a crane. Their claws were similar to those of the hawks. The Birds were two meters high and they had wings of five meters each. Moreover, even if they were carrying a person on their backs, their flight was still quite smooth, it was clear that these birds were also quite strong.

Most importantly, the cries of these birds were very clear, it was very serene and was like a melody in itself, very interesting to listen to. It might be possible that the name of Voiceless Songbird came from this.

But what made Zhao Hai feel strange was the fact that he hasn’t heard of a Voiceless Songbird in the continent before .Why was this?

One must say that the Elves had waged multiple wars with the Humans. If these birds were used by the Elves at those times, then they should’ve already been written in Human records. And even if the Radiant Church had modified the history, they wouldn’t have an incentive to eliminate the mention of these birds. Were these birds a recently tamed beast by the Elves?

In truth, Zhao Hai had guessed right. These Voiceless Soundbirds were indeed recent additions to the Elven Race. These Voiceless Soundbirds were extremely rare in the past, and they were also quite vigilant. Only Elves with affinity to these birds were able to tame them, otherwise they wouldn’t come in contact with an Elf. Also, the Voiceless Songbirds weren’t as big as they were now.

However, just more than 300 years ago, a nest of Voiceless Soundbirds suddenly fell down from the Tree of Life. This nest of eggs soon hatched and bore large Voiceless Soundbirds, two meters in height. Most importantly, these Voiceless Soundbirds weren’t vigilant towards the Elves and were even the ones to go and come in contact with them. And slowly, as time went by, these Voiceless Soundbirds had become the mounts of the Elves.

Chapter 655: Elf Queen

After studying the Voiceless Soundbird for a while, Zhao Hai found himself to have nothing else to study. He shifted his gaze towards the scenery of the Elven Forest.

Beautiful, it was too beautiful. If you gaze at the forest, you would feel that you were in a magical world. The forest was just too dazzling for him.

This green landscape was completely different from the green lands of the Prairie. The Beastman Prairie was flat, as if there was a green carpet on the ground. But here, you will be subjected to a green world. There were all kinds of trees with leaves of all shapes and sizes. If the greenery in the Prairie was like a calm sea, then the greenery here was like a raging sea.

Although this kind of sea was static, it didn’t undermine its beauty at all. It wasn’t any worse than gazing at the endless sea. Zhao Hai was quickly absorbed into the scenery of the forest.

After Billy’s discomfort passed, he was also attracted to the scene around him. His mouth opened from time to time as he expressed his admiration.

Then suddenly, a huge tree appeared in their line of sight. This was the biggest tree that Zhao Hai had ever seen. It was so huge that the Bread Trees back at Ape Island looked like saplings.

The only plant that Zhao Hai can compare to this tree would be Cai’er. The scene of Cai’er enveloping a city was completely similar to this tree, it was a shocking sight.

Zhao Hai and the others stared blankly at this tree. Then they could faintly spot a few black spots coming out of the forest. Before long, these black figures appeared in front of Zhao Hai. They were a group of Elves that were riding on top of Voiceless Soundbirds.

All of these Elves wore wearing long green robes. The robes were beautiful and looked very elegant, Zhao Hai couldn’t think of the material that these robes were made of.

The one on the lead was a female Elf. The people going along with this female Elf were all harp-bearers. On the other hand, the female Elf was actually holding a magic staff, evidently, she is a Mage.

Then the one who escorted Zhao Hai spoke to the female Elf. “My lord, Patriarch Billy and Mister Zhao Hai has arrived.”

The Elf woman nodded, then she turned her head to Billy and Zhao Hai before giving a small bow and said, “Gellar has seen Patriarch Billy and Patriarch Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai and Billy immediately returned the bow, they don’t dare to be arrogant in front of the Elves. The arrogance of these Elves were quite well known. It wouldn’t be good if Zhao Hai and the others were to be rude. At the end of the day, there was no need to offend the Elves.

Zhao Hai knew that even if these Elves have been quite hard-headed, their fighting power was still significant. It would be good if he had them as his allies.

Gellar nodded to the two men, “Please come with me, Her Majesty is already waiting for you.” Then she turned her mount around and flew towards the big tree.

To be honest, Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting this reception from the Elves. He knew that the Elves were already aware of him being a Dark Mage. For them to give him this welcome was something that was out of Zhao Hai’s imagination.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others entered the forest and into the big tree. Compared to the tree, the Elves who were busying themselves looked as insignificant as an ant.

Then with a command from the leader, the Voiceless Soundbirds fell on top of a branch of the tree. The diameter of this branch alone was ten meters, and it definitely wasn’t the largest branch.

After Zhao Hai and the others came down from the birds, Gellar went to them and said, “Everyone, please come with me.” Then she waved her hand and turned around. Zhao Hai and the others immediately followed her to walk along the branch.

While walking along, Zhao Hai also took the time to look around. This tree was really too big, he didn’t know how high it was. The only thing that he knew was that when he was at the back of the Voiceless Soundbird, he wasn’t able to see the top of this tree. The tree seems to have broken through the sky.

The stems of the tree were also quite thick, Zhao Hai didn’t have the capacity to measure it. In any case, Zhao Hai can assure that the trunk of the tree was comparable to the size of Golden Island. And almost the entire Elven population was living on this tree.

Then Gellar led Zhao Hai and the others into the trunk of the tree. The inside of this tree looked just like the interior of Dwarf Mountain. There were densely packed caverns inside with each cavern occupied by an Elf household. The inside of the tree’s trunk was very spacious, one couldn’t see the bottom of this space. At the same time, Zhao Hai can also see that there were some Elves that rode some Voiceless Soundbirds to navigate the inside.

Gellar took Zhao Hai’s group to a cavern inside the tree. This cavern had an area of more than 50 meters. It had a living room as well as a smaller caverns for bedrooms. Gellar then turned to Billy and Zhao Hai and said, “Patriarch Billy, Patriarch Zhao Hai, please take a rest here while I go and inform Her Majesty the Queen.”

Billy and Zhao Hai simultaneously gave a salute to Gellar and said, “Thank you for the trouble.” Gellar returned the salute before turning around to leave.

After Gellar left, Zhao Hai and Billy sized up the room that they were in. The chairs and tables in the room were all made of rattan. Every single one of them were a work of art. It seems like the Elves had merged the pursuit of art with their own lives.

After Billy looked around, he went to the a chair and took a seat. He let out a long sigh and said, “This was the first time that I flew in my entire life. It actually feels very good.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I actually ride a Hawk, but I really can’t feel anything special with them. On the other hand, the cries of these Voiceless Soundbirds are very pleasant to hear.”

Billy smiled and said, “I forgot that you have these flying Phantasmal Beasts. How about giving us some?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s not a problem, I can give you as many as you want. However, those who ride these beasts need to have training. Otherwise, you won’t be able to fly even if you have them.”

Billy nodded and said, “That’s great. Give me some of them when we get back. Those Phantasmal Beasts would make Dwarf transportation much better.”

Zhao Hai nodded as well, then he looked at Billy and said, “Patriarch, why did you think the Queen called for us? I’m quite worried.”

Billy stared, then he comforted Zhao Hai, “Don’t worry, it’ll be fine. Our trip this time is related to the whole continent. We’re only here to convince the Queen to join our cause.”

Zhao Hai sighed and then he said, “I really hope that the Elves would form an alliance with us. It would be best for the continent if all non-human races unite against both the Demons and the Divine Race. When that happens, I can then take the beast skin scroll to the Buddha Emperor, my Father-in-law, as well as Boris. As long as they agree to deal with the Divine Realm, then we would have nothing to fear.”

Billy looked at Zhao Hai, and then with a serious tone he said, “Rest assured, we can certainly deal with all of our enemies. Whether it be the Demons or the Divine Race, everyone who wants to enslave our races shall be eliminated.”

Zhao Hai replied, “I also believe that we can defeat them. I just hope that the Elves would be on our side. Otherwise, when the Divine Race comes, we couldn’t just accept them as allies. And with no point of retreat, the Elves would be placed in a dangerous position.”

Billy nodded, then said, “This time, whether we succeed or not, we should go and deal with the Dragon Race. Their reputation alone is causing huge problems. Moreover, their current arrangement divided the continent in half. This wouldn’t be a good thing for us when the Divine Race arrives.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’m aware of that. That is why I immediately thought of eliminating them. After I head back, I shall start to deal with the Dragons. We can’t afford to wait anymore lest more problems pop up.”

While the two were talking, a female Elf had come in from outside. She brought a bottle of wine as well as some fruits. After placing the food on the table, she looked at Billy and Zhao Hai and said, “Please have a taste. These fruits and wines are special products of our Elven Race.”

Naturally, Zhao Hai and Billy didn’t decline. After thanking the Elf, they immediately tasted the fruit and wine. There was no need to mention it, the fruit and wine were extremely good. This was especially true for the wine, it had a variety of fruit aroma as well as a very special taste.

When the two had drank a glass of liquor, Gellar can in. Upon entering, she gave a salute to the two and said, “Patriarch Billy, Patriarch Zhao Hai, Her Majesty has invited you in.” The two immediately stood up and followed Gellar out.

After walking round and round the tree for who knows how long, they finally came out from a hole in the trunk. Then they went on further outside and arrived in a thick branch. This branch was very large and had twigs that formed a platform with an area of about 10 thousand meter squared. And erected on this platform was a palace.

The palace wasn’t very big, its body was completely made out of wood branches. Moreover, these branches were still alive, as seen from the green leaves that can be seen here and there.

There were no guards in this palace. What can be seen on its huge entrance were Elves that were continuously going in and out. Before long, Gellar took the two into the palace. While walking along, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at the ground. The floor of the palace was made out of leaves that were carefully cut and arranged into very beautiful patterns.

Then Gellar led them towards a Great Hall that had ‘Life Temple’ written on it. It seems like this temple was named after the God that the Elves worship, the God of Life.

When the three people entered the temple, Zhao Hai and Billy couldn’t help but stare. Inside the temple wasn’t only the Elf Queen. There were chairs inside the hall where Elves can be seen sitting. The hall was packed, it had an audience of no less than a hundred people.

In the innermost part of the hall were three chairs. The chair on the middle was more elevated from the other two and there was a female Elf sitting on it. This elf doesn’t look old, she wore a green robe and had a magic staff on her hand. She also had a crown made out of vines on top of her head, giving her a noble aura. It seems like this person was the Elf Queen. On the left side of the Queen was another female Elf, she looked quite old due to the wrinkles on her face. However, her eyes was shining, and the seriousness on her face made people feel like she wasn’t a person that was easy to get along with.

On the left side of the Queen was a tall and handsome man. Even if one were to consider the other Elves around him, he still stood out. His figure was quite tall and he had a very symmetrical build. He had a neat small beard that didn’t make him look less attractive, instead, it actually made him exude a more manly charm. On his left hand was a sword while on his right hand was a harp. Unexpectedly, he was an Elf who was an expert in both sword and harp.

The Elves commonly studied either magic, swords, or the harp. There were almost no Elves who had both Martial and Magic cultivation. However, there were people who can actually study both the sword and the harp. However, these people were in the extreme minority. This was because studying both fields can cause a person to divide their attention, making their progress mediocre. But at the same time, there were still people among the Elven Race that were referred to as ‘Heavenly Gifted’ in their childhood. These people are extremely gifted in both sword and harp. When these people finish their study, they would be called Great Warriors. These Great Warriors are amongst the fewest of the few in the entire Elven Race.

Gellar brought Zhao Hai in front of the Queen before she stopped and bowed, “Reporting to Her Majesty, The Great Elder, and the Prince. Patriarch Billy and Patriarch Zhao Hai has arrived!”

This was a special characteristic of the Elves. Their ruling body not only comprises of the Queen, they also have the Elder’s assembly as well as the Prince’s Palace. This Elder’s Assembly was composed of Elf Elders that were chosen, majority of them were women, the other men were part of the Queen’s courtier’s, men who follow by her side. The Prince’s palace was generally the hall of the Queen’s husband. The Prince’s men also held some sort of authority. These three group were the core body of the Elf community. Once something related to the whole race comes us, these three would convene and vote for it.

Zhao Hai and Billy quickly took a step forward and gave a bow to the Queen, Great Elder, and the Prince and said, “Zhao Hai(Billy) has seen the Queen, the Great Elder, and the Prince.”

The Queen nodded and said, “In behalf of my Elven Race, I welcome Patriarch Billy and Patriarch Zhao Hai. Please have a seat.” The Queen’s voice was very nice to hear, it had a certain magnetic charm to it. Although her voice wasn’t loud, one could still hear every single word very clearly.